<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Between Us Queens</title>
    <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/7zyhYh6kVG9c6g9rQGoXJM</link>
    <description>Have you ever wondered: Na-busted na ba ang isang Miss Universe? How does a Miss International deal with PMS? Si Miss Intercontinental ay dumaan na ba sa isang crazy breakup? Join Pia Wurtzbach, Carla Lizardo and Bianca Guidotti as they shake off the glitter of the pageant world and get candid about life in this podcast meant for every girl, every mamsh, and every queen.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8a7120f3dfa05cbe058389ab2c</url>
      <title>Between Us Queens</title>
      <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/7zyhYh6kVG9c6g9rQGoXJM</link>
    </image>
    <language>tl</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:49:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>For Better or For Worse?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4M5c99kzUeznknxjJgmi2p?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Relationships can be full of rainbows and butterflies, but in the long run, it's also about hard work and compromise. We talked to sportscaster, podcaster, and gamer Cesca Litton-Kalaw about how to keep the flame in a marriage alive and burning bright. Married for almost a decade, she shared some advice which are very useful especially to those who are thinking of settling down! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4M5c99kzUeznknxjJgmi2p</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2724</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work-Life Balance</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/44QuxKOF51y21qTjIdnrLE?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In the fast-paced world that we live in today, work-life balance seems to take a backseat here in the Philippines. With life returning back to normalcy, will we be seeing more workplaces adapting or is it back to the same old grind? We talk about hustle culture, overtime and what to look out for when choosing a career. Listen to this episode to find out more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44QuxKOF51y21qTjIdnrLE</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1876</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do We Over-Romanticize Love?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6VpMb8VaQ9rVlDYJJX9K9d?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The recent debacle at the Oscars sparked many different opinions about how one would react in the same situation. Was it too much, or just the right thing to do? This led us to another question from our FB group: do we Filipinos over-romanticize love? We also share our thoughts about the different biases women face when it comes to romantic relationships. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6VpMb8VaQ9rVlDYJJX9K9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2351</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving Out</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6hAwykLOQSE7Xk63mRUS0S?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Have you ever wondered, when is the best time to move out and be your best independent self? How does one prepare for the responsibilities of being on our own? We shared our own experiences stepping into the adult world - when and how decided to live solo, and the kind of lifestyle we had to adapt to survive the grown-up world. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6hAwykLOQSE7Xk63mRUS0S</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2264</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relationship Advice From The Queens</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1V2n8DrgTV4c7opMLOSmCK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>There are so many ongoing conversations in our community - from moving on from a bad relationship, to dealing with love drain. In this episode, we tried our very best to lend an ear, hoping that it gives light and hope to the Queens out there who needs a hug or a shoulder to cry on. Feel free to check out our Facebook or Discord group to join in the conversation! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1V2n8DrgTV4c7opMLOSmCK</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1986</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are you an Introvert or an Extrovert?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4aJDjxb0VVCLCXqKDr9E16?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Socializing with people is an important skill that one must master. Other people have it easy, while some would need to gather a lot of courage just to be able to start a conversation. Which type are you? In this episode we discuss if we’re introverts or extroverts, how it affects us, and how being aware of our personality type helps us navigate through life. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4aJDjxb0VVCLCXqKDr9E16</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2520</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invasion of Ukraine by Russia feat. BJ Enverga</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7LXeWiDtS9MUkD01tba0Fa?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>There’s a great conflict happening in the northeastern hemisphere of the world. As we’ve seen on the news, Ukraine is currently being invaded by Russia. We invited Director and Assistant Professor of the European Studies Program of Ateneo de Manila University, BJ Enverga, to enlighten us with how this conflict arose, how it affects us Filipinos, and what we can do to help in our own little way.  Donate at https://donate.unhcr.org/int/en/ukraine-emergency Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7LXeWiDtS9MUkD01tba0Fa</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2638</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landing Your Dream Job feat. Aaron Atayde</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0j0LGukgiy7dhk6Vojws5R?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>As kids, we try to do well in school in the hopes of being one step closer to our dreams and aspirations. We invited a King on this episode to talk about how he was able to land his dream job amidst the pandemic. ESPN US SportsCenter Anchor Aaron Atayde gives tips on how you can also achieve that career that you've been eyeing since childhood. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0j0LGukgiy7dhk6Vojws5R</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2514</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets To Everlasting Friendships feat. Riki Flo &amp; Tin Gamboa</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1CbNESPNdJtYsCps2B6O0w?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>True friendships are hard to come by, especially those that will withstand the test of time. Is there a perfect recipe to being BFFs 4Ever? Listen to today's episode as we talk to The Week Sauce hosts Riki and Tin about how their bond was formed. They also shared a couple of tips on how to make your relationship a safe space so that you will be in each other's lives 'til you're old and gray. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1CbNESPNdJtYsCps2B6O0w</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2101</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-Nup Agreement 101 feat. Atty PY Caunan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2TSfTcp5VHesuU9C1hNel1?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>A cultural taboo topic takes the spotlight on the pod today, as we believe this is something that needs to be talked about. Should pre-nuptial agreements be considered before getting married? We invited Atty. PY Caunan to let us know more about the benefits of drafting a pre-nup, who might need it, and how to get one. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2TSfTcp5VHesuU9C1hNel1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2310</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lowdown on Narcissists feat. Dr. Joyce Maglaque</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6nzoCaSnYhyYf4iYUQ3M47?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We hear the word narcissist thrown around a lot when we encounter people that are full of themselves - but how do we identify someone who actually has narcissistic personality disorder? We are joined by Dr. Joyce Maglaque, a psychiatrist specializing in general adult and addiction therapy to give us all the details - traits to watch out for, how it's developed &amp; diagnosed, as well as some advice on how to set healthy boundaries when dealing with a narcissist. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6nzoCaSnYhyYf4iYUQ3M47</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2452</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Piece of Biancake</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4ngxx38kyc7AhjQRX60VBo?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The three of us enjoy playing video games together once in a while, shooting zombies is one of our favorite bonding activities! We wanted to learn more about the world of gaming, so we invited international gamer and streamer Bianca Yao, popularly known as Biancake, to share her story. Listen as she tells us how she got her big slice of the gaming cake (hihi), how she pursued her passion, and how she navigates the male-dominated space with grace. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ngxx38kyc7AhjQRX60VBo</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1968</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Journeyuuuh of Mimiyuuuh</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/601UjuIW16Z0JPdC8HMnZU?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Her infectious happiness and out of this world vocal chords has taken the internet by storm, and she's on the pod to grace us with her wit and charm. Mimiyuuuh chats with us as she gives us a glimpse of journey to success in social media, and what her plans are in the near future. Listen in as Mimiyuuuh shares tips on how to succeed in your chosen field and skrrrt your way to the top! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">601UjuIW16Z0JPdC8HMnZU</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2145</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarot Reading feat. Niki Vizcarra</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4pBhgKfeh6QYYoyOz8Iyii?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This year, we’re going all out with manifesting our goals and getting what we want for our future! With us today is International Tarot Reader and Paranormal Expert Niki Vizcarra, giving us a glimpse of what our future holds and sharing bits of advice to ensure that we achieve what's written in the stars. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4pBhgKfeh6QYYoyOz8Iyii</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2522</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Organize Your Life feat. Mica Canto</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4DH96DUowootsVwMnnrhHr?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Ringing in the new year means decluttering our own spaces for good energy to flow. We've all been there though - attempted to start organizing our things, but ended up making a bigger mess. Where do we begin and how can we be more consistent? We invited the Queen of organization and founder of Tidily Ever After, Mica Canto, as she gave us very helpful tips on making this year a very tidy one! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4DH96DUowootsVwMnnrhHr</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2105</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Year, Better Me</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2oJtbdV5WOwOnr7CsnL8aK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>I don’t know about you, but we’re feeling 2022! The new year is here and it’s another chance for us to manifest our dreams, experience opportunities, and follow through with our resolutions. In this episode, we talked about how we can be better versions of ourselves and how we can carry through with all our plans for the next 365 days! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2oJtbdV5WOwOnr7CsnL8aK</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1888</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Traditions &amp; Cheers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1N0ho37nEyBOxz5VBHbziZ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The holidays aren’t complete without traditions with our family and loved ones. It makes the celebration more festive and heartfelt! We talked our favorite Christmas gifts and meals, and we also featured answers from the Queendom!  In the spirit of giving, let’s do our part in giving to our brothers and sisters affected by Typhoon Odette who need our help. Here are some avenues to send assistance to:  Waves for Water Save the Children Tanging Yaman Foundation Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1N0ho37nEyBOxz5VBHbziZ</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1799</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Awkwardness in the Better Normal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1sMV8C9j2jPW3u8UrtCY87?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Queens, we finally saw each other in person after almost two years! We’ve been recording all our episodes digitally. That means all weekly episodes of BUQ were done with us not not actually seeing each other. So you can imagine how excited/awkward we were to see each other again in real life.  As the world starts opening up, we're sure that we're all a bit rusty with our social skills! We talk all about social awkwardness because of the pandemic in this episode. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1sMV8C9j2jPW3u8UrtCY87</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1771</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manifesting Joy feat. Kimi Lu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0lhpTnVJiCItZbJz27GNdr?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>As we get ready to wrap up another year, we need to take the time to reflect about ourselves &amp; how we want to grow moving forward. What do we want to attract into our lives? How do we manifest joy in the things that we do? The Queens sit down with renowned global Life Coach Kimi Lu to discuss how we can become more confident and grateful so we can be ready to rock 2022. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0lhpTnVJiCItZbJz27GNdr</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2043</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shopping for Sustainability feat. Jammy Magsino</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/747AUb1onKn8kmFMTB01Ok?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Climate change is a global issue that needs to be addressed not just by governments, but by every citizen in the world. The Queens sit down with Frankie and Friends founder, Jammy Magsino, to talk about promoting sustainable &amp; ethical shopping habits that we can start to apply this holiday season. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">747AUb1onKn8kmFMTB01Ok</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1671</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life of a Diplomat feat. Ambassador Laure Beaufils</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6edvs7L00ps7gnN6Ymt87y?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>As women we are expected to balance our career together with home life. It's easy to say, but very challenging to do - especially when your career demands constant travel and uprooting your family frequently. The Queens sit down together with British Ambassador to the Republic of the Philippines, Ambassador Laure Beaufils. Listen as she fills in the Queens on how diplomatic life has played out for her, and what her personal advocacies are. This episode will give confidence not just to diplomat aspirants out there, but to all our queen listeners as well. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6edvs7L00ps7gnN6Ymt87y</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2041</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex Positivity feat. Amina Swanepoel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6csLAz0QXBXmm56YCSAcQm?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>A harsh reality is that we still live in a society that perpetuates macho culture, and Filipinas have to deal with being objectified and sexualized on a daily basis. It's very important to empower women by letting them know their reproductive rights and how to express consent. The Queens sit down with Roots of Health founder, Amina Swanepoel, for an educational episode about sex positivity and how we can take back control of our bodies. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6csLAz0QXBXmm56YCSAcQm</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2081</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask The Queens!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5aGlBbkMRiy3Yg3KVzYdap?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The Queendom asked, and the Queens answered! In true pageant fashion, we asked our listeners to send in questions and the Queens were given just 45 seconds to answer. Join in on the fun as we talk about topics ranging from drunk stories to some serious life advice. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5aGlBbkMRiy3Yg3KVzYdap</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1981</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Move On from a Breakup</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6qnVr2H758lYvK40ZFxghr?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>To anyone who's been in a failed relationship, we all know that breaking up with your partner is never easy. But the hardest part is moving on from it. The Queens sit down and talk about their own experiences with difficult breakups. Listen in as they share tips on how to move on and help yourself get back on your feet. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6qnVr2H758lYvK40ZFxghr</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1870</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wedding Planning During a Pandemic feat. Amanda Tirol</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3hPpett3hIodapKuLR9bWQ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>With the pandemic affecting mass gatherings and especially weddings, it can be tough to plan one during this time. The Queens sit down with renowned wedding planner and owner of Boracay Weddings, Amanda Tirol, to chat about the challenges and benefits of getting married during a pandemic and how to go about it. Listen in as Bianca also shares her own pandemic wedding planning story! Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3hPpett3hIodapKuLR9bWQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1996</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel Tips &amp; Stories</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3rC6Jy1zIhK9RqaoKgAnfi?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We've been stuck in a bubble for quite some time and everyone is itching to take a break and have a change of scenery! The Queens sit down and exchange stories about their favorite places to go to, funny airport memories, and how to travel in the new normal. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3rC6Jy1zIhK9RqaoKgAnfi</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1765</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Money or More Happiness?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6yRhn6fKDjQIzfEHVEL098?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In our careers, we tend to reach a crossroad where we need to make tough decisions that will greatly affect our lives. Don't worry, everyone goes through this! But how do we make the right choice? The Queens sit down and weigh in on choosing between a higher paying job within a highly stressful environment VS a job you're passionate about that offers lower pay. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6yRhn6fKDjQIzfEHVEL098</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1770</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coping During The Pandemic feat. Cat Trivino</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2jKN0JXEnK7Zhd4Xp6hGfU?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>With most of us working from home, we all can feel the pandemic fatigue - demanding work hours with little or no time for rest. How do we make sure to break from this cycle that makes us feel isolated and weary? The Queens sit down with co-founder and Chief Marketing Officer of MindNation and the Branding Director for non-profit CORA Philippine, Cat Triviño as they enumerate the steps that we can do to support our mental health during this time of pandemic.   If you would like to get help and support, Mind Nation is having a sale on their therapy sessions which you can avail this 10.10! Click here to know more.   Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2jKN0JXEnK7Zhd4Xp6hGfU</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1830</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dealing with Siblings feat. Sarah Wurtzbach</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1aLJN64co0tUVBF6DLNzwt?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Have you ever had any conflicts between siblings or family members? How were you able to resolve them smoothly? The Queens sit down with Sarah Wurtzbach, the beautiful sister of Pia Wurtzbach. Listen as we talk about family dynamics and how to keep peace and harmony within the family. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1aLJN64co0tUVBF6DLNzwt</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1776</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking Barriers and Dealing with Pressure feat. Hidilyn Diaz</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6xTptdVnanE4ezmNzI3JQ0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Being a successful woman in a male-dominated space is such a great feat - but getting there takes a lot of courage and determination. The Queens sit down with gold-medalist athlete Hidilyn Diaz as she talks about her journey to her breathtaking win at the Tokyo Olympics 2020. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6xTptdVnanE4ezmNzI3JQ0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1797</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unapologetic Confidence feat. Ayn Bernos</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6HpMUsm3FvfikBiFFWNvTY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In our journey towards self-love, we're usually our own harshest critics. How do we break through society's norms to be confident enough to achieve our goals? The Queens sit down with teacher, podcaster and MUPH candidate Ayn Bernos to talk about how she's learned how to fully embrace herself, and to use that strength to inspire others.  Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6HpMUsm3FvfikBiFFWNvTY</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1797</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gen Z 101 feat. AC Bonifacio</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1FY2Von2kICBXnjZnAbobX?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>To all the Millenials feeling like they're losing touch with the latest Gen Z trends, this is the episode for you. No cap. The Queens sit down with dancer, actress and social media star AC Bonifacio as they talk about the distinctive traits of each generation and how we can all learn from each other. uWu Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1FY2Von2kICBXnjZnAbobX</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1796</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dealing with Long Distance Relationships</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6JFEU7s8jIuCVIAq9ByiMa?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Long distance relationships have always been defined by the miles (or continents!) that are separating lovers. But with the pandemic still going on, LDR has been given a new meaning. The Queens sit down and talk about the different ways on dealing with this challenging relationship sitch. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6JFEU7s8jIuCVIAq9ByiMa</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1748</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Guys and Girls Be Bestfriends?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2GyqKRaHF45SvQLLlf5wHu?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Society says we can't have a platonic relationship with the opposite sex. True or not true? The Queens talk about their own take on guys and girls being best of friends without catching romantic feelings for one another. They also react to stories from the BUQ community! Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2GyqKRaHF45SvQLLlf5wHu</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1739</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's Your Zodiac Sign?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3uIs3hDwqXqZiOVrIXJ9XG?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Astrology can be fun to read about, and can serve as a guide for life decisions and relationships. Are the stars aligned for you and your barkada? The queens have a fun discussion about their signs, and all the ways they click and clash as a group. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3uIs3hDwqXqZiOVrIXJ9XG</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1769</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Effect on Body Image</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4vCt6fEdWCkz5XiG63DeM1?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Studies show that the lockdowns are linked to a shift in body image. Some have been given a positive boost, but others have struggled with the relationship they have with their own body. This episode, we focus on how we're feeling and what we can do to give ourself that big dose of self-love that every queen deserves. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | TikTok Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter | TikTok Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4vCt6fEdWCkz5XiG63DeM1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1714</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Weirdest DMs We Got</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6RmHOX5eSEHWBtZQduhtEX?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We've all probably gotten some weird DMs on our social media accounts. Sometimes, these are messages that we can simply laugh off. Unfortunately, we also experience messages that are considered online harassment. The Queens share some DMs from their personal inboxes, and give their insights on how to best deal with these experiences in the digital space. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6RmHOX5eSEHWBtZQduhtEX</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1785</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voter Registration with Ria Atayde</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7A71Lz075HJpoPVudaqz5f?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>With everything that's happening in the world, the need for good governance has been highlighted. As a democratic country, we Filipinos have the responsibility to make our voices heard. We need to to elect good leaders for a brighter future for our country. In this episode, we sit down with actress and We The Youth Vote leader Ria Atayde to share everything you need to know about registering to vote. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7A71Lz075HJpoPVudaqz5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1890</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Along With In-Laws</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3nlEchJrjLNtAEX88DjQKq?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Getting along with your significant other's parents is usually a big plus for any serious couple. How can you make a good impression, and how do you build a good relationship with your current or future in-laws? The queens talk about their experiences and share tips on how they won over the hearts of their boyfriend/husband's families. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3nlEchJrjLNtAEX88DjQKq</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1715</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toxic Masculinity feat. Chico Garcia &amp; Gino Quillamor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1HOs85BcFnhUjbNehuyMUS?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Toxic masculinity is something that affects not only women, but affects men and society as a whole. How do we experience it in our daily lives, and how do we change these standards for the next generation? The Queens discuss these questions with radio DJs, hosts and fellow podcaster Chico Garcia and Gino Quillamor for this episode. This is our first time having KINGS over! You can listen to their new podcast, OnlyFun with Chico and Gino, on Spotify as well. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1HOs85BcFnhUjbNehuyMUS</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1851</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Your Passion &amp; Purpose feat. Trese Lead Actress Liza Soberano</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5ND0X6ulhKq7Wep5zx6w0q?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>What does passion and purpose mean to you? How do you figure out what you really want to do with your life? These questions that are difficult to answer, so we invited the amazing Liza Soberano (who is the voice of Alexandra Trese!) to help us out. We share our personal perspectives and bits of advice, so come join us! Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ND0X6ulhKq7Wep5zx6w0q</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2040</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What If We Weren't Beauty Queens?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1fojkFsfAs7JfxP1H7hHnK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>A lot of people end up pursuing something completely different from their childhood dreams - us included. That makes us wonder at times, "what if I pursued something completely different? What would my life be like today?" We explored these questions in this episode, and realized that things have a funny way of working out in the end. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fojkFsfAs7JfxP1H7hHnK</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1410</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maintaining A Healthy Mindset During This Pandemic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6u4qqn34pZTBgBj9yizAjs?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In the last year, we've been experiencing a rollercoaster emotions. We may have felt lost, overwhelmed, and confused. How do we deal with these emotions and maintain a healthy mindset during this crisis? The queens share their experiences and how they've been helping themselves in this episode. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6u4qqn34pZTBgBj9yizAjs</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1750</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 Vaccine Talk feat. Dr. Ronnivin Pagtakhan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3r1KMX3RrWd94sZmUt6o57?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The vaccination program here in the Philippines is ongoing, and is a very important step in achieving herd immunity. We know that you queens may have a lot of questions about the process and about some myths that are floating around online, so we invited Love Yourself founder and director Dr. Ronnivin Pagtakhan to lay down the facts. We are also encouraging everyone to seek out trusted sources of information like the World Health Organization and Love Yourself to get answers to these questions. Visit who.int or loveyourself.ph to learn more and take steps to bring us all closer. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3r1KMX3RrWd94sZmUt6o57</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1640</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Be A Better Ally feat. Mela Habijan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6aCnoQyer7aIfRmku04glC?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Happy Pride, Queens! For today's episode, we talk to Miss Trans Global 2020 Mela Habijan about inclusivity in pageantry, the SOGIE bill &amp; how to be a better ally. We also listen to the life stories of some of our listeners about the challenges that they face as part of the community. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6aCnoQyer7aIfRmku04glC</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1650</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friendship Red Flags Pt. 2 feat. Saab Magalona-Bacarro</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7qiEYfLOXwouoQKnWLsELY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We felt like there was a lot more to unpack with the friendship red flags conversation, so here's a surprise episode drop! We also invited actress, host &amp; fellow podcaster Saab Magalona-Bacarro to share her thoughts on the topic. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7qiEYfLOXwouoQKnWLsELY</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1799</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friendship Red Flags Pt. 1</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1McobasSxDrUFiMzKFrKyM?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>After talking about romantic relationship red flags, we decided to sit down and explore the topic further. We need to be mindful about ALL our relationships, and sometimes friendships can turn toxic as well. For this week, the Queens share their friend breakup experiences and red flags they usually look out for to see if a friendship is worth keeping. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1McobasSxDrUFiMzKFrKyM</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1646</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Things We Wish We Knew Before Turning 30</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4qyZjP7I3tdjY1qabST56z?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Our life experiences allow us to learn and grow as women… but do you ever wish that you had a time machine so you could give advice to your younger self? There are times when we feel that way! So we decided to record an episode sharing 5 things we wish we knew before we turned 30. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4qyZjP7I3tdjY1qabST56z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1746</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raising Strong Women feat. VP Leni Robredo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7ylhc8CiMNx83yaUWRQYtU?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Any mom would want to see her daughter take on the world. How does one raise a strong, independent woman who won't let society's standards get in the way? For this episode, VP Leni Robredo gives us advice on motherhood, empowerment &amp; breaking the glass ceiling. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ylhc8CiMNx83yaUWRQYtU</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2181</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relationship Red Flags</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7l1ExZ22wA7YwT5rINmJ0K?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Sabi nga nila, love is blind. And sometimes, reality hits you when you’re already in deep. The Queens discuss specific traits that led them to end relationships, and red flags that they usually watch out for when it comes to commitment. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7l1ExZ22wA7YwT5rINmJ0K</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1752</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motherhood feat. Anne Curtis-Smith Heussaff</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7JCLI7VTVgf2QvVKWHYdor?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Happy mother's day, queen mommies! For this episode, we have Anne Curtis-Smith Heussaff joining in on the conversation. We discuss the biggest changes in her life as a career woman and her journey with baby Dahlia so far. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7JCLI7VTVgf2QvVKWHYdor</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1813</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Between us queens, let's talk about our period!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4L1ccUprFxrBhvF9889GqD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Do you look back at your embarrassing tagos/period moments and cringe a little inside? Well, don't! Every queen goes through the samel thing &amp; it's about time to normalize talking about our time of the month. For this episode, let's talk all about our periods! Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on social media as well: Bianca Guidotti: Facebook | Instagram  Carla Lizardo: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube Pia Wurtzbach: Facebook | Instagram | Youtube | Twitter Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4L1ccUprFxrBhvF9889GqD</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1759</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Between us Queens, kuripot o galante ka ba?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3khU2rNecxUIllq7nRIk3p?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Let's talk about money. Are you the type to be super tight with spending or do you love splurging? The queens talk about their spending styles when it comes to different situations - from gift giving to handling utang. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on Instagram as well: @piawurtzbach @bianca.guidotti @carlalizardo_ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3khU2rNecxUIllq7nRIk3p</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1335</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Between us Queens, agree ba kayo sa live-in? feat. Ellen Adarna</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/67Mu3IxXXNsc50bNUPxY8y?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The idea of living-in before marriage is still generally frowned upon in the Philippines. Is it time to change this traditional mindset? The Queens sit down with TV Actress Ellen Adarna and talk about the pros and cons of living together with your partner prior to marriage. Join the Between Us Queens Facebook group and share with us your thoughts about this! Follow the Queens on Instagram as well: @piawurtzbach @bianca.guidotti @carlalizardo_ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67Mu3IxXXNsc50bNUPxY8y</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1915</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Between us Queens, does age matter in love? feat. Pauleen Luna-Sotto</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1KuN3jtYhNApDSeocQ6JFC?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Relationships with big age gaps tend to raise eyebrows and attract criticism. But does age really matter when it comes to love? Or do other factors play a much bigger role? The Queens sit down with TV Host Pauleen Luna-Sotto to explore this question. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1KuN3jtYhNApDSeocQ6JFC</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2002</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Between us Queens, what are the dumbest fights that you've ever had?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5QbW04MMonqhYMCeb3nqMc?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Some days, you can't just seem to see eye to eye with your significant other. What might seem petty for you could be a big deal for him, and vice versa. This episode, the Queens talk about the dumbest fights they've ever had. We also have some great stories from our listeners, so stay tuned until the very end! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5QbW04MMonqhYMCeb3nqMc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1888</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Between us Queens, is happiness equal to success? feat. Bianca Gonzalez-Intal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/75KFooXqqEDfatV90Z0VIO?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>How do you define success? Is it all about achieving wealth &amp; fame? Does it equate to being happy? The Queens sit down with host, writer &amp; advocate Bianca Gonzalez-Intal to explore what it truly means to be successful in life. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75KFooXqqEDfatV90Z0VIO</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1841</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Between us Queens, what are your go-to landi moves?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5dxFUn11sZ2nLJ3AR9RJyq?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>There's absolutely nothing wrong with women making the first move! The Queens share their go-to landi moves in this Between Us Queens episode. What worked &amp; what failed for them? Listen to find out! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5dxFUn11sZ2nLJ3AR9RJyq</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1985</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Between us Queens, what’s your crazy breakup story?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0GuADpUITHcZWd0neDo1LO?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Ending a relationship is never easy. With all those emotions, things can get pretty crazy. In this episode, the Queens discuss their own memorable breakup stories and how it helped them grow as women. We also get to hear some great stories from Between Us Queens listeners! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0GuADpUITHcZWd0neDo1LO</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1773</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Between us Queens, anong mga trip mo 20 years ago?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4nQOJ0rGIyCEXMxueIcjIw?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>5, 6, 7, 8! Let’s throw it back to the early 2000’s! Remember elephant pants, Bazooka, chinese garter, and Steps? The Queens sit down for a nostalgic discussion about the TV series, songs, and websites that got them through the drama of high school. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4nQOJ0rGIyCEXMxueIcjIw</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1717</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Between us Queens, nag quarter life crisis ka na ba?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/47RxPUh5gn5H5ZxjtOs8ji?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We all hit roadblocks in life where we’re unsure about what to do next. The Queens talk about their own personal “quarter life” crisis experiences and what they did to overcome it. FB Group: Between Us Queens Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47RxPUh5gn5H5ZxjtOs8ji</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2638</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Between us Queens, bakit ang hirap magpapayat?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/08A5QK3yV6lhPYUm78IgY8?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Bakit ang hirap magpapayat? A question that we can't seem to shake off. The Queens talk about fad diets, fitness routines that they swear by, and working on a healthy body image. Facebook Group: Between Us Queens Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08A5QK3yV6lhPYUm78IgY8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2983</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Between us Queens, kailan dapat magpakasal?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4wmm6s7MVZ0mqMgBe9mMfZ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>What is the right age to get married, and what are the factors that should be considered before taking the plunge? The Queens answer the dreaded questions Filipino titas love to ask whenever there’s a family get-together. Facebook Group: Between Us Queens Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4wmm6s7MVZ0mqMgBe9mMfZ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2475</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Between us Queens</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4gp9hTtGFKjKgRiFYYIv3w?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4gp9hTtGFKjKgRiFYYIv3w</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>187</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

