<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Call Her Daddy</title>
    <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/7bnjJ7Va1nM07Um4Od55dW</link>
    <description>Call Her Daddy started as a podcast and evolved into a global movement. Alex Cooper bulldozed a lane of her own, spitting in the face of misogyny and putting a modern twist on feminism. The woman-led empire produces raw, relevant and provocative conversations that promote sexual liberty and personal empowerment while stripping away any barriers of judgement. Strap in and enjoy, and more importantly - welcome to the Daddy Gang. Episodes on Wednesday - only on Spotify starting July 21st.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8ad67368b7bb79a6dbe12a3444</url>
      <title>Call Her Daddy</title>
      <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/7bnjJ7Va1nM07Um4Od55dW</link>
    </image>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:17:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Get High (4/20 Edition)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1m8wVbQGUlmfe9FHgTnIBc?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, join Father Cooper for a SOLO EPISODE. Call Her Daddy debuts the very first vlog podcast. Listen AND WATCH your father as she gets stoned out of her mind in celebration of 4/20. Before getting completely baked, Big Al reminisces on the first time she got high- it was her, three men, in a car, with a water bottle.  Do you like to fuck while you’re high? Al does! Your dad shares the first time she got stoned, with the ultimate pothead, Slim Shady (and trust me he’s no Angel). It resulted in a sexual nightmare.  And, with baseball season upon us, Alex found a way to throw two other MLB teams under the bus by sharing the shopping list of drugs they demanded she buy them. But hey, it’s their money!!  As the weed sets in, Alex get’s deep, answering the philosophical questions you all want to know the answers to. The munchies hit - so join your Papa in the kitchen while she makes her favorite high snack. She didn’t burn the house down… that’s a win. Watch Alex like you’ve never seen her before…taking a gravity bong to the face. Come get stoned with your dad and let’s celebrate this holiday.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1m8wVbQGUlmfe9FHgTnIBc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2679</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do I tell him I love him? </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3O9QeB3ZdmKE0SafCYNvom?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In a highly anticipated trip, we are heading to France. Let’s talk about the L-bomb and when to drop it. I’ve been with my partner for a year, is it appropriate to say I love you? What if they don’t say it back? There are so many questions surrounding this moment and Big Al addresses them all. We all know about Only Fans, but what about when your boyfriend is the one who has one? Let’s pause for a little PSA. No one should tell you to put your vibrator away during sex, you deserve all of the clit stimulation in the world. Alex also provides advice on how to reset your relationship and escape the “ick”. Buckle up for a little story time, Big Al takes us on a journey that begins with a purity ring and ends with a google doc coordinated sex spree. Enjoy!</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3O9QeB3ZdmKE0SafCYNvom</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1557</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIP STASSIE BABY [VIDEO]</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6F1sPChJccoLqcnmj2t8ZI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>(VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper sits down with the woman who never does interviews…Stas Karanikolaou. Alex uncovers the mystery behind Stas and asks the questions we all want the answers to. How did Stas rise to her current level of fame? Is she still friends with a certain friend? Stas opens up about her social anxiety and the role her friends play in supporting her through it. Alex and Stas discuss the evolution of plastic surgery and how temporary trends can impact lifelong decisions. Does Stas regret any procedure and would she take anything back? As the drinks continue to flow the conversation becomes even more unfiltered and we see how Stas has rightfully earned the title of “life of the party”. We get the inside tea on her sex and dating life like you’ve never heard before. Enjoy! </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6F1sPChJccoLqcnmj2t8ZI</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3777</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girl talk (ft. Drinking with Cazzie David) [VIDEO]</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1fHMDjKy20yecqMcWW1zB8?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>(VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper is joined by Cazzie David. Recently, the girls reached a milestone in their friendship…they went on vacation together. Alex and Cazzie debrief their Cabo trip and breakdown their first ever fight. Did Alex commit the largest possible vacation sin or is Cazzie just being dramatic? Right when it seems the tension has died down, Alex calls Cazzie out…for her cameo in a Hannah Montana episode (low blow?). At least the girls can agree on one thing - their love for reality television. If they were cast on the bachelor, what would their strategy be? Would Alex show up in sweats? In this rollercoaster ride of an episode Alex and Cazzie take us through MANY topics and constantly have us wondering…do they hate each other? Are they being serious or sarcastic? Guess you’ll just have to listen and decide for yourself. Enjoy!</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fHMDjKy20yecqMcWW1zB8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3424</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix a Broken Heart (ft. Guy Winch) </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/21EOvErpVnMJ3A84VLAyiI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper is joined by clinical psychologist Dr. Guy Winch. There is the classic saying…only time heals a broken heart. WRONG! Thankfully Guy is here to provide us with tangible advice on how to navigate heartbreak and get ourselves back out there. What are the rules when it comes to stalking an ex on social media? Can I ever go back to “our” favorite restaurant again? How do I know when I’m ready to date again? Do I really need “closure” in order to move on? If you are one of the lucky few who has not experienced heartbreak, you surely know someone who has. Guy provides guidelines on how to be a good friend to someone experiencing a breakup while also ensuring that you are setting boundaries for your own mental health. Daddy Gang, if you or someone you know has recently experienced heartbreak, this episode is a must listen.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21EOvErpVnMJ3A84VLAyiI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2350</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicole Byer [VIDEO]</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2k5WhJFSSPaJR5Ff3VgBWv?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>(VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper sits down with comedian Nicole Byer. Alex and Nicole discuss the struggles of online dating and break down each of the dating apps. We all love a little positive reinforcement in the bedroom right?  C’mon men, we need some moans! The duo discusses strategies to elicit verbal feedback from men during sex. While playing never have I ever, we learn that Alex had a sugar daddy, Nicole has fucked more than one person in 24 hours, and both have filmed themselves during sex. Nicole also shares some insight on the newest and hottest vibrator…a Theragun! Sometimes the pussy just needs a real pounding. Alex and Nicole provide the Daddy Gang with solid advice on fucking your gym trainer, giant dicks, nude etiquette, sexting and more. Enjoy!</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2k5WhJFSSPaJR5Ff3VgBWv</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3468</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Courtney Stodden [VIDEO]</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3UrIY0bY1q4fAxBQv67cCD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>(VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper sits down with Courtney Stodden. Courtney broke national headlines back in 2011 when at 16 years old they married 51 year old Doug Hutchison. At the time, Courtney received endless online hate and negative media coverage. Courtney, a child, received death threats, was stalked by the paparazzi, sexualized, and labeled a whore. Courtney is now 27 years old, has gotten into therapy, and started their recovery journey. This is a story of child abuse that began 10 years ago and after finalizing their divorce in 2020, Courtney is now beginning to process what it means to be a survivor. This episode discusses adult subject matter, including descriptions of sexual abuse of a child, and is intended for adult consumption only. Listener discretion is advised. If you have been affected by sexual violence, free, confidential support is available 24/7 through RAINN's National Sexual Assault Hotline at 800.656-4673 and online.rainn.org.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3UrIY0bY1q4fAxBQv67cCD</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3889</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anna Delvey [VIDEO]</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0FbUJq278xkiGNSx9UQABt?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>(VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper interviews Anna Delvey from prison … or should we say Anna Sorokin. Alex doesn’t go easy on the fake German heiress who conned the elite of New York City. Find out the answers to the questions we all want to know. Watch the video for the full experience. You won’t be sorry. Enjoy.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0FbUJq278xkiGNSx9UQABt</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3337</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where'd all my friends go? (ft. Mel Robbins) </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6PkQKO0eAXz7UMpeONkAo0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper is joined by author and motivational speaker, Mel Robbins. Have you ever felt insecure about the number of friends you have? Do you define your worth by your friend group? Alex and Mel normalize going through periods of life where friends fade and the focus shifts - to being a good friend to yourself. Mel shares concrete advice on how to alter this pattern of thinking, so that we stop defining ourselves by external factors and take control of our lives.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6PkQKO0eAXz7UMpeONkAo0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1588</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chloe Cherry [VIDEO]</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/41o6GBWGnf3PiUWyh84s3V?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>(VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper sits down with Euphoria star Chloe Cherry. Chloe provides the inside scoop of her time on set for Euphoria and details what it was like to work with some of the biggest names in the industry. Prior to joining the cast of Euphoria, Chloe was a highly accomplished porn star. Chloe opens up about the effect her porn career had on relationships with friends, family and her own body image. Alex and Chloe break down some of her most popular porn videos and give some top notch tips on anal, double penetration, roman showers, and squirting. Chloe also details the most lucrative videos she created for her Only Fans account and shares the wild requests she would get from men to role play. Enjoy Daddies! This episode includes discussion of eating disorders and graphic sexual material. Please keep this in mind when deciding if, how and when you’ll listen. For resources on these topics, visit spotify.com/resources.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41o6GBWGnf3PiUWyh84s3V</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3255</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Those Feeling Lost in Their 20s… (ft. Mel Robbins)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5OZEvC4mOoSQWgE2CDJ4Ie?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper is joined by author and motivational speaker Mel Robbins. Have you ever felt lost or uncertain with the direction of your life? Why is this feeling especially amplified in our 20’s? Alex and Mel break down how this sense of uncertainty is rooted in insecurity, comparison, and regret. Mel shares concrete advice on how to regain control of your life and provides a new perspective on how to positively approach social media. Enjoy!</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5OZEvC4mOoSQWgE2CDJ4Ie</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1845</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Bought a House with My Boyfriend</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3K2HbVpUrfItMDkL2fuyCl?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Join Father Cooper this week for another SOLO episode. Alex addresses the “Uncuh Jahmz” phenomena and clarifies where her relationship with Julia Fox stands. Big Al has a BIG announcement … she bought a house with her boyfriend! She phones her bff Laren to discuss moving in with a partner and the obstacles that come with it. Alex then shares a recent lingerie fail and how she was able to bounce back at the last minute. She breaks down two very specific sex moves from this moment that obviously include sucking dick. Enjoy!</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3K2HbVpUrfItMDkL2fuyCl</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3013</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s Time to Ask About His Past… (ft. My Boyfriend)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3UjfaPeT9xV66zERezpiKV?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Join Father Cooper this week for a SOLO episode.  A turn of events leads Alex to dig out her “ex-box” - you know the literal box where you keep possessions from your exes. She takes us along for the journey as she reads STD results, love letters, cheating apologies and a few other surprises. The real question…is it okay to keep possessions from an ex-partner? Alex hits us with the hard truth of why we should all be asking our partners about their exes. Let’s phone a friend (or two!) Alex calls Mr. Sexy Zoom Man and Harry Jowsey to hear the male perspective on learning about our exes. Last but not least, Big Al reveals an accidental voicemail she received and how someone she thought was her friend was shit talking her. Enjoy!</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3UjfaPeT9xV66zERezpiKV</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3071</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Guide to Better Sex (Dr. Brotto) </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6F8SjnV3HD50mPKJL1ERbq?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper is joined by clinical psychologist Dr. Lori Brotto. How should we overcome issues like low sexual arousal, lack of orgasm, and painful sex? What even is a “normal” sex drive? Do I have a sexual dysfunction? Dr. Brotto breaks down all of these questions and walks us through a variety of specific strategies anyone can implement in order to achieve better and more pleasurable sex. Join Dr. Brotto at the end of the episode for a guided sexual sensations meditation that you can try in the privacy of your own bedroom (grab those vibrators). Enjoy! </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6F8SjnV3HD50mPKJL1ERbq</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2617</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Ex Sent My Family My Nudes </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0vd8OhTpOAHlOfvAQiIdgP?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Join Father Cooper this week for a SOLO episode. Alex tells us what REALLY happened on her recent trip to NYC. We find out the drama that went down after her interview with Julia Fox. And with the Super Bowl in LA last weekend, Alex takes the opportunity to expose a Bengals player for cheating and her ex for sharing nudes with her family…TUNE IN FOR THE TEA! </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0vd8OhTpOAHlOfvAQiIdgP</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2586</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Julia Fox [VIDEO]</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2AqZ8qqwwYJXklic1PU3Jm?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>(VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper sits down with Julia Fox. This year, Julia has been the center of media attention following her romantic relationship with Kanye West. But don’t get it twisted - Julia has been living a fascinating life way before Mr. West entered the building. Julia gives us the inside look at life as a dominatrix and describes what it is like to work in the  ‘dungeon’ and her favorite characters to role-play. Julia also reveals how her young NYC party lifestyle led to her battle with addiction. Obviously your father doesn’t hold back, we discuss all things Kanye West as well as Julia’s thoughts on being compared to Kim Kardashian. Grab your popcorn and enjoy! This episode includes discussion of substance misuse. Please keep this in mind when deciding if, how and when you’ll listen. For resources on these topics, visit spotify.com/resources.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2AqZ8qqwwYJXklic1PU3Jm</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3577</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emma Chamberlain (Part 2) [VIDEO]</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6Igp6WPiuE3gabHfG5hIaW?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>(VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper sits down with Emma Chamberlain for the second part of their conversation. Emma recalls feeling used by other Youtubers in order to gain views and how she was burned by the people she once looked up to. The pair discuss feeling out of control of their public perception and the need to consequently address and debunk fake rumors. Emma describes the anxiety she experiences as a result of constantly being surveillanced while out in public and the feeling of wanting to disappear. Let’s get into relationships and sex. Emma opens up about her struggles with her sexual identity, her ex-boyfriend, AND her new relationship. We also learn how Emma lost her virginity, what her favorite style of sex is, and what gives her the ick. Enjoy daddies! </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6Igp6WPiuE3gabHfG5hIaW</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4443</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emma Chamberlain (Part 1) [VIDEO]</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5YG5tfhOXMo62IGTPsEY0s?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>(VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper is joined by Emma Chamberlain for her first official in person sit down interview. The pair discuss Emma’s high school days and cover everything from being an only child, her parents divorce, and ultimately her decision to drop out and pursue Youtube full time (OH and they also discuss the classic high school dick pic). Alex and Emma open up and reflect on the fears associated with being a content creator... Who am I outside of the content I post? Is there any room for mistake? Can I do this forever? In response to all of this, Alex then asks Emma, “Have you ever considered just quitting?”. Daddy Gang, enjoy part one of this two part interview with Emma Chamberlain. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5YG5tfhOXMo62IGTPsEY0s</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2886</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancel Call Her Daddy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4NlLM2d2iHDDiLIruxHfgw?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>I’m going to France.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4NlLM2d2iHDDiLIruxHfgw</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1591</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jamie Lynn Spears (Part 2: The Conservatorship) [VIDEO]</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3YGHGo6ZZw9DIkvy6VV0TJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>(VIDEO PODCAST) Alex Cooper sits down with Jamie Lynn Spears for part two of their interview. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3YGHGo6ZZw9DIkvy6VV0TJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2583</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jamie Lynn Spears (Part 1) [VIDEO]</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/15hon6ou2F8hQ3x98qNGgu?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>(VIDEO PODCAST) Alex Cooper sits down with Jamie Lynn Spears for a two part interview.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15hon6ou2F8hQ3x98qNGgu</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3902</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Plastic Surgery Story </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3gkO2eu3rp4UmQuYlAm2lW?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Father Cooper is back with a vacation recap. She details a fight with her sister, a non photoshop fail, the moment  Mario Lopez appeared mid fuck, and how a teammate spreading gossip landed our father face to face with a plastic surgeon. And, because she is the greatest podcast host of all time, Alex reveals the controversial first guest of the new year. Enjoy daddies. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3gkO2eu3rp4UmQuYlAm2lW</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1543</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother Cooper (Revisit)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1TpKnjzlnzz6fMaVH0ZW5f?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>100.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1TpKnjzlnzz6fMaVH0ZW5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3001</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSA - He (Still) Doesn’t Like You</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2FniuMeyjqDPC0ragZzJ6o?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Your Father, Alexandra, gets deep this week and walks women through the wake-up call they all need. Stop clinging on to every little thing a men says to you and LOOK AT THE BIG PICTURE FACTS. If you viewed your dating life from a third party view.. what would you think of yourself? An episode EVERY woman needs to hear. Also, giving a huge tip for women that are having a hard time achieving an orgasm/ have never had one (wink wink ASMR porn). And, if you have a bad gag reflex, Alex is coming to the rescue with tricks of how to mask it. ENJOY #DADDYGANG Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2FniuMeyjqDPC0ragZzJ6o</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3372</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Official Breakup Guide</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3DUoCQ1uIgQ0barJacltkk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>It has arrived – the official Call Her Daddy breakup guide. Haven’t recently gone through a breakup? Well, a little birdie told us you are about to be broken up with, no one is safe, so listen up daddies. Father Cooper walks you through every step of what to do in the moment when you are broken up with (and no…it actually does not involve fucking his dad OR his brother!) Breakups are hard, and sometimes what’s even harder is getting closure. But have no fear, Big Al gives you 5 specific questions to ask to help you get the answers that will ultimately help you to move on while also keeping your dignity intact. Let’s pump up the party a little with a pep talk from your daddy. We are viewing a breakup as…FREEDOM! Father Cooper may directly call us out in this episode, but trust me Daddies, you need to hear it.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3DUoCQ1uIgQ0barJacltkk</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2733</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infiltrating a Girl Group</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5tRr3a8lknP7fBRclunHLn?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Hello you dirty daddies - let’s cuddle up together and ease our Sunday scaries. How might you ask? Two words…cruise control baby.  Alex is providing the roadmap to getting through yet another week of work hell. Big Al opens up and shares a vulnerable side of herself, telling a story from her past that embodies rejection and desperation…haven’t we all been there. This week is filled with story-time and advice…breaking the ice with new friend groups, navigating a night out without drinking and drugs, and crushing a night out at the bar when you are single. Enjoy!  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5tRr3a8lknP7fBRclunHLn</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1867</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuck Me with a Dildo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3B2WRMrS0VN2A2IDW9QHNa?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper is coming to you live from a secret snowy location…and she’s not alone! Big Al is currently sharing a home with her ENTIRE family and Mr. Sexy Zoom Man (the sexual frustration is real). Alex details her plans to creatively and secretly get it in without her father finding out her true identity – the throat goat. Alex’s problems are so big this week she phones an expert – sex therapist Dr. Castellanos. What’s our new favorite thing on Call Her Daddy...some role play! Alex and Dr. Castellanos play out a variety of scenarios you have probably encountered at some point in your life. What if your partner doesn’t turn you on? What if you like masturbating more than sex? What if you’re flat out just too stressed at work to even think about sex? Dr. Castellanos gives us these answers and more. For all my horny daddies, let’s ramp this conversation up a bit. Let’s discuss dirty porn, giant dildos, and erotic fantasies! I guarantee when this episode ends you will be reaching for some lube and your clit – enjoy ;)  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3B2WRMrS0VN2A2IDW9QHNa</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3082</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colton Underwood (A CHD Exclusive)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2OlQLrqQ5yZblEbOlXuaFk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper sits down with Colton Underwood. Colton repressed his sexuality for the first 28 years of his life; a former NFL player and Bachelor star, Colton went to extremes to promote and perpetuate a heterosexual identity. Colton sits down with Alex to reflect on his manipulation tactics and the people he hurt along the way. Daddy Gang, tune in this week to hear Colton speak on the events that brought him to rock bottom, led him to make some of the biggest mistakes of his life, and ultimately reveal his true sexuality. (This episode includes discussion of suicide. Please keep this in mind when deciding if, how and when you’ll listen. For resources on these topics, visit spotify.com/resources.) Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2OlQLrqQ5yZblEbOlXuaFk</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4262</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Esther Perel (Cheating 101)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/35liExm4PPX1yCs9l0ZWFr?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper sits down with Esther Perel. Esther is a psychotherapist who is recognized as one of the leading voices in modern relationships. Her most recent book, The State of Affairs: Rethinking Infidelity, explores why people cheat and provides guidance on what to do in the wake of discovering this ultimate form of betrayal. Alex presents Esther with a situation…you open your boyfriends iPad to find messages that reveal he is cheating on you. Esther walks us through step by step on how to respond in the moment and how to move forward. Do you admit to reading his messages? At what point do you stop reading? Is make-up sex the ultimate mistake? Who do you tell? How do you know if you should break-up? Tune in this week Daddy Gang to hear from the expert herself – Esther Perel. To hear more from Esther, listen to her podcast Where Should We Begin? Also, check out Where Should We Begin – a game of stories, created by Esther Perel and designed to unlock the storyteller within. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35liExm4PPX1yCs9l0ZWFr</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3005</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuffing Season is Here</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/18BH0xgnRgquH5qUfvUNqb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Your favorite neighborhood losers are back and delivering one spicy mini episode. Laren tells Big Al the story of her recent journey from small town Louisiana to Los Angeles, where she encountered both Santa Claus and Dwayne the Rock Johnson after narrowly escaping a kidnapping. The girls discuss coming across one lusty locksmith…but is it ever a good idea to become romantically involved with a man that can easily break into your apartment? Cuffing season has officially arrived. Alex breaks down how to find a cuff, maintain a cuff, and eventually break off a cuff. Ah – the circle of cuff. Stick around for the showdown…Laren admits to Alex she is in love with Thor (Alex’s ex-boyfriend). Will Alex give Laren her blessing to go to pound town with the mighty hammer? Listen and find out.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18BH0xgnRgquH5qUfvUNqb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1984</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Social Media Ruined My Life</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4MRU17L5oHurYt2fhnglo7?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper sits down with her longtime best friend Laren, who recently deleted all of her social media accounts. The two reminisce on the evolution of social media throughout their lives, including Myspace top friends, Snapchat nudes, Facebook party albums, and the ultimate beast…Instagram. Laren tells all regarding her decision to completely delete her social media and reflects on how her life has changed since going off the grid. Alex and Lauren discuss online bullying, body image, relationships…and how social media influences basically every aspect of our lives. Even if your social media is private and you have less than one hundred followers, this episode is sure to raise some questions that everyone can relate to. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4MRU17L5oHurYt2fhnglo7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4132</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talking shit (ft. Pete Davidson)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3FJPISg4It9b8D2ka7NC8z?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Description: Secrets revealed. Love, Alex.   Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3FJPISg4It9b8D2ka7NC8z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1511</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Brought my Boyfriend Home- a fail.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2UpNfiBgvb1oKjYuBERpJy?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Let’s take a walk down memory lane…vodka in water bottles, clip in hair extensions and hook ups in your childhood home. Smells like the biggest drinking night of the year – aka blackout Wednesday. STORYTIME! Big Al has experienced a Blackout Wednesday (or two) … let's expose a few more of Father Cooper’s hometown horror stories. How do you think it went the first time she brought Mr. Sexy Zoom Man home to meet her family? (Spoiler alert: a complete disaster). Daddy Gang, you know the drill...we need to sprinkle in a bit of health and wellness. Alex ends the episode by having a conversation with clinical psychologist Dr. Suzanne Wallach and the two discuss a variety of tactics anyone (even if you aren’t in therapy) can implement when it comes to difficult family situations during the holidays. Dr. Wallach addresses topics ranging from boundary setting to disordered eating and grief. Enjoy! This episode includes discussion of eating disorders. Please keep this in mind when deciding if, how and when you’ll listen. For resources on these topics, visit spotify.com/resources. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2UpNfiBgvb1oKjYuBERpJy</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3465</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amanda Knox - “I didn’t fucking do it.”</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3rSF2tacw9E78meQkZFNr8?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper sits down with Amanda Knox. The interview begins with Amanda giving a clear reminder to the world – “I didn’t fucking do it”. In 2007, while studying abroad in Italy, Amanda was wrongly accused and convicted of murdering her roommate Meredith Kercher. Meredith was the victim of a brutal murder. Amanda was the victim of trial by media. Her sexuality was used against her in order to manipulate a story that she was a sex crazed murderer - and that was the story that overtook international headlines. Fourteen years later, Amanda is exhausted, and is still working to detach her name from a murder she did not commit. Tune in this week as Amanda details the events that occurred on November 2nd 2007, the interrogation process and the four years she spent in Italian prison. This captivating interview highlights Amanda’s struggle to reclaim both her name and her life.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3rSF2tacw9E78meQkZFNr8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5385</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affording Therapy 101</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0Gbm7iZNKFG8na7lI2fsyy?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Give me an “M”...give me an “I”…you know where this is going. Father Cooper is back for another mini episode and with some advice you are sure to be ~thankful~ for ;) If you’ve ever listened to an episode of Call Her Daddy you know the drill – get into therapy ASAP. But, easier said than done, right? Well, grab your pen and notebook because Alex has done her research and is here to give you some answers on how to access affordable therapy. Let’s also discuss - can I date my brother’s best friend; do I prioritize family or the fuck? Has a significant other ever gifted you an iPhone? Well you lucky bastard, take it and run, because Big Al addresses when it is appropriate to buy someone an iPhone (spoiler alert…never – you’re being used). Last but not least, Father Cooper breaks down how to ask someone to get STD tested and when it is appropriate to hold blowjobs for ransom. If you’re horny and you know it clap your hands and go fucking listen – enjoy Daddies!   Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0Gbm7iZNKFG8na7lI2fsyy</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1728</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emily Ratajkowski</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1aCABdjaqT99gHieqRSJer?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper sits down with Emily Ratajkowski. While you may think you have an understanding of Emily’s seemingly perfect life, this interview reveals that you never know what someone is actually going through. Emily opens up about the traumatic experiences she has overcome throughout her life and how these events have reduced her to feeling like nothing more than a mannequin. Many are quick to dismiss Emily’s struggles because she has an envious body and posts provocative photos – but does one’s appearance diminish the pain and trauma they have experienced? Does one’s appearance and capitalization of their own body take away their ability to identify as a feminist? Tune in this week daddy gang – happy Wednesday. TRIGGER WARNING: This episode discusses adult subject matter, including descriptions of sexual violence, and is intended for adult consumption only. Listener discretion is advised. If you have been affected by sexual violence, free, confidential support is available 24/7 through RAINN's National Sexual Assault Hotline at 800.656-4673 and online.rainn.org. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1aCABdjaqT99gHieqRSJer</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3523</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Friendship VS. Reality Tv (ft. Hannah Berner &amp; Paige Desorbo)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7vvi6JQVJowJarU5J0gBRy?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper sits down with Hannah Berner and Paige Desorbo for the show’s first threesome. The episode takes a turn when Hannah and Paige reveal they haven’t spoken about the biggest challenge their friendship has ever faced - reality televisions attempt to prey on their relationship and tear them apart. There are tears, extremely uncomfortable moments and no one holds back. You will hear their friendship put to the test while sitting on the couch of your friendly local therapist…Dr. Alex Cooper reporting for duty. Your father is here to listen… and expose the tea. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7vvi6JQVJowJarU5J0gBRy</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5644</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ex Encounter</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7eVCa4IBisZEzPyDzTBT74?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Halloween Sunday scaries got you down? Well this mini is sure to bring you up. Father Cooper begins by discussing the difficulty of managing your time between your friends and your significant other. Is it wrong to want to spend all of your time with your boyfriend? Are your friends just jealous? All of my struggling Catholics out there - please stand up. Big Al explains how she overcame the strict ideals of sex imposed by the Catholic church and how she currently fucks and sucks guilt free.  So, you’re a virgin? Well if your name isn’t Mary we are dropping the V word all together. Father Cooper discusses what to say to someone if you are having sex for the first time. Are you obligated to tell them? Should you take the secret to your grave? As great as Big Al is at having sex, some may say she is even more skilled at avoiding it. Alex gives a play by play on how to stop a hookup from going all the way while still keeping the mood flirty and fun. SOS – I’m going to see my ex, what do I do?! In this episode, Father Cooper fully breaks down the ex-encounter…what to do, what to say, and one specific move we all want to add to our arsenal. Last, but certainly not least, a tale as old as time…sexting. Big Al discusses how to handle that sext that went a little too far and got a little too freaky. Happy Halloween and enjoy daddies!  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7eVCa4IBisZEzPyDzTBT74</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1983</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I got ghosted, now what?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4wbGfhujm7JPjhldFzUkaS?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Halloween is upon us and what’s spookier than ghosting? ;) This week, Alex covers all things ghosting, including, a story you have never heard before - The tale of Slim Shady’s teammate ghosting Big Al. Then, Father Cooper shares her controversial take on ghosting - and why it’s incredible- while also sharing advice for those doing the ghosting and to those being ghosted.  Are you the asshole still debating your Halloween costume? We all know there are two types of girls on Halloween, Sexy and Funny. WRONG AGAIN. This year Father Cooper calls out a Tik Tok claim and sets a much needed new rule …   Finally, your Father gives all the details of how to turn Halloween night into a successful roleplay situation. Costumes that easily transition from your Halloween party into the bedroom? Grab your pen and paper, you’re going to want to write down all the details of how to pull off the perfect Halloween roleplay fantasy. Enjoy Daddies! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4wbGfhujm7JPjhldFzUkaS</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3112</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emma Kenney (ft. Shameless)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/462tfkbnWbUEm9Y4BUHFyj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper sits down with Emma Kenney. Emma spent more than half of her life starring as Debbie Gallagher on the TV show “Shameless” and in this episode Emma spills all of the tea about growing up on set. Emma even dishes which co-star she had a crush on. She gets personal and opens up about her decision to go to rehab at a young age and shares new insight on that experience. As a child actor on the set of an adult show, young Emma was exposed to many explicit topics (Weed! Cocaine! Dildos! Nymphos!) and even had her first kiss with the cameras rolling…and her dad in a front row seat. This episode sheds light (and many funny stories) on what it is like to grow up on the set of one of the most popular TV shows. Enjoy Daddies!   Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">462tfkbnWbUEm9Y4BUHFyj</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2917</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop Cyberbullying and Start Masturbating</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2yK4NXqLksUmtA9CqZ7XTg?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Ask and you shall receive…this mini episode is the second part of Father Cooper’s conversation with Eileen Kelly. So if you have not yet listened to the full Eileen Kelly episode – go get her done and then come on back. Big Al and Eileen continue the conversation around masturbation and hope to soon see all you daddies out there flicking the bean. We heard Eileen’s revenge porn story, but it doesn’t stop there, Eileen was also the victim of online stalking and harassment. Eileen shares everything… including what happened when the stalker was eventually caught and the conversation that went down. You may not have experience with the world of Hollywood agents, but everyone has had at least one shitty boss in their lifetime. Unfortunately for Eileen, she was dumped by her agent (no they weren’t dating) and as you would expect, Eileen spills all of the tea. Enjoy daddy-hoes. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2yK4NXqLksUmtA9CqZ7XTg</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1840</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eileen Kelly (threesomes, revenge porn, &amp; blowjobs)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/10tbDpRczCNdi9WX4Hu9qz?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper sits down with podcaster Eileen Kelly. After the sudden loss of her mother at a young age, Eileen formed an online community through Tumblr and blogging where she discussed sex, relationships and growing up. Alex and Eileen reminisce on their catholic school days and the sex-ed they wish they were taught. Well, what would they teach…porn and pleasure? While we are educating the masses, let’s discuss all things masturbation. Why are we embarrassed? What’s the ideal setup? Eileen also shares her experiences and stories with threesomes and suggests guidelines for those who are potentially considering. Have you ever had to file a restraining order against someone trying to blackmail you with revenge porn? Well, Eileen has and she spills the full story in this episode. The pair end the episode with a conversation around mental health and Eileen openly details her decision to check herself into McLean Hospital, a psychiatric hospital in Massachusetts where she spent five months. Enjoy daddies! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10tbDpRczCNdi9WX4Hu9qz</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3318</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cazzie David (ft. pick me girls &amp; love bombing)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0PCPZfcvhZyQE2TAFKGUQC?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper sits down with Cazzie David (despite Cazzie’s last minute efforts to ditch). The two then get serious and discuss family relationships and social media. Cazzie details what the pilot episode of her family’s reality TV show would be and Alex reminds the world that she does in fact have a sister. Building upon last week’s episode, the duo discusses the negative impact of social media along with the popular Tik Tok trend, the notion of a “pick me girl”. While on pop culture they also discuss the D’Amelio show, the Scott Disick dm, and last but certainly not least…Larry David at fashion week. This is Call Her Daddy, so let’s talk dating and relationships. Alex and Cazzie dive deep into the concept of love bombing and Cazzie offers up examples from her own personal experience. The girls give advice on how to recognize the warning signs and overcome an abusive relationship. This episode surely contains a little bit of everything – enjoy daddies! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0PCPZfcvhZyQE2TAFKGUQC</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4096</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is your sign, text him.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4eUBgAbkBfViNrDvVTkbkm?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Mini mini mini minaaaaaaaaaay. Daddy Gang, we have much to discuss this week. What are the rules when it comes to nude etiquette? Do you have to delete your old nudes when a new partner comes along or are you able to build yourself a portfolio that lasts forever? Ah the classic stalemate situation, and no I’m not fucking talking about chess. I’m talking about the moment when you are so invested in the game of “who can give less fucks” but someone has to make a move. Well, this is your sign…text him. While we are here, why not also talk about the rules of threesomes, when to write in your diary (yes you read that correctly) and how to make the most of that post sex moment. Enjoy Daddies!  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4eUBgAbkBfViNrDvVTkbkm</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1639</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Got Caught Photoshopping</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5cc87uywpcXcoeCwpvF0GE?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper addresses a recent Tik Tok that went viral after exposing her for photoshopping. Opening up a larger conversation Alex discusses the role insecurities and bullying from her childhood play in her current relationship to social media. Why is there such a pressure to edit photos? Does it really matter if everyone does it? Is she only saying this because she was caught? Will she continue to edit photos? Following this discussion, Father Cooper speaks with Dr. Jean Twenge who holds a PHD in psychology and is a personality and social psychologist. Dr. Twenge has authored multiple books, has over 140 scientific publications and her research focuses on generational differences and more recently the influence of social media. The pair continue the conversation surrounding the negative impacts of social media on one’s mental health.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cc87uywpcXcoeCwpvF0GE</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3056</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nico Tortorella</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5O9kuvK2o0a2YMgokNv5ku?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper sits down with Nico Tortorella. Nico is both an accomplished actor and author. In June of 2016, Nico came out as sexually fluid, and in their book, Space Between, they wrote, “I am comfortable today calling myself a queer, nonbinary, bisuexual, happily married, polyamorous/non-monogamous human being.” In this interview the pair dives deep into Nico’s life and discusses topics ranging from sex and sexuality to overcoming alcoholism. Father Cooper and Nico also discuss polyamory and how Nico’s polyamorous relationship with their partner Bethany has evolved over time. Why is the hotel where the interview is occurring triggering to Nico...they’ve had sex all over it?! Daddies - enjoy an episode that is both vulnerable and simultaneously hilarious. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5O9kuvK2o0a2YMgokNv5ku</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3983</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOS I've been Friend Zoned</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/605dU73C3pjCwTvvU24kfJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Did someone say…mini episode? This week, wisdom is spewing out of Father Cooper’s asshole like lava. Should you believe a guy when he says you need to be “friends” so he can “work on himself”? Big Al also advises on topics ranging from the classic small penis problem to how to properly go to titty-town. In the spirit of health and wellness (and growth) let's revisit an old topic – do men love “the crazy”? Lastly, just to make sure we stay on brand, let’s discuss therapy and drugs. Honestly, does this episode even count as a mini? Enjoy daddies! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">605dU73C3pjCwTvvU24kfJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2459</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexis Ren</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4xYwUTxts8tl8CG1qA4qge?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper sits down with Alexis Ren for a raw and vulnerable conversation where Alexis shares stories she has never before discussed. The duo discusses Alexis’ upbringing being homeschooled and overcoming the loss of a parent and toxic relationship. For the first time, Alexis details what actually went down in her infamously known Instagram relationship. The interview concludes with the pair discussing an instance of sexual harassment Alexis faced in the workplace early on in her career. Join Father Cooper post interview for a continuation of the conversation. * Trigger warning * - This episode includes discussion of eating disorders and sexual assault. Please keep this in mind when deciding if, how and when you’ll listen. For resources on these topics, visit spotify.com/resources. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4xYwUTxts8tl8CG1qA4qge</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3525</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Therapy and Drugs for All</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0qOvse6DMhC54D0WdCHICS?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper sits down with Laren (that bitch still hasn’t left) in an attempt for redemption. The girls have put down the bottle and picked up … a book? After reading (a chapter) of Esther Perel’s Mating in Captivity, the pair get serious and analyze their own lives while contemplating the question, can passion and stability coexist in a relationship? The duo discusses a spectrum of dating topics ranging from being single to taking accountability within a relationship. It’s hard to tell where book club ends and girl talk (free therapy?) begins but this week every topic is tackled… dating, friendship and life. Spoiler alert…Richard is back and the girls have one final bender in LA before Big Al sends Laren home (for the sake of both her reputation and liver). Enjoy Daddies! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0qOvse6DMhC54D0WdCHICS</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3034</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happens in Vegas - Goes on Call Her Daddy. (Ft. Mr. Sexy Zoom Man, Marshmello, Kygo, Logan Paul, Richard, Laren &amp; Country Club Man)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2sromhqcLGbzve34jRlpC5?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>I am still too hungover to write one of these. The title says it all. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2sromhqcLGbzve34jRlpC5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2962</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Roast of my Past</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/35Ekjs0pSwOZ0fgPIDINiz?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week the tables are turned and Father Cooper is the one being interviewed. In honor of her 27th birthday, Big Al is grilled with 27 questions that will reveal untold stories from her past. Have you ever wondered how many people she’s had sex with? Her first heartbreak? Has she ever successfully pulled off a catfish? Oh, and of course, the question everyone has been wondering…are her tits real? Daddy Gang, tune in this week to hear something a little different and to feel a little closer to your Father.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35Ekjs0pSwOZ0fgPIDINiz</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2656</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealing the Biggest Cock I’ve Ever Taken</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3fFXmzAC6KbbINnXzgc7rg?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Welcome back for another mini episode! This week, Father Cooper breaks it down as to why her clit climax got cancelled in Hawaii. So, insert plan B (no not the pill) but french onion soup, dick and *****. Do you ever wonder the man behind the biggest cock Big Al has ever taken? Well, you are not alone, Mr. Sexy Zoom Man also had the same question – and Father Cooper gives us (and him) the answer. It’s Leo season baby – and your local narcissist Alex Cooper intends to roar her way through Las Vegas in celebration of her big 2-7. If you’re a greedy bitch raise your hand and cheer because yes…to France we go. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3fFXmzAC6KbbINnXzgc7rg</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1968</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heidi Montag</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/42ZrP6vWE19UtRD6OcWhNT?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper sits down with Heidi Montag, and lots of champagne. The pair get things popping off immediately…poppin bottles that is. Heidi takes us to Italy (sorry not France) where she spent her final year of high school. If you are here for The Hills drama, Heidi does not hold back and dishes all of the tea regarding her plastic surgeries and her former co-star Lauren Conrad (i.e. Lauren didn’t live up to her potential). How many orgasms a night are you having? This episode we learn Speidi are having 4-5 a night! Pour yourself a glass and chug along with Big Al and Heidi because this episode is surely a ride. Enjoy Daddies! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42ZrP6vWE19UtRD6OcWhNT</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2989</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnnaLynne McCord</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3dL8J406ZTE313kc0s2EyM?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper sits down with AnnaLynne McCord as she recounts the life events that led up to her diagnosis of dissociative identity disorder. * Trigger Warning * - this entire episode may be triggering for those who have suffered from sexual abuse or would be triggered from the discussion of self harm. If this episode was at all distressing to you, please reach out to the 24/7 national crisis hotline at 1-800-273-8255. To reach a 24/7 crisis counseling texting hotline send “HOME” to 741741 (valid for the US and Canada). Crisis hotlines for additional countries will be posted via the Call Her Daddy Instagram. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3dL8J406ZTE313kc0s2EyM</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3000</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I am the Star of Your Sex Dream</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2NpcQPa8YHXSfWHQxTJoeH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Welcome to the first mini episode mother fuckers…save the date! These bad boys will be dropping every other Thursday. This episode, Father Cooper recalls an instance where a stiff sleepy dick was inserted into her throat…aka she starred in a sex dream. You are all aware of Big Al’s podcasting career, but did you know she is also a landlord? And currently having trouble with her tenants? When will you greedy whores ever be satisfied…god damn, yes you are going to fucking France (with a little Hawaiian twist). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2NpcQPa8YHXSfWHQxTJoeH</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1852</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiffany Haddish</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4hxHQz3dYfI9Dgc79gqkvD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week Father Cooper sits down with Tiffany Haddish. Need the perfect recipe for revenge? Take a note from Tiffany’s book and gulf down some corn and take advantage of that shit…literally. Corn shit isn’t your thing? Why not try a strategically placed billboard with your own face on it to really get back at an ex. Tiffany surely doesn’t hold back in this episode and shares her opinion on internet trolls, big dicks, dad bods, cuckolding and so much more. Are you ready Daddy Gang? Well, you better buckle up because Tiffany Haddish is here and SHE READY.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4hxHQz3dYfI9Dgc79gqkvD</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2829</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chelsea Handler</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2UWtNP1zsgXfbFEH3qJF5T?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week (and the start of the exclusive season with Spotify) Father Cooper sits down with Chelsea Handler. Alex recounts a vivid memory from the first time she met Chelsea, an instance Chelsea has absolutely no recollection of. The duo discusses topics ranging from cancel culture, the evolution of comedy… and drugs. Daddy Gang, get ready for an epic launch to a new era. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2UWtNP1zsgXfbFEH3qJF5T</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2757</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“Block him” - My therapist</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/16fKjBCR97GlwHXUbK0gaE?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, we begin the episode STILL in the fucking Hamptons. You thought things couldn’t get any wilder from last week? Oh, you thought wrong…get ready to meet the neighbors. Once Father Cooper finally makes it to Chicago she changes the pace up a bit and sits down with Lauren to discuss some therapist approved dating advice. Big Al and Lar chat about blocking, second dates, deciding what your type is and so much more. But of course, Chicago couldn’t come to a close without one wild night out. Father Cooper finally has her debut on stage and delivers an impromptu performance. Last, but surely not least, Big Al meets up with the daddy gang in Chicago for a LIVE questions of the week. Buckle up, because this episode is filled with surprises. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16fKjBCR97GlwHXUbK0gaE</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3842</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happens in The Hamptons Does NOT Stay in The Hamptons</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/36aerBZd8Uoo7gZZtfQXbL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Hello, you have come to the right place to clear up any controversy regarding Father Cooper’s recent Fourth of July trip to the Hamptons. Kicked out of a bar? YUP…and don’t worry she is giving you the full story. Not only is she detailing the physical removal from a bar, but she is also reporting so many more stories that you sneaky little bastards missed with your iPhones. This episode is sure to be unlike any other and contains recordings from bar bathrooms, the Montauk highway, and hungover in bed. No one is safe and nothing is left out. So buckle up (grab a drink) and get ready daddy gang because you’re going to the Hamptons with your dad. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36aerBZd8Uoo7gZZtfQXbL</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2755</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blacking Out in a City Near You (ft. me)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2NuKoTJu8XhrVda15slOGO?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper begins by recalling a traumatizing memory from childhood that somehow managed to seep its way into her current relationship. Old habits never truly die and we all pause to witness a moment of regression in our dear daddy. Speaking of relationships, do we dare drop the L word…lube, labia, libido? Clench your assholes as Father Cooper finally and formally introduces Henry to the world (and I say ‘clench’ because I know a certain b-word really fires some of you up). Be sure to stick around for the announcement of Father Cooper’s world tour…yes she is finally taking up her pop star career. Big Al is taking no back seat to hot girl summer and is taking you along with her on her upcoming adventures. Yes, Betty…this tour once again includes a trip to France…god you greedy whores. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2NuKoTJu8XhrVda15slOGO</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3901</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infiltrating His Friend Group</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7kHgZysSxP3BJR0RXcMOFk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper takes you on her (mental) journey as she tries to figure out how she will get herself to the one and only…Kentucky. After narrowly escaping death, she takes a moment to reflect upon this upcoming season and how she can ensure the daddy gang continues to ~vibe~ in Dunkin Donuts. In a teaching moment, she recounts an old NYC tale involving everyone’s favorite rapper (or baseball player?) …Slim Shady sit down. After listening to this episode, friend groups across the county are sure to be infiltrated. Don’t worry you greedy whores, you are going to France this week, and it is quite a ride. ENJOY DADDIES. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7kHgZysSxP3BJR0RXcMOFk</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3437</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Glucked My Way to the Top.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/06rTyfG2K7PIt1Mh20Lt4f?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Welcome back daddies. This week, as we kick off a new season of Call Her Daddy, Father Cooper wastes no time spilling every ounce of tea - starting with a “business meeting” in Harvey Weintstein’s office, to signing with Barstool Sports and the details of the show’s new home at Spotify. Daddy Gang, get ready for an episode full of big announcements, big stories, and big green dick energy. ENJOY. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06rTyfG2K7PIt1Mh20Lt4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3398</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>121- The Season Finale</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5DQvZE06vi98WelD29vHOF?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Is a season finale ever dull... ;) Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5DQvZE06vi98WelD29vHOF</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3278</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>120- COUPLES THERAPY (ft. Dr. Orna Guralnik)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4Wh3AY5LBHHouGKDA7FsEN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper is joined by clinical psychologist, psychoanalyst and star of the hit docu-series Couples’ Therapy… Dr. Orna Guralnik. This episode is sure to be both interesting and insightful whether you have never attended therapy in your life or you are years deep. The duo breaks it down beginning with the basics (aka do I bring a PowerPoint presentation to my first therapy session) and even moves on to address topics such as attachment style, dissociation, and transgenerational trauma. Not currently in a relationship? Doesn’t matter. Have pen and paper ready because every word out of Dr. Guralnik’s mouth is a piece of wisdom you will want to hold onto. Bonus content…does she analyze Father Cooper in the process? ;) ENJOY DADDIES!!!!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4Wh3AY5LBHHouGKDA7FsEN</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4644</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>119- WE DON'T NEED MEN (ft. Josie Canseco)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/68TLDbVEx2uPobGfKDipPR?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper is joined by new LA friend, Josie Canseco. The women discuss Josie’s dad sliding into Alex’s Dms and a formal apology from Alex. Also, Josie explains growing up as the daughter of a famous professional athlete, her childhood in the spotlight, the bullying that ensued, and her journey towards establishing her individual identity. Josie addresses the topic of body dysmorphia, struggles with self love, coping mechanisms, and her journey towards happiness. The concept that, “you only fall in love three times," is explored, as Josie details her first love/ soulmate as well as her last relationship and why it ended. ENJOY!!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68TLDbVEx2uPobGfKDipPR</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3235</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>118- "I AM THAT B*TCH" (ft. Rickey Thompson)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7qxLnLxxhJV8wMIsirtL9b?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper is joined by actor, comedian, fashion icon, social media personality, and co-host of the "We Said What We Said" podcast - Rickey Thompson. The two sit down to discuss the impact of careers in social media and the pressure to remain relevant... all while protecting one's private life. Rickey discusses his experience growing up in North Carolina; a story that began with bullying and isolation, and ended with him as prom king. The duo discuss moving to LA and Rickey's dating life... spoiler alert-he is recently in a committed relationship! They continue on sharing best and worst sex experiences, Grinder vs. Tinder, playing games in and out of a relationship, and so much more. TUNE IN THIS WEEK. ENJOY. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7qxLnLxxhJV8wMIsirtL9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3727</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>117- Backstabbing D*ck (ft. Madison Lewis)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/56su3m228mAyUocik6aVda?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>DADDY GANG. This week we are diving into the truth behind a very public and messy TikTok real-life drama. Four best friends - two men, two women, now entwined in the ultimate cheating scandal. Madison Lewis’s boyfriend went behind her back and started a relationship with her best girlfriend. The raw emotion and heartache that unfolds in this episode is relatable whether you have 100 followers on social media, or 11 million. Betrayal, backstabbing, public embarrassment, and eventually following your gut to a very hurtful truth... TUNE IN FOR THE LIVE DRAMA AND STORY. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56su3m228mAyUocik6aVda</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2839</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>116- Dirty Deets from The #1 Playboy Bunny (ft. Holly Madison)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5ODUyFFi44TBWcxET0qQXM?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper is joined by an ICONIC guest, former playmate, Holly Madison. During her 20s, Holly entered the Playboy mansion and became one of the many girlfriends of Hugh Hefner, the infamous founder of Playboy magazine. Holly walks the daddy gang through her childhood and relationship with her family, as well as the struggles she experienced internally and socially that eventually led her to not only become a Playboy bunny, but to join the inner circle of women exclusively intimate with Heff, who at the time was 74. Holly’s truth about life in the mansion is radically different than how it was portrayed on the successful reality show, ‘The Girls Next Door.’ Strict curfews, clothing allowances, plastic surgery funds, love bombing, cult behavior, verbal and emotional abuse, were all creatively promoted as the never-ending party for the elite due to the manipulative disguise of one man’s money and power. Holly Madison, who went on to build an amazing career (headlining the Peep Show in Vegas, securing a spot on Dancing with the Stars, and becoming a New York Times #1 best selling author), shares her journey of battling through depression and repression in a misogynistic era, and although navigating through the most difficult time in her life, shows the strength of not only someone who survived, but thrived and did not allow a powerful and wealthy man to tear her down. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ODUyFFi44TBWcxET0qQXM</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5415</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>115- K-Holes &amp; Chlamydia (ft. Harry Jowsey)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5VskOclQV3JZGTeKRjRHia?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper is enjoying spring break with the one and only... Harry Jowsey. AND THINGS ARE GETTING INSANE. Harry immediately confront Alex about a man that is talking about her head game in LA.. drama. Then, the 2 discuss their experience getting chlamydia, uncovering if guys look at your butthole during doggy-style, bleaching your asshole, and drugs &amp; k-holes. Lastly, Alex tell 2 college stories she has never told on the podcast before, one including a Patriot's player she woke up in bed with in Foxborough and doing drugs with her ex-boyfriend gone wrong. ENJOY DADDY GANG!!!!!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5VskOclQV3JZGTeKRjRHia</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4863</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>114- This is Mia Khalifa. (ft. Mia Khalifa)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7D04gvJCUyGV6fUxtAUxDp?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Father Cooper sits down for an interview with the one and only Mia Khalifa…move over Oprah. Mia opens up about the struggles she faced while growing up as an immigrant in a post 9/11 society and the bullying and harassment that followed. She recounts the darkest time in her life and how she overcame global shaming, death threats, and ISIS. Mia tells her story with an inspiring amount of strength and affirms how one’s past does not define their future. It wouldn’t be an episode of Call Her Daddy without a little sex, and Mia shares one of the most intimate sexual experiences she has had with a partner. Lastly as always, therapy is the key to life. ENJOY DADDIES! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7D04gvJCUyGV6fUxtAUxDp</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3958</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>113- How to Trick Him into Proposing (ft. Hannah Berner)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2kFOWsVvIsgHy5wSYtoHNH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week’s episode, Father Cooper is joined by OG guest and fan favorite, Hannah Berner. AND IT’S A BIG ONE BABY. Hannah sits in the hot seat and details for the Daddy Gang how she managed to get a man on TWO knees and propose to her. The dirty details of how unglamorous engagements are, picking out your own ring, putting a ring on chubby fingers, and the awful bachelor show effect on love will all be discussed on this week’s ep. AND IT DOESN’T STOP THERE. It gets even juicier when the girl’s get deep and talk how social media has effected their mental health and the issues they have come to face through hate and the podcast industry. ENJOY DADDIES!!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2kFOWsVvIsgHy5wSYtoHNH</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4070</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>112- The Debaucherous Tails Aboard The Litty Titty Torture Train (Ft. Egg Farts)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/62gW0oI52hAtPuNO4I1Koz?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, join Father Cooper aboard the litty titty torture train as she details the train wreck that has been her and Lauren’s life since moving to LA. They explore not only the impact covid has had on their alcohol intake, but also how it has affected their masturbation style...cue bathtub masturbation. The girls really bring relatability this week when they discuss a classic topic, egg farts. If you smelt it, you dealt it! If egg farts aren’t your thing, this episode should at least make you feel less shitty about your own drunken nights. Lost keys, fingers in buttholes, blue lips, and a country club...this episode has a little of everything. Enjoy Daddies!!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62gW0oI52hAtPuNO4I1Koz</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3560</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>111- The Map to Dating Apps &amp; Rich Dudes (ft. my holemate, Paige DeSorbo)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/68iEayhSAuRnje0BxNUO0B?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Father Cooper is joined by NYC reality tv star, fashion blogger, beautiful human and holemate- Paige Desorbo. The two describe their sides of the story to knowing each other through an ex boyfriend... as one of the girl's matched with the other's boyfriend on a dating app.. DRAMA!!! They also discover they were dating the same famous actor in NYC at the same exact time, going on the same exact dates LOL. Paige then details her newly single life, dating younger vs. older men, model apartment life in NYC, dating the bad boy phase, going to an all girl school, being in love only once, dealing with bitchy girls, and SO MUCH MORE. This one feels like you are sitting around, talking shit with your girlfriends. ENJOY DADS!!!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68iEayhSAuRnje0BxNUO0B</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5923</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>110- Will The Real Slim Shady Please Stand Up</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4cuSmnBIIRxrgt6TAsqfKd?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>A week into being in a relationship and shit has already hit the fan for Father Cooper. Although on a journey to health and wellness, when times get tough sometimes a little toxicity just slips out like an unexpected shart. This week, Father Cooper takes a back seat to the daddy gang and shifts the spotlight. Get ready for questions of the week like you’ve never heard before... CUE HER RAP DEBUT. Father Cooper tackles a plethora of topics ranging from how to approach pegging a guy to how to approach a boyfriend who refuses to celebrate valentines day. Oh, and is it fucked up to date your best friends ex? Most importantly...will the real slim shady please stand up? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cuSmnBIIRxrgt6TAsqfKd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3430</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I HAVE A BOYFRIEND</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4uu81pwVEbGcLpKr10rX6P?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4uu81pwVEbGcLpKr10rX6P</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5540</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>108- Pick me, Choose me, Love me.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7fwu43mLS39ieLzohA8bvw?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Father Cooper is BACK AT IT AGAIN detailing her violent interaction with her former New York neighbor and the recent incident where she almost killed her new LA neighbors. Classic. Then, Alex turns into a full ASMR Erotica Performer and details the skull fucking rendezvous that ended with her bodily chunks on the floor. Alex’s roommate, Lauren, is back and Alex calls her out for her Corona Dating App 101 fails. BUT, Lauren’s messaging style gets revamped before your eyes as she allows Alex to take over her phone and message the men herself. Lastly, but most important... Alex leaves the episode announcing a huge bomb Mr. Sexy Zoom man dropped on her before he left for London and a decision she must face and make by Monday. ENJOY Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7fwu43mLS39ieLzohA8bvw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3491</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>107- "I'm Just Not In Love With You Anymore."</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3tLrlZxKkucfoiLr104Wt9?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week is pure drama, drama and more drama. Father Cooper kicks off the episode by revealing a dirty package she sent across the pond.. but more importantly, she tells the Daddy Gang about a secret she’s been keeping from them. Tune in to find out what actually happened to Alex last month in London. This story includes the police and a very toxic third party that will be exposed and revealed. Lastly, someone who ended their 7 year relationship with their boyfriend joins the show this week and reveals how she found the courage to end it, the hard truth of ending it over just “not being in love anymore,” details on the breakup conversation, and life after a breakup. Guess who? ENJOY DADDIES!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3tLrlZxKkucfoiLr104Wt9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2800</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>106- New Year, Old Me (ft. Toxicity)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1eQvzIOatQFZzsJMe9dBb8?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Father Cooper returns in 2021, exploiting a psychotic toxic event that recently took place between her and the infamous Mr. Sexy Zoom Man. This drama filled story fully exposes Alex for attempting a manipulation tactic gone wrong. She fucked up her own scheme and now has to pay the price. WHO IS READY FOR TOXIC ALEX TO BE BACK?… her therapist is guaranteed to be getting ghosted this week. ENJOY DADDIES. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1eQvzIOatQFZzsJMe9dBb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3623</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Daddy Gang</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6lvqpk3SJYWWZLrKgrfrVm?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>From the Father’s mouth to your ears, Alex Cooper welcomes you to the worldwide phenomenon that is Call Her Daddy. Strap in for raw conversations on sex, relationships, mental health and more. New episodes every Wednesday. Listen free, only on Spotify!  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6lvqpk3SJYWWZLrKgrfrVm</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>87</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>105- Goodbye 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0x55pE814aZyXUgiATW4YC?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Goodbye 2020… Father Cooper takes on a solo episode this week and closes out the insane year of 2020 with the Daddy Gang. She talks highs and lows of her year as well as the Daddy Gang's. She also gives a quick dick riding tip to girls on how to make sure the small dick stays in and doesn't fall out, what to do when your boyfriend slut shames you for your past, training men like you train a dog, a story of a guy Alex fucked to use his rooftop pool in NYC, the issue of dating someone in college after you have graduated, what to do when you find your boyfriend saving photos on Instagram of other girls, the rules to being friends with your ex, the McRib?, fucking your physiotherapist, AND A WHOLE LOT MORE. ENJOY DADDIES. SEE YOU IN 2021!!!!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0x55pE814aZyXUgiATW4YC</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3429</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>104- The Roadmap to his A**hole</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6dPq1Ct6i6UMdJ6GkiX6d6?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Father Cooper discusses what is about to happen in the next 24 hours of her life, and it includes 2 men. A DP?! No lol. Maybe. Then, she is joined by the brilliant sex therapist and Daddy Gang favorite, Emily Morse! Emily and Alex discuss how to tell your partner you have sexual trauma (TRIGGER WARNING 14:22-17:51), men that can’t get hard, dating a pre-mature ejaculator, how to ride dick with your legs around his head, ways to finger and eat his/her asshole, vaginismus, herpes AND MUCH MORE. Enjoy Daddies!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6dPq1Ct6i6UMdJ6GkiX6d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4770</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>103- Tana Mongeau Exposed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/43lCVMhqjlOAtoA77rOGXU?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>2 years later, the bitch showed up and immediately regretted it. TANA MONGEAU EXPOSED. #DADDYGANG Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43lCVMhqjlOAtoA77rOGXU</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5263</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>102- The Toxic Dick Daze (ft. Katie Florence)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5khnw2QjNVFVc8smwedwdg?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>DADDY GANG-This week, Alex discusses the intense fallout of her decision to ghost her therapist for 3 straight weeks while being in a foreign country quarantining with a man. Not smart Big Al! Then, the first ever Daddy Gang member sits down with Alex to join the show this week! Katie Florence, who started her career as a substitute-school teacher now turned Tik-Tok star, initially caught Alex’s attention from the relationship comedy videos she was making during quarantine. The girls messaged on insta and then Katie flew up to NYC to record an episode with The Father. She brings vulnerability and relatability to the show this week, explaining her consistent and frustrating issue of always getting ghosted, being addicted to toxic dick, and the struggles and stress that come with finding ‘the one’ worth settling down for. She also walks us through a time in her life when she was in a Polyamorous relationship, detailing specifics of what it is like to date a man who is dating multiple women, how condoms work in the dynamic, and STD testing. The episode provides a fun new dating perspective from someone other than Alex’s big head. It’s fun to explore the dating world through someone else’s eyes in this week’s episode, especially when it's Daddy Gang :) ENJOY!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5khnw2QjNVFVc8smwedwdg</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4442</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>101- Boyfriend D*ck (ft. Harry Jowsey)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5OjLIkOAlIXQRbLIPL42uK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On this week’s episode, Alex details her Cabo excursion with a man, as well as why she is in London with a man. Then, Harry Jowsey, an irrelevant one-hit-wonder reality television star, joins the show to talk ALL THINGS SEX AND DATING. They discuss girls over performing in the bedroom, the terrifying experience Harry had when he first got his ass eaten by a wrestler, and his first disastrous anal experience. They also get into the joys of eating pussy, his celibacy for 4 months, and good old 'boyfriend dick'. Also, Harry gives some great tips to boost women's success rate in the dating game aka stop going on dates at nighttime. Alex and Harry also talk dating apps for men and women, and provide a sure-fire strategy to land your target. If your dating life has not been successful, this episode is for you! Lastly, Harry addresses his ex girlfriend aka the only reason he is relevant and puts the drama to bed. ENJOY DADDY GANG!!!!!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5OjLIkOAlIXQRbLIPL42uK</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3926</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100- MOTHER COOPER</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1BOxz435WuyW5ZQB7OqtCC?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>100. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1BOxz435WuyW5ZQB7OqtCC</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2865</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>99- BREAKING NEWS</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6Se6ZBjndRPrLsMFZwmB5M?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>DADDY GANG- BREAKING NEWS. At the beginning of this week's episode, Alex divulges what is going on in her life and provides breaking news. THEN, Hannah Berner is back this week with Alex to discuss meeting the men they are dating’s parents… or not? Discussing men’s dating history and the fascinating question which is- what if the guy you are dating has a history of dating a type of girl and you aren’t it???? Should you feel insecure if you are the ONLY brunette he has ever dated and all his ex's are blondes?? They also get into different fighting tactics with your partner, and discuss ex’s and if you should or should not bring them up with the person you are currently dating. LASTLY, Alex asks Hannah her thoughts on 3somes and 4somes because she is considering engaging in these escapades with one of the men she is currently dating. ENJOY DADDIES!!!!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6Se6ZBjndRPrLsMFZwmB5M</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3569</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>98- The Red Wedding (ft. Lauren &amp; Hannah Berner)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/25ddsvNcE5LsyhE28XQMKo?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Welcome to The Red Wedding Mother FUCKERS. Alex is joined by childhood best friend, Lauren, to exploit the recent drama that she has been involved in with her ex- Slim Shady, his best friend who is getting married next week, and his current side hoe. Lots and lots of drama, which ends in Alex potentially attending a wedding? Then, Hannah Berner joins Alex to discuss an update on both of their dating lives. Hannah has a 44 year old boyfriend who she has fallen in love with and moved in with?!?! What has quarantine done to us! The women also detail the dirty FaceTime sex they have been having with their men, the perfect toilet angle for the p*ssy(?!), discuss the ass eating they are loving, and the angles that make your asshole look fabulous. ALSO, Hannah explains a strange phenomenon she is experiencing that includes only being able to have an orgasm when her legs are straight. ENJOY DADDY GANG!!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25ddsvNcE5LsyhE28XQMKo</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3917</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>97- The Life of a Porn Star (ft. Lana Rhoades)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0CxA5oyExggktcUhpMTuLh?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Call Her Daddy introduces it’s first Porn Star guest, Lana Rhoades. Lana discusses life before, during, and after porn. Lana knew since she was 13 years old she wanted to do porn, she explains how the hard core scenes (gang bangs) have left her scarred, and her dating life after porn, money and happiness. The girls also discuss eating your man’s ass while he is on all fours, different types of balls, school girl role-play, and the strangest role-play Lana proposed to a boyfriend and got turned down to do. Alex also gives person updates on the men in her life and a special Slim Shady update. Enjoy! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0CxA5oyExggktcUhpMTuLh</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4344</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>96- The Orgasm Gap &amp; Forced Sex Fantasies (ft. Sex With Emily)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3I0lRxDPVBZ1NLBWV5mgoc?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>DADDY GANG!!! This week Father Cooper kicks off the episode with an update on a man she is dating. The update includes a SERIOUS social media road block, one that she has never encountered with a man before... so naturally the uncharted territory calls for a full mental break down!!! THEN, Emily Morse, the sex therapist best known for her podcast 'Sex with Emily,' joins the show to discuss an array of sexual topics. They get right into it, addressing 'forced sex fantasies,' which Emily explains in detail the psychology behind why so many people experience them/why you should not feel shame for having these fantasies. The women also dive into juicy topics like the huge orgasm gap between men and women, how to have an orgasm, how to SQUIRT, people in relationships with different sex drives, and a whole lot more. ENJOY!!!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3I0lRxDPVBZ1NLBWV5mgoc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3760</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>95- Mental Terrorism (ft. The Bitch Bible)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1rqtjTeB7ajpZvqwOA7vXb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Alex discusses the scary reality that is now life in isolation. She explains the affects that the time alone has had on her love life, the two 30 year-old men she is currently dating, her journey towards health and the battle she’s facing in attempting to leave the crazy behind and in her past. THERE IS ALSO A GUEST THIS WEEK. Introducing, Jackie Schimmel, who is the host of ‘The Bitch Bible’ Podcast. The women discuss the strange rule that goes a little something like this- If you can’t joke about divorce, cheating, or breaking up with your partner, then you are getting a divorce, getting cheated on, or getting broken up with by your partner!!! Joking about divorce is the ultimate way to a healthy marriage; Jackie can attest because she is in fact married! They also discuss cringe influencers overdoing swipe up ads, Tik-Tokers vs their personal 15 year old awkward phases, and a traumatic sexual experience that Jackie endured on a date, which included a man humping her leg, squatting, and cumming. Enjoy Daddy Gang!!!!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1rqtjTeB7ajpZvqwOA7vXb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3938</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>94- Bisexuality &amp; Depression (ft. Maggie Lindemann)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0zCcsnlugWN2xACNOkqv7A?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Call Her Daddy gets a bit more serious, dark, and real this week. Father Cooper kicks it off with a sex update and some healthy news regarding her dating life and the show. Then, the guest this week, Maggie Lindemann, a singer/songwriter, joins the show and discusses her personal journey to coming out as a bisexual woman. Maggie explains when she knew she was bisexual, how she revealed the news to her family via text message and to the world via live stream (!!!). She also discusses the struggles of girl on girl relationships being fetishized, the frustrations of hooking up with straight women, and how being bisexual has affected her male relationships. The episode only gets deeper when Maggie opens up about her younger teen years, self harm, and the road to recovery and getting healthy. Enjoy Daddies! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0zCcsnlugWN2xACNOkqv7A</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3490</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>93- The Sloppy Toppy Delight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/320apPUfIEI7nT4pjBqYKk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week is a solo episode with your father! Alex is detailing her sexcapades with Mr. Sexy Zoom Man ft. her cum in his beard, his pussy eating skills, her sex with him, and a battle between him and another man that made her realize how she feels about him. Alex also gets deep and opens up to the Daddy Gang about anxiety and some hate she has been receiving. AND OF COURSE, you all know when you leave Alex alone with a solo episode… you are getting a new blow job tip!!!! This bad boy focuses on the upper third region of the penis and a multi-tasking moment with the taint. Enjoy!!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">320apPUfIEI7nT4pjBqYKk</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3954</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>92- MILEY CYRUS</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4aqiLMvHH3ciDLinkwmxTk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>THE DADDY OF ALL DADDIES HAS ARRIVED. Miley Fucking Cyrus joins the show this week and immediately hits it off with your father. Miley is officially Daddy Gang and spills an extreme amount of tea this week. So get your popcorn, relax, and enjoy the show folks. Heartbreak, trauma, therapy, guilt, girl-on-girl, being put on the no-fly list for smuggling drugs, her relationship with Hannah Montana, the first person she lost her male virginity to, her 'Love Languages', what she is looking for in a relationship, her personal sex advice, AND MORE. This episode is packed with a whole lot of content. INTRODUCING MILEY CYRUS EVERYONE. Enjoy! #DADDYGANG (once you finish listening, go watch the video vlog of Miley &amp; Alex meeting/ hanging on Youtube @ alexandracooper) Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4aqiLMvHH3ciDLinkwmxTk</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3471</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>91- Dabble with Emasculating Him (ft Olivia O'Brien)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4DRlmApfbxPIQcguX6u50y?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, your single father brings you along the journey as she narrates her first date with Mr. Sexy Zoom Man, and you can clearly hear the sexual tension through the microphone. THEN, the beautiful and talented singer/songwriter Olivia O’Brien, well known for writing songs about the men she dates (very on brand with CHD) joins the show. Olivia dishes new information about the “house rule,” which will tell you who has the power in your relationship. She also details a recent cheating scandal that her friend Charli publicly went through. Moral of the story, never trust your man when he says he doesn’t have a second snapchat :) Alex &amp; Olivia also discuss being a good friend to your girl friends, trust issues, dating in LA, and awful sex that is being had. Olivia also recounts a time she blacked out and slapped a man in the face. Great times this week. ENJOY! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4DRlmApfbxPIQcguX6u50y</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4046</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90- I'm Going to LA...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/14Dfbp5VqpYw6q7lAyEuX4?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Alex is going to LA for a business trip..../ potential date?! This week, Father Cooper reveals that she might for the first time be mixing business with pleasure. But is convinced it is worth it...lol. A man in entertainment and not an athlete?? We love to see it. She also discusses what is means when your boyfriend tells you to block a girl on social media *BIG RED FLAG* Also this week, HANNAH IS BACK. The episode continues the interview with Hannah Berner. They talk Hinge, the horrors of dating comedians, and answer Daddy Gang's questions in Questionz of ZEWEEK!!! Enjoy daddies :) Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14Dfbp5VqpYw6q7lAyEuX4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3333</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>89- "I F**ked the Mascot" (ft. Hannah Berner)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3DIwo0EX3oNgyT7KkVjeHC?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Father Cooper is joined by a guest who is bringing the energy and a shit-ton of wild stories this week. Daddy Gang, give a warm welcome to Hannah Berner. In this week's episode, Hannah fucks a mascot, Alex lies about Chlamydia, and a man does coke off Hannah's tit. Are you READY?! Also, the Flirting Bible is revealed, the women dive into Hannah's time on reality television, her parents watching her have sex, and their commonality of both having been Division 1 athletes, and also their love for f*cking athletes! ENJOY #DADDYGANG Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3DIwo0EX3oNgyT7KkVjeHC</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4233</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>88- The L Word.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7slwC4PeJ3vIOQBuizE4Fu?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Alex is coming clean about the man that has been in her life behind the scenes for 5 years... and the L word is used. Also, A DADDY GANG MEMBER IS FEATURED ON THE SHOW THIS WEEK!!!!! Our guest is bringing you a very relatable situation- the 'in between' stage. We are discussing how to navigate it and calling her out on misreading some clear signs. Lastly, the topic of initiating sex 50/50 in a relationship is hammered into the brains of every woman this week. Alex provides 2 huge tips for girls that struggle to be confident when taking the lead. ENJOY!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7slwC4PeJ3vIOQBuizE4Fu</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3425</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>87- PSA: He Doesn’t Like You</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0cOfT9dgJKUKY2m1LMvLdC?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Your Father, Alexandra, gets deep this week and walks women through the wake-up call they all need. Stop clinging on to every little thing a men says to you and LOOK AT THE BIG PICTURE FACTS. If you viewed your dating life from a third party view.. what would you think of yourself? An episode EVERY woman needs to hear. Also, giving a huge tip for women that are having a hard time achieving an orgasm/ have never had one (wink wink ASMR porn). And, if you have a bad gag reflex, Alex is coming to the rescue with tricks of how to mask it. ENJOY #DADDYGANG Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0cOfT9dgJKUKY2m1LMvLdC</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3260</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>86- Fuckboy Love &amp; Fingering for Dummies (ft. Savannah Montano)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7bgXGDGJ12qTADRhNod57H?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>HERE WE GO!!! THE RUNDOWN FOR THIS WEEK'S SHOW: We are instructing men on exactly how to finger a girl's butt during doggy, which finger to use and the speed at which it should be happening; normalizing butt plugs and how it makes a women's orgasm SO much better, how to get a guy to be ok with a vibrator in the bedroom, getting cheated on, why we pick fuck boys, the OG way to finger a girl, and handing over the secret potion for women of how to make a man fall in love by 'fucking his fingers.' Is this episode sexual enough!? ENJOY. GUEST HOST: Savannah Montano. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bgXGDGJ12qTADRhNod57H</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3856</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>85- Let's Have Sex Again...(ft. Savannah Montano)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4qVyLI22AFTIWj0moZOx0U?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>2 PART SERIES. Alex is joined by guest Savannah Montano, a girl she idolized at a young age because of the promiscuous lifestyle Sav promoted as a teen on the internet. The two girls, now in their 20s, have become friends through Instagram and are talking dating high profiled men, strategically not sleeping with men for an extended period of time (3 months), and Savannah addresses her favorite sex- the 'slow stroke'- and gives details of how to give head/ride on top. The girl's also discuss how the men in their lives are terrified of the show and getting exposed. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4qVyLI22AFTIWj0moZOx0U</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3621</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>84- The 3rd Roommate Speaks...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3IW4NqdWQ6OqV6wjkdOS5N?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week's guest is the infamous third roommate who lived with Alex and Sophia. The episode officially closes the chapter surrounding ALL the drama. ONWARD!!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3IW4NqdWQ6OqV6wjkdOS5N</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2954</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>83- Dave Portnoy- America's #1 Porn Star?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6Q5r7KsiZG1Wik8uAu40nr?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>https://blacklivesmatters.carrd.co https://blacklivesmatters.carrd.co https://blacklivesmatters.carrd.co https://blacklivesmatters.carrd.co https://blacklivesmatters.carrd.co https://blacklivesmatters.carrd.co . Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6Q5r7KsiZG1Wik8uAu40nr</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3431</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>82- The Funeral</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0Z8JhLKZljvXzXGjO4ahle?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>A new era begins. A single father, a divorced father, moves forward with the show. But first - we must attend this funeral and mourn the loss. Then... WE PARTY! (Daddy Gang drinking game- drink every time Alex says the word f*ck… you’ll all be hammered). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0Z8JhLKZljvXzXGjO4ahle</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3337</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>81- Daddy Speaks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/62fPXwVyiBZAEiRZauN4HR?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>El Pres Explains the Call Her Daddy Fiasco From the Barstool Perspective Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62fPXwVyiBZAEiRZauN4HR</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1743</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80- How To Keep Them Interested During Quarantine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5WJgErkBamQt65WE29rWCN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Kesha...The End . Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5WJgErkBamQt65WE29rWCN</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3288</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>79- OnlyFans = WHORES</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1Zn63X0s6XDyxUJxgVdOxb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>It's all about to change... Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1Zn63X0s6XDyxUJxgVdOxb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4238</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>78- Seeking Arrangements: Our Story</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1QC2vM6y9DdDxh0kY2OvLs?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This is how you should do Corona. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1QC2vM6y9DdDxh0kY2OvLs</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4326</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>77- Re-release (Corona Edition)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4WUvcJJ4HQ9D7ylGOnZzKS?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We love you all, stay safe. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4WUvcJJ4HQ9D7ylGOnZzKS</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3300</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>76- Sorry for the Shit Show</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3MqSSC7xjCuw6Z0kL7f531?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3MqSSC7xjCuw6Z0kL7f531</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3481</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>75- We Had Fun</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3rjngeDxIunMKDnatAuoJY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3rjngeDxIunMKDnatAuoJY</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3018</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>74- It's Over</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1NXHgy3ErBEyb5AUJ5EDJ3?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1NXHgy3ErBEyb5AUJ5EDJ3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3241</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>73- SUPLEH</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1MySlNec1NdG8iUhyaWD4L?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1MySlNec1NdG8iUhyaWD4L</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3605</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>72- Prisoners of Azkaban</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6CEz1h5lhfeFOBbEqXBn8d?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6CEz1h5lhfeFOBbEqXBn8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3418</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>71- Floop's Fooglies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/32hGGnvrCgYZmeCYKTZX2o?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32hGGnvrCgYZmeCYKTZX2o</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2807</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>70- Dear Side Hoe...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2RYqSwDOWa7dP2oOA0IsSg?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The episode kicks off with a recap from the girls as they discuss their latest drama, specifically Alex who catches Slim Shady in a lie on her recent trip to visit him! Uh oh! They also address the proper way to behave during the early stages of dating and when to post to social media… daddies… we gotta reel it back in. Lastly, men with little dicks need to stop lusting after women with fat asses AND yes, we are giving hand jobs again. Thank you!  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2RYqSwDOWa7dP2oOA0IsSg</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2852</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>69- EPISODE 69 (ft. Chlamydia)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/58XV1vqeuzLArzce9zavHU?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The episode you have all been waiting for... and we have been dreading.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58XV1vqeuzLArzce9zavHU</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2924</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>68- Nudes &amp; The New York Post</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5rvpjAR5qwWAz6vGh33TlN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls kick off this week's episode discussing their photo shoot from HELL and what to do when you are dealing with a greedy little bitch boy who asks “Can I get more?” after you send a nude. Knock. It. Off. Also this week, the girls do something a little different as they discuss some pop-culture in way that is most likely going to get them sued! Yay! Last but not least, it's now Alex's turn to spill the deets on her dating life. Let's go Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5rvpjAR5qwWAz6vGh33TlN</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3587</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>67- BACK AT IT AGAIN</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4GCxrG2O4eLiiTLDnOk0WN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>WE ARE BACK. Get ready for a very different episode this week. The girls have decided to do Call Her Daddy a little different this year starting with a HUGE announcement from Sofia and a deeply personal account from Alex. The Fathers have feelings!? Don't worry, they are still just as unwell. This week's episode addresses the topic of 'first impressions' with your significant other's friends and family and how to handle it. The girls roast the women who try too hard to be “one of the guys”, and last but not least, some hot girl-on-girl talk. Cheers to 2020!  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4GCxrG2O4eLiiTLDnOk0WN</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3996</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/487atWKCJQsIxYZehik8li?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>2020 is the year for the Daddy Gang....  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">487atWKCJQsIxYZehik8li</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3785</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2Mrl5xvlmxUIKbKGhfvRdT?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Happy Holidays Daddy Gang :) WE LOVE YOU Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2Mrl5xvlmxUIKbKGhfvRdT</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5521</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>66- Why We Can't Cum</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1eDvog8bNOFM9WQ0aWFE7A?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week's episode kicks off with a mental breakdown from Alex who went snooping at a guys house and saw something she shouldn't have. Risky business! Also, the girls discuss why they (and women everywhere) can't cum during sex and a revolutionary way to take an a** pic. Ladies, this will be the only nude you will want to take from now on, GUARANTEED. Plus, the girls debate if it's ever okay to send a dirty video.…that includes you having sex with someone else. Hot? Or not?  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1eDvog8bNOFM9WQ0aWFE7A</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3683</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>65- The Daddy Hotline (3) ft. Anal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3cCZoB7Yoh1nzu3IjjeYjf?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>“How has your dating life been affected since starting this podcast???” It's a question the fathers receive regularly…and they are answering it candidly in this week's episode. They also tackle some tough questions like “What is the best form of birth control?” and “How kinky is too kinky?” Tune in, as the fathers have some MAJOR differing opinions this week!!! Lastly, with the Holidays approaching, Alex and Sofia are telling us exactly what to get our fuck buddies for Christmas. Listen up! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cCZoB7Yoh1nzu3IjjeYjf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2498</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>64- The Cocaine Chronicles</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0haGCqe1rHN6xcvbSrvStG?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We all know Sofia has gotten into some trouble in her past….well now she is finally ready to tell the full story of her time behind bars! Get ready for some bend over and cough fun because this is a genuinely crazy story (our court system is f*cked!) Also in this weeks episode, the girls have had a complete change of heart and think you should NOT delete pictures of your ex but only under ONE condition: men, if you want to up your dick game, trust us on this one. And last but not least, Sofia gives a personal account of what a man did recently that rocked her world…and it includes a tongue and a vibrator! EVERYONE SHOULD BE DOING THIS IN BED. Tune in! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0haGCqe1rHN6xcvbSrvStG</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3652</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>63- How Our Families Really Feel…</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0DLScpRqx7IUpuLQOCWiik?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Alex and Sofia get real as they dive into the family drama they have endured since starting this podcast…extended family is the worst! (LOL). Happy Thanksgiving! This week the girls are discussing a brilliant way to make friends (especially in a new city), the biggest dating app no-no that even the smartest men are committing (watch out for this one ladies), and lastly, THE BALL! As in mens' balls. And before you roll your eyes and say ‘this is amateur hour', think again! For some men, how you handle his balls could determine how he forever remembers you. CAUTION: This episode includes the most grotesque story submission ever. Not for children!    Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0DLScpRqx7IUpuLQOCWiik</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3511</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>62- Oprah &amp; F*cking Your Friend's Ex</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1ymXaUtfvpHC9ZE5GA5ErN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Yes. It is true. Call Her Daddy has been nominated for an award alongside OPRAH WINFREY. For what you may ask? It's not what you would expect! Make sure to tune in, Alex and Sofia are giving us all the details. Also this week, the girls go on a rant resemblant of an exorcism as they express their disdain for all things pertaining to the gym…specifically girls that get dolled up to work out- STOP WEARING YOUR HAIR DOWN. They also discuss the sensitive subject that is fucking your friends ex…should they always be completely off limits? Lastly, Alex is giving us story-time as she recalls a hookup she had recently where the guy did something…weird AF. Lots to cover!  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ymXaUtfvpHC9ZE5GA5ErN</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3841</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>61- Revenge Porn</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3nLrLd69MUAyejxPFvmQyI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls partied hard this past week and are getting into all the wild details including strip clubs, head injuries, and an NHL team! Wahoo! Also, Alex and Sofia have breaking news regarding TWO major iPhone updates/hacks. If you have ever thought of sending a nude or having FaceTime sex, you better listen up! Lastly, the girls talk about revenge porn AND do a rate and review of a fellow daddygang member's nude... in real time. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3nLrLd69MUAyejxPFvmQyI</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3419</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60- You F*cked Up, Now What?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3pjpfSpY5518RYiidcGjwF?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Alex has a black eye and is telling us exactly what happened PLUS, she has a confession…she ended up in bed with an ex! Get the full story- it's as crazy as it sounds. Also this week, the girls discuss drunken fuckups and exactly how to recover. Whether you got sloppy in front of a girl you've been trying to bang or texted your crush something super embarrassing, we've got you. If you want any shot at redeeming yourself, there is a method to follow that works and may just surprise you. The girls are also discussing an injection that is not just making sex better for women…but making them squirt. Sofias' mom's friend had the procedure done and is telling us all about it. Lastly, and most importantly, did you know you can teach yourself to squirt? Alex and Sofia are talking about just how to squirt on demand.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3pjpfSpY5518RYiidcGjwF</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4034</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>59- Backhand That Cl*t</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1GXCRDo7reLbrSyWpZ7n0J?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls get serious as they tell a chilling story that took place in Elizabeth, New Jersey. One they will never forget involving an abandoned house, law enforcement, and oh yeah, they've got it all on film (check out the CHD Instagram). Also this week, Alex and Sofia discuss a sex tip so scary they've only seen it done in porn... until now. Introducing ‘Scream' and ‘The Joker'- they tried it out for the daddies and are giving you all the details. Also men, you should be having the poop talk with your girl. We are telling you how.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1GXCRDo7reLbrSyWpZ7n0J</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4099</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>58- The Daddy Hotline (2)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/43jlBftAOXys1Y3cfsxXJ0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Covering everything from ‘how to fuck your professor' to ‘moving on from a fuckbuddy', the girls are giving us a good mix of crazy and healthy in this week's episode! They are also getting a little personal this week, as they share their worst date experiences and throw some shade at a shared nemesis of theirs (cough cough you know who you are!). Last but not least, the fathers are providing a solution to your Instagram stalking dilemma. They may have taken away the following page, but the crazy will always prevail!  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43jlBftAOXys1Y3cfsxXJ0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3507</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>57- Every Man’s Achilles Heel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4P0rO4lXBT6rGrhiG7zB2f?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this week's episode, the girls share their personal experiences with bondage…including special guest the HDMI cord! Sofia also shares another embarrassing story from her past…believe it or not it is arguably the most embarrassing thus far. Lastly, Alex and Sofia call out all the girls who are posting pictures HOLDING their ass in place. Enough is enough! Also, a sex/blowjob tip that has to do with only a guys LEFT side…his Achilles Heel.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4P0rO4lXBT6rGrhiG7zB2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3591</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>56- The Instagram Scam</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4BP0L7AA3lUYoyLvXNzGZ4?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Sofia tells us about a traumatizing experience she had while her mom was in town this past week…just say no to drugs kids! Also in the episode, the girls discuss uncircumcised dicks. They can be complicated so listen up. Even if you have never encountered one, you should know how to Gluck it like a daddy. They also talk about fitness girls on instagram, ass injections, and last but not least, eating the puss* from behind.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4BP0L7AA3lUYoyLvXNzGZ4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2853</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>55- Body Count &amp; The Social Vulture</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1QxgN8wOPqQkmrGKlUmxcV?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls discuss past sexual partners, how many is too many, and everything you've ever wondered about body count- including the EXACT number girls should tell their man. Also, they dive into the taboo topic of bad personal hygiene for women… men have been complaining about the taste/smell of their girl's clam (worst nightmare), but don't worry we have a solution! Last but not least, bringing you the social vulture. Everyone has encountered this wretched species. Tune in to find out more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1QxgN8wOPqQkmrGKlUmxcV</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3671</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>54- The Walk of Shame</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4fjsWOUy9q3THUNGB1Kq4j?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this week's episode, Alex and Sofia are giving health and wellness a good ol' fashioned try. You heard that right! The girls discuss the importance of “having your own life” in a relationship and where so many women go wrong- especially WAGS, (wives and girlfriends of professional athletes). They also discuss the most cringe-y thing a guy can post on his dating profile (no thanks), clout chasing, and most importantly WALKS OF SHAME. Otherwise known as a stride of pride for a true daddy. Enjoy!  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fjsWOUy9q3THUNGB1Kq4j</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4043</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>53- Alex &amp; Sofia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7vI2TppiQCFCB7OqF5lU6m?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This is an episode your therapist would HIGHLY recommend you do not listen to...... The girls discuss the amount of time you wait in between sex with different people…as in, how many is too many in a day? In a week? In an HOUR? And should you feel bad or embrace your inner freak? Everything answered on this week's episode. They also address the multiple personality wheel…aka the swift personality change that occurs when arguing with your partner and how to use it to your advantage. And lastly, the girls go r-o-g-u-e this week as they dissect Bang Energy, KO Watches, and Baby accounts…(baby Alessi update: we've been BLOCKED) Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7vI2TppiQCFCB7OqF5lU6m</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4146</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>52- College Life: Being Hot vs. Not</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3b2PuMEL4wTLubKqXWvIHO?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Welcome to College 101 Daddies! Bringing you the ultimate guide for back to school- the College Playbook. Get ready to finesse the fuck out of your college campus and pay close attention, because navigating school is a little different when you are a 5 vs. 10 (apologies in advance)! They also talk about what to do when you're BLOCKED, getting Shadow banned on Instagram, and a sex move that is so simple yet so effective…the Hamburger. It's like a workout for your esophagus. Get that exercise in! Also, if you are ever suffering from cotton mouth- have no fear the daddies are here!!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b2PuMEL4wTLubKqXWvIHO</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3455</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>51- Win Your Ex Back</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4pj7whXTNE55myHwoA7bTa?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Men are out here sucking their own dicks, sticking them in tissue boxes, and comparing them to remote controls…and we are here to address it! Also, we discuss the ultimate strategy to win your Ex back, a hack to take the perfect selfie, and male dick pics. And last but not least, we talk about what to do AFTER he cums and how you SHOULD keep sucking...  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4pj7whXTNE55myHwoA7bTa</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4252</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50- MILF HUNTER (Guest #1)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2w81eY3Vypw3hOVygP0xRD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>No description needed.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2w81eY3Vypw3hOVygP0xRD</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4032</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49 - Stop Ruining Your Relationship</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7l5vcz6EwGP3np8sORWZfD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Girls get more insecure after they get into a relationship. FACTS. This week, the fathers discuss why this is the case and how it leads to women doing bat shit crazy things... including Alex's most brilliant/insane behavior yet. They also get into a new sex position called “Time Out” for all you naughty hoes and how to get verified on Instagram REAL quick. P.S- Alex and Sofia reveal their personal experiences with some serious stalkers Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7l5vcz6EwGP3np8sORWZfD</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3194</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>48- The Daddy Hotline</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2ETxKA0uJVnSqOGS17eZU0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls are covering everything from, “Is it okay to stay friends with your ex?” to the 'bonus nude'- a nude that is saving relationships one send at a time...milfhunter didn't even know about it!!! They also discuss dealing with your significant others parents (cue pervy dads), men posting shirtless pics/food on the gram, and the most insane way this girl caught her man cheating. Lastly, there is a consent app celebrities are using and the girls are giving you all the details. A full episode dedicated to the daddy gang. Enjoy!!  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ETxKA0uJVnSqOGS17eZU0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2998</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>47- Open Relationships</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4K1q3l6XAMOqKGGUm4VPIt?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls talk about their traumatic last week living in the Lower East Side of NYC (Sofia witnessed a stabbing). They also discuss dressing up in lingerie for your man…with some personal FAILS, everything about open relationships, and some super dirty school girl role-play. Including detailed, nasty, line-for-line things to say to pull it off. P.S. Enough with the b-day reposts, no one cares!!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4K1q3l6XAMOqKGGUm4VPIt</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3700</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>46- Hornier on Our Periods</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1yt8F6RItC120gUGQBXblA?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, the girls address two things men do that are total turn offs- baby talk and getting too drunk. Also, the girls tell a recent personal story of their own drunk escapades in NYC, Alex's husband, throw-up, and a Restoration Hardware couch. They also have a confession…they too have taken pictures of men while they are not looking/sleeping…and explain the reasons why. Lastly, they discuss all things period sex (including oral) with some embarrassing personal stories! Yay! P.S. Baby Alessi is back. Instagram influencer parents must be stopped.         Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1yt8F6RItC120gUGQBXblA</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4094</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>45- Post Sex Tape Regret</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0tZz4oToQASdkHRqpKnSia?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this weeks episode, Alex and Sofia recap their staycation experience at an old NY hotel and it is TERRIFYING. They also discuss nonconsensual sex tapes, when to know and accept you're just a fuck, and groupies taking pics of the men they just had sex with….while they are asleep. Last but not least, introducing the PSTR-Post Sex Tape Regret. It's a wild ride :) Also, they surprise the daddy gang with an added iPhone recording.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0tZz4oToQASdkHRqpKnSia</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3419</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>44- Girls He Fucks vs. Girls He Dates</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0b8Y0cHtwpoitxv0xHeJzD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Lots to cover on this weeks episode! Sofia and Alex talk about the types of girls men choose to fuck vs. date, and they are getting extremely specific/personal- talking about their exs. They are also discussing the REAL reason females cockblock their girlfriends, instagram bios that are preventing you from getting laid, and two new moves that will make your behind look like you got ass injections! Also, Alex reads a text from her mom that puts everyone's stalking skills to shame.    Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b8Y0cHtwpoitxv0xHeJzD</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3254</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>43- Run-ins With Your Ex</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3z2GjBBs4nrREBknCv395I?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Alex and Sofia are talking about running into your ex (accidental or on purpose), how to handle it, and reminisce on their times of being total losers and letting a guy get the best of them. They also discuss escaping the friendzone for girls and an update for men who continue to marinate there. And lastly, TWO new blow job updates- The Gluck Gluck Turbo Edition. P.S- We gotta stop with birthday months... Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3z2GjBBs4nrREBknCv395I</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3856</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>42- Let Him Watch Porn</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2hStsMMtgvI5mToXOhK5hR?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, the Fathers are discussing the highly anticipated porn debate-should your man be allowed to watch it? Uhhhhhh, duh. Strip clubs, massage parlors, boys nights, you name it, the girls are talking about it and get ready for a reality check. Also, presenting two new sex moves that will have men celebrating WAY more than just their independence this 4th of July. Introducing, the Superman and Glory Tit Shot (tits want facials too)! Last but not least, there is something extremely sexy you can be doing on both twitter AND tumbler to spice shit up. Tune in, daddies. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2hStsMMtgvI5mToXOhK5hR</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3274</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>41- How To Eat Pussy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7dUKeNrTYGrOj7FebDf1OT?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Sofia and Alex PROMISE that after this episode, you will eat the clam and make her O in a way that has not been done before. The. Seven. Wonders. Of. The. Pussy. Eating. World. As an extension of the 'Cooch Gobbler,' there is something for even the most advanced sex gurus to learn. Also, the girls finally discuss hooking up with co-workers, including some personal experiences. And lastly, we are telling you where you can get some cheap Plan B and it is NOT planned parenthood! Let's get after it, daddies!  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7dUKeNrTYGrOj7FebDf1OT</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3389</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40- Rejection &amp; Exposing the Clit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3WcZTjy2ES2lH32w9di4km?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls discuss their encounter with a #daddygang member at a drug store in NY and let's just say shit got wild! They also introduce some new sex pointers, including a move that Alex said made a man cum in under one minute- cue the ‘Pendulum Pussy'. And lastly, they get into REJECTION. It's happened to all of us, and this is how to deal, like a daddy. P.S. It is with heavy hearts, we include a surefire way to know if your girl is faking it. Protect yourself! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3WcZTjy2ES2lH32w9di4km</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3303</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>39- Squirting &amp; Ghosting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1wJfXjYNiDFx2B2aMrY4JJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls finally get into all things SQUIRTING. What is it, how to do it, how to fake it, are men into it? Give HIM a facial! Squirt or be squirted on. They also discuss some criminal activity they witnessed at the bar by multiple men, a serious Gluck Gluck update, and some new social media drama involving fake influencers. Lastly, listen up daddies, this is how you deal with being ghosted, once and for all. CHD style ;) Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1wJfXjYNiDFx2B2aMrY4JJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3873</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>38- Welcome to Slut Camp</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0zSxL8OAyqWTEjGnpGW9gL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls are discussing shower sex, panic boners, and Slut Camp. Yes, you heard that right. Welcome to Slut Camp, where you will learn how to conceal the slut and trick your man into thinking you are wifey material. Everyone deserves a slut phase with no repercussions! They also talk poop fetishes and where they originated (army bases?), embarrassing things bitches are doing on instagram, and last but not least, Alex tells a tragic tale involving her a** hole, a penis, and a cheating scandal.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0zSxL8OAyqWTEjGnpGW9gL</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3657</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>37- Cheating Olympics &amp; Apartment Orgys</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2moVlaNH8d7r1nbj2AGKVI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this weeks episode, the girls tell a story of an unexpected visitor who showed up to their apartment…and shit got sexual. They also address what signs to look out for if you think your partner is being shady. Cheat or be cheated on! Lastly, they discuss hot, steamy bathroom sex, a serious tip to spice things up with your guy/girl in public group settings, and some hacks that could RUIN LIVES (Do Not Disturb, Reverse Phone Lookup, Uber locator).  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2moVlaNH8d7r1nbj2AGKVI</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3121</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>36- Sex Sins &amp; Girls DMing First</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3vD47U8UOyGqJka4MYCt3p?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Alex and Sofia are talking datings apps and sliding into the DMs, specifically for girls who are not shooting their shot and absolutely need to be. They are also talking sex ‘sins,' where they cover the basics like foreplay, screaming and scratching but also include some you haven't thought of and are probably committing. You don't deserve to f*** if you are doing these!! Finally, the girls lose their shit while trying to explain the newest most underrated sex position. Not for the easily offended. P.S. girls need to stop crying about getting hit on. Knock. it. off.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3vD47U8UOyGqJka4MYCt3p</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3502</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>35- Professional Athletes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0uVNQyQWFe22BVDb2oU23E?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Alex and Sofia are getting into how to make your girl and/or guy jealous, especially out at the bar/in social settings. It's unhealthy but it works! They also discuss a little black (manipulative) book a guy left behind that got his d*** sucked, their embarrassing makeup moments- when a guy walks in on the foundation/eyebrow/contour phase, and a PSA from milf hunter on how he likes girls to ride it on top. Lastly, they finally begin to touch on Professional Athletes with a personal testimonial from Alex, a side bitch, and a cum rag. Enjoy.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0uVNQyQWFe22BVDb2oU23E</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4458</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>34- Fu** Dave Portnoy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/51YR1dFRNrh1kJLknFtqZ2?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls discuss some scary things they witnessed at the bar this past weekend and are once again helping men get laid (we are giving you a makeover). They are also talking about how to use whiskey dick to fuck with a fuckboy and a jack-in-the-box nude to make a man cry. Lastly, they get into the scariest snooping hack to date which reveals ALL of your partner's password. And address girls, poop, and the lengths we will go to hide it. P.S. Doggy is out, the Pony Express is in.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">51YR1dFRNrh1kJLknFtqZ2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3967</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>33- Clits and Coke</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6LsOUkAyNosT1oienuZbcL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Is it okay for people in relationships to like the opposite sex's pics on instagram? The girls are addressing the topic and introduce a psychotic way to see ALL of your partner's instagram activity. They also discuss an amazing way to dominate dating apps (that has worked for both of the girls), a serious criminal past involving the Fathers, and lastly a sex position that made a guy cry that involves girl-on-top and NO eye contact. PSA: Be careful of this new hack exposing all Facetune users. Its not what you think. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6LsOUkAyNosT1oienuZbcL</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4064</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>32- Cat Fishing &amp; Confetti Cumshots</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7tgFEfeor76tN4TKwOap3T?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Do you know the 3 ways a guy orgasms? Introducing the Confetti Cumshot, the Warning Shot, and the Follow the Leader Cumshot. Also in the episode- Picking up a girl at the gym is NEVER okay, but if you must, we are telling you how to do it successfully ft. the water fountain aka watering hole. The girls have had it with the modern day catfishing on instagram, it's now gone too far and they are calling celebs out on their bullshit. If you have your tagged photos feature turned off, you're an IMPOSTER. Last but not least, the girls are screwing over airlines again-getting you guys drunk for free and introduce a new mind game to play in the bedroom.. that truly makes girls O harder than they ever have before.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7tgFEfeor76tN4TKwOap3T</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3863</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>31- You're Just a Hole</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1yUZCbTbBTI2POdAsHIxP0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls are discussing some hard truths- men only care about the face, people who only mention eye color are ugly, and their sexual history together. They also talk public sex…high school forced the girls to hook up in some WEIRD places, (church, tractor, Dick Sporting Goods Tent, etc.) Lastly, they analyze a phenomenon that will have girls cringing and men clapping- WHY WOMEN ASK MEN SHIT THEY KNOW WILL HURT THEIR FEELINGS (relayed by the worst offenders). And oh yeah, how to make condoms hot.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1yUZCbTbBTI2POdAsHIxP0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3461</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30- Sex Toys &amp; How to Not Catch Feelings</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0SW2sFSepDwCXOKRJHWksm?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>FINALLY, the girls get into sex toys- their favorites, how to use them, and when to introduce them in the bedroom. They also discuss the tricky art of how to not catch feelings…that works every time. They also discuss a new shady trend amongst sugar daddies (beware), couples that have joint instagram accounts, and a new blow job technique that involves TEETH. Bonus: how to catch your girl cheating...and it involves her toilet seat cleanliness Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0SW2sFSepDwCXOKRJHWksm</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4003</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>29- Why They Won't F*ck You</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6zKLvKE5ftWrloOGPlbX0G?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls are discussing the harsh reasons your boyfriend or girlfriend have stopped fucking you… always keeping it real on Call Her Daddy! They also explain how to take the perfect nude with detailed descriptions of their personal favorites, how dick pics can be sexy if done correctly, and talk about a new fetish that is as popular as it is disturbing, welcoming Party and Play porn. Lastly, they tell one of their most embarrassing stories together that took place on an airplane. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6zKLvKE5ftWrloOGPlbX0G</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3948</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>28- Finessing a Fuckboy (or girl)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5KaJUwueoDJbswafHoyqNP?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Alex and Sofia listened to another podcast..and want to apologize to their listeners in this week's episode. They also discuss a sex move they recently encountered that EVERY man should be doing to women- introducing the Mona Lisa. They also address plan B and faking pregnancies. Lastly, they discuss a huge trend in social media that needs to STOP and reveal an old internet hack that is pure gold (Hi Google).  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5KaJUwueoDJbswafHoyqNP</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5212</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>27- Our First Foursome.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6PA2OqresGYPcRInk6yPcl?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Attn: This episode is crazier than usual. Alex and Sofia recap Cabo, where they had Kylie Jenner's smoking hot body guard in tow…the one rumored to be Stormi's dad. They get into fingering the crazy out of a crazy girl and awkward sex (farts, pets, and death threats). They also talk missionary sex- which most of you are doing wrong, the New York slasher, and first date DONT'S for men. Lastly, Sofia gives us a personal story of a vengeful STD rumor. Yay!  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6PA2OqresGYPcRInk6yPcl</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4128</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26- Drunk Sex: Blackout Edition</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1MFJgWon8E8Zz5iYR1WFxb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Alex and Sofia reminisce on the days when they worked corporate jobs and somehow didn't get fired for their inappropriate behavior. They also break down a new strategy for men on how-to successfully transition from liking a girl's pics on IG to sliding into her (DMs). Lastly, they get into the horrors of drunk sex, Instagram famous frauds, and an amazing iPhone technology hack that will elevate and spice up your sexting game. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1MFJgWon8E8Zz5iYR1WFxb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3357</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25- Post D*ck Appointment Flashbacks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6ZzRWdWFk68x4x1va8vSdt?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls discuss their crazy weekend, as Alex traveled to see a man and Sofia headed back to her hometown. They also give men brilliant pointers regarding their Instagram picture game (including some huge instagram DONT'S) and introduce the rotisserie chicken move that all freaks needs to be using in the bedroom. Finally, Sofia tells a horror story of a past relationship as well as her complicated relationship with Kid Cudi. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ZzRWdWFk68x4x1va8vSdt</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3369</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24- Confessions of a Mistress</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7arh4TnjYBUxZIQd3WDVnD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In typical Call Her Daddy style, the girls unveil how to cheat or catch a cheater in 2019. They also get into high sex, provide a sure fire way to pick up girls at a bar, and expose a celebrity cheater- straight from the source herself. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7arh4TnjYBUxZIQd3WDVnD</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3895</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>23- Cuckolding, Everyone’s Doing It</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4SZt4DasVieGxW0FowTxvh?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls give us a technology hack to help you get away with murder or better yet, cheating! They also give some advice regarding texting response time, Instagram filters, and initiating sex. Finally, they discuss all things cuckolding and end the episode with the craziest #daddygang stories to date. Stay till the end.. you don't want to miss this.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4SZt4DasVieGxW0FowTxvh</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3536</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>22- Condom Poker</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5G6QFdu7ALnq7O7Bs4uRyH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls are here to discuss how to get over a breakup and introduce one of the riskiest games of poker ever played…condom poker. Watch out for STD's! They also get into the ‘double tap' feature on the iPhone and how you can use it to become a master manipulator. Last but definitely not least, the girls bring us a new sex tip to make sure your sex is hot and steamy and it involves flipping the bird. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5G6QFdu7ALnq7O7Bs4uRyH</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3379</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21 - Sex Tapes &amp; Cucumber Fun</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5afOpLn7f0hHg3X8Q9SDEY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On this weeks episode the girls reveal a crazy Vegas story including a cucumber and Rachel Bush takes to twitter once again to bash the girls. Also, Sofia has a GYNO appointment that goes terribly wrong, and the girls talk role play, flacid d****, and fake IG accounts. Last but not least, the girls come to the rescue to tell you what to get your significant other or fuck buddy for Valentines day!  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5afOpLn7f0hHg3X8Q9SDEY</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3218</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20- Butt Stuff</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3U42TjvxHmkaJlqhu3oAJN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls talk about everything butt related (including ass eating), the best way to pick up a guy at the bar, and finally explain what the hell happened when they were stood up by celebrity guest- Tana Mongeau.  They also address some #daddygang grievances, models turned DJs, and the ridiculousness of name dropping Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3U42TjvxHmkaJlqhu3oAJN</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3156</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>19 - Men, Talk Nasty to Us</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0UAWIa2E6Je3hNxqCgGaqq?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls give an update on their apartment and it includes a break in. They also address drunk snaps, thirst traps, and that promoter life. Finally they get into dirty talk for men, a man's O face, and Alex introduces a new sex technique...cue the 'chopsticks move'.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0UAWIa2E6Je3hNxqCgGaqq</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2902</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>18 - Facetime Sex &amp; Morning Head</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4MsfeHcwxTa2dpdfcwmf6m?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls get graphic as they give you yet another mind blowing blow job strategy and the hottest moves to nail the perfect FaceTime Sex. They also divulge one of their craziest stories from a trip they took to LA involving an A list celeb. PSA: Everyone should be putting #CallHerDaddy in their dating app bio. Listen to the episode to find out WHY. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4MsfeHcwxTa2dpdfcwmf6m</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3765</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17 - Daddy Girls’ Arrested and Kinky Fetishes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/74ZFEHWGOZSXyzWqTBhZrH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Sofia gives us crazy new details surrounding her arrest and the girls discuss the genitalia of the men in their office. They also get into some bizarre fetishes while outing their foot fetish stalker. They implement a new rule for Facetune, Instagram stories, and pictures with your ex.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74ZFEHWGOZSXyzWqTBhZrH</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2821</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16 - Double Penetration and a Happy New Year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4dGCcKZF67S0FeonAqqTtY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The duo is back for 2019 talking double penetration, girls faking nudes, and the BEST Instagram trick for guys to get laid. They also share on masturbating to a friend in the other room and introduce the term “soaking,” something near and dear to Sofia's heart. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4dGCcKZF67S0FeonAqqTtY</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2717</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BONUS EP - Meet Biznasty And His Uncircumcised Dick</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/10mnD9PAbZxEHE7GHhQglI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Biznasty talks squirters, flaps, and gets offended when the Daddy Girl's ask him to get naked in the studio. Enjoy!     Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10mnD9PAbZxEHE7GHhQglI</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1090</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 - Escaping the Friend Zone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/09WDtUjV8ZGTpAJKIETIig?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The girls get into masturbating and sharing toys. They also provide the blue print for men to escape the friend zone. Finally, they discuss the real life horror story that has become their neighborhood.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09WDtUjV8ZGTpAJKIETIig</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2517</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14 - Are We F***ing on a First Date?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3FpjvliTYW0dcYVUyENcE1?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Alex and Sofia have different opinions regarding sex on a first date. Shocker! And the pros and cons to both. Alex also discusses bringing a guy back to her ex-boyfriends apartment, and what would this episode be without some good ol' fashion talk about face f***ing.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3FpjvliTYW0dcYVUyENcE1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2685</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 - Let it Snow...it’s Time for a Facial</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/61dYcpsOKBNzCOwoSABV8R?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>With the Call Her Daddy Instagram page down…the girls go WILD in this weeks episode. They talk facials, hearing each other getting it on in the next room, and take notes people, they are getting uncomfortably graphic with how to talk dirty.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61dYcpsOKBNzCOwoSABV8R</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2408</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 - Ride it like an Equestrian</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7dmfyoLtzu07OO0ZIhQzcL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Alex and Sofia give a detailed description on riding D to the finish line- introducing the ‘Rocket' and the ‘Reverse Cyclone.' They revisit the ideal outfit for a guy, address going through your partners phone, and dive into their shadiest cheating scandal story to date. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7dmfyoLtzu07OO0ZIhQzcL</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2731</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 - MILF Hunting Season</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3K7IJY1s8ycVP43OAmNZZH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The duo explains how they faked their grandfathers death to get out of an airline fee. They provide multiple ways to finding a third for a threesome, get into a detailed strategy for hunting MILFs, and how to navigate that fuck buddy life if you want more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3K7IJY1s8ycVP43OAmNZZH</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2226</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10- Stop Nutting Early Please</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1fgSeBgKLY4N8vi7yLklPF?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We discuss our favorite topic which is how to out crazy the crazy. We also provide the four important steps for men to last longer in the bedroom along with sugar daddies and queefs. Enjoy! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fgSeBgKLY4N8vi7yLklPF</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2825</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 - Faking O’s and Threesomes-Oh My!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7MaZP06iTq905F15nFRPaZ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this weeks episode, the duo addresses their families disapproval of them and revisit the subject of nudes. They also discuss the hard truth about faking O's and everyone's favorite topic- threesomes-ending with some of the craziest #daddygang stories yet. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7MaZP06iTq905F15nFRPaZ</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2898</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 - Plot Twist- Small Dicks for the Win and Using Tears for Lube</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5TvqSSzN1cZucsfIswHZJh?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Alex and Sofia discuss manscaping, why Adriana Lima blocked Alex on instagram, period sex, and why small dicks are great. They also divulge their sexual love story and why they are done with girls blaming the other woman (cough cough Rachel Bush).  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5TvqSSzN1cZucsfIswHZJh</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1972</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 - Sliding into the DMs - It’s Time to Get Laid Boys</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2oosxKCVJ5622rqYfRNwpN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Alex and Sofia give men the ultimate guide to DM success and break down the do's and don'ts of their social media habits. They elaborate on dirty talk in the bedroom, and why girls with hair extension are an easy f**k Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2oosxKCVJ5622rqYfRNwpN</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2522</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 - The Post Nut Clean Up &amp; the Gluck Gluck continued...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3od1ewIyrhGwLKSZmxf1NF?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Alex and Sofia discuss the importance of the cleanup after he nuts, incorporating the balls and the butt in the Gluck Gluck, proper ghosting etiquette (we approve), AND Sofia's criminal history... Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3od1ewIyrhGwLKSZmxf1NF</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1897</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 - Fine Dining: An Eating Out Special (ft. The Cooch Gobbler Combo)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/14jMYx3gbhnEesASOUBYp2?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>You guys asked for it, we are giving it to you. Introducing the blow job special for girls- Cooch Gobbler Combo style. In Episode 5, Alex and Sofia reveal the ultimate way to land a girl at a bar, dish some celeb hookup stories, and give a detailed description of the power women hold between their legs- featuring the Voodoo Clam. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14jMYx3gbhnEesASOUBYp2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2040</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 - SEXT ME SO I KNOW IT’S REAL</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6WeScBow0GCkh4eCN0Uw9f?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Follow along vlogger Alexandra Cooper and best friend Sofia Franklyn as the duo dives into the explicit details of their life in NYC. In their 20s, the two exploit the f*ck out of their lives, making you feel a hell of alot better about yours. Relationships, sex, the NY social scene, embarassing moments, and weiner holes are all addressed here on CALL HER DADDY. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6WeScBow0GCkh4eCN0Uw9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2177</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 - If you’re a 5 or 6, Die for that D*ck</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/61Tbf5XAz2u3wpb1Rb1qlw?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Alex and Sofia dive into the differences between 5's and 6's vs 9's and 10's. Depending on where you land on the scale...you may need to work over time in the bedrooom. Plus, Sofia discusses getting caught cheating thanks to her fat a$$. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61Tbf5XAz2u3wpb1Rb1qlw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1714</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 - The Gluck Gluck 9000</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3hSbq89TaNnENs5BAe3253?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Alex and Sofia touch on making money from guys' foot fetishes (hey dirty coachella sandals!), secret sugar daddys, and the ultimate blow job technique that is guaranteed to be every man's krytopnite. Introducing- The Gluck Gluck 3000 vs 9000. LADIES AND GENTS, listen up! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3hSbq89TaNnENs5BAe3253</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1779</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 - Nudes Never Die</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0ze3ssUe3bYtTr8dHlgpxb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Alex and Sofia discuss sending nudes and an important technology hack they have discovered- one they guarentee will save the credibility and integrity of your nude. Also, they dive into the 'porn test challenge,' shaving your vagina at 3 am, and guys spitting on girls backs to fake an orgasm. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ze3ssUe3bYtTr8dHlgpxb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1711</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

