<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Dare to Lead with Brené Brown</title>
    <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/3oEPsPKDhPVoNNL7pH5db6</link>
    <description>Brené’s newest podcast is based on her book, Dare to Lead, which debuted at #1 on the New York Times, and Wall Street Journal bestseller lists, and has become the ultimate courage-building playbook for leaders at every level. Brené writes, “The Dare to Lead podcast will be a mix of solo episodes and conversations with change-catalysts, culture-shifters, and as many troublemakers as possible. Innovating, creating, and building a better, more just world, requires daring leadership in every part of our daily lives – from work to home to community. Together, we’ll have conversations that help us show up, step up, and dare to lead.” Dare to Lead is a Spotify Original from Parcast.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8ac42498b3560fb76c4a3c9841</url>
      <title>Dare to Lead with Brené Brown</title>
      <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/3oEPsPKDhPVoNNL7pH5db6</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:23:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Dr. Linda Hill on Leading With Purpose in the Digital Age</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4Qem4GKIW1hLgPtQCWmFmZ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I am talking to Dr. Linda Hill, a researcher, professor of business administration, and chair of the Leadership Initiative at Harvard Business School. She is regarded as one of the top experts on leadership and innovation, and she has done a new study on how to lead in the digital era. We talk about her findings and what leaders are wrestling with today, the qualities of a digitally mature organization, and why digital transformation is less about technology and more about people. We also talk about leading for innovation rather than leading for change. Our organization is definitely experiencing so much of this transformation, and this conversation was so clarifying as we move forward and lead with purpose. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4Qem4GKIW1hLgPtQCWmFmZ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3742</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Scott Sonenshein on Why We’ll Never Be the Same Again (and Why It’s Time to Talk About It)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/08u8NEqVoaYeSIePrOqiF9?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This is one of the most important conversations that we’ve ever had on the Dare to Lead podcast. I’m talking with Scott Sonenshein, a researcher, organizational psychologist, and New York Times best-selling author, about the pandemic, the racial reckoning, and work—specifically, what it means for people going to the office for the first time, or staying hybrid, or working from home. We will never be the same again after what we’ve experienced over the past couple of years, and it’s time we talk about how we’re going to rebuild moving forward. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08u8NEqVoaYeSIePrOqiF9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3333</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené and Barrett on Why Every Leader Needs to Worry About Toxic Culture</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6fij6ie7x0ET7F1fgsCcU0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Barrett and I have not been able to stop thinking—and talking—about an episode we did a few weeks ago with Donald Sull and Charlie Sull of CultureX: “How Toxic Work Cultures Are Driving the Great Resignation.” In that episode, we took a deep dive into an MIT Sloan Management Review article the Sulls had recently written, about what was driving the Great Resignation. In sharing their findings, they also gave us a sneak peek at a second article they had in the works, about the attributes of a toxic culture. That article has now been published, so in this episode, Barrett and I are digging into the research and talking about the five attributes of a toxic culture. It's so interesting to see how their findings compare to what we are seeing in organizations. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6fij6ie7x0ET7F1fgsCcU0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2118</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with James Rhee on Kindness, Math, and the Power of Goodwill</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/35lxab37aIQRIUJ1j6ULdx?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This is a conversation about how a simple act of generosity can put someone on a new, groundbreaking course. I’m talking with James Rhee—acclaimed impact leader, entrepreneur, educator, investor, and goodwill strategist—about why kindness matters. He leads with a powerful combination of kindness and math and demonstrates how revenue doesn’t define our lives. We unpack the power of goodwill—which is actually an accounting term—and how it affects many other things that we need to be thinking about. He also shares a number of tools, lenses, and music we should be considering as we define what success looks like for us and our organizations. This is a beautiful conversation that was an infusion of hope and possibility for me about the power of what we can be. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35lxab37aIQRIUJ1j6ULdx</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4045</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Dr. Amishi Jha on Finding Focus and Owning Your Attention</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4Lg7eUMHbMt2Neo5c6ReJa?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>I want you to pay attention and direct your flashlight right on this podcast—you’ll understand what that means after you listen to this episode. I’m talking to Dr. Amishi Jha, a neuroscientist and the author of the best-seller Peak Mind, about attention, focus, concentration, and mindfulness—specifically how mindfulness can literally change our levels of attention. This incredible conversation was a game changer for me. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4Lg7eUMHbMt2Neo5c6ReJa</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4438</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Dr. Donald Sull and Charlie Sull on How Toxic Work Cultures Are Driving the Great Resignation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3lqchNE10miAPNBU7A6IKW?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Get ready for one of the most powerful Dare to Lead episodes we’ve recorded, especially in terms of data. I’m talking with Dr. Donald Sull and Charlie Sull about an article I came across in the MIT Sloan Management Review titled “Toxic Culture Is Driving the Great Resignation.” As we know, between April and September of 2021, more than 24 million American employees left their jobs, an all-time record. Donald and Charlie researched what’s driving the Great Resignation. It is both revealing and confirming to hear how their research connects with the work that we do with Dare to Lead, and it is exactly what we’re seeing in companies all over at the world. We dig deep into the definition of toxic culture, how it shows up, and what it costs individuals and companies. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3lqchNE10miAPNBU7A6IKW</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4157</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Megan Reitz and John Higgins on Leading in an Age of Employee Activism</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2xXHfzoOfis3qQ74Bg3unv?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I’m talking to Megan Reitz, a professor of leadership and dialogue, and John Higgins, a researcher and author, about an article they published in the MIT Sloan Management Review titled “Leading in an Age of Employee Activism.” It’s a huge topic in every organization I talk to, and I can say, as an employer and an activist—leading a team filled with organizers and activists—that this is definitely an important issue. We talk about what it takes to make a difference, to do the internal work, and to give leaders the skills to lead with advocacy in the modern workplace. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2xXHfzoOfis3qQ74Bg3unv</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4256</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Debbie Millman on Why Design Matters</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4osFS16WON0H4KjG29sbsP?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I’m talking with the legendary Debbie Millman—designer, author, educator, curator, brand strategist, and host of the long-running, multi-award-winning podcast Design Matters—about her new book, Why Design Matters: Conversations With the World's Most Creative People. It’s a conversation about creativity with one of the most creative people in the business, where she answers a lot of direct questions like, What is good design? What are the politics of curation and how is it different from discernment? What gets in the way of a creative life? We also, of course, talk about shame and worthiness, and some of her answers are just incredible. I can’t wait for you to hear this. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4osFS16WON0H4KjG29sbsP</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4237</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Dan Pink on The Power of Regret</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2vKHXqiUN9rgmrJkDoscFi?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Dan Pink is one of my favorite researchers and writers. In this episode, we dig into one of my least favorite feelings (but one of my best teachers): regret. In his new book, The Power of Regret: How Looking Backward Moves Us Forward, Dan shares findings from two large studies on regret. It’s fascinating. One big takeaway: We have more regrets about the things we did NOT do than the things we did do. Both Dan and regret are great teachers—you’ll be glad you listened. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2vKHXqiUN9rgmrJkDoscFi</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4289</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené and Barrett on the Great Awkward</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1E2OsaHD6JllUl8mvtlOBD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We’re back! It’s 2022, and we’re all talking about “returning to the office” at some point. There are a lot of unknowns, and it’s going to be awkward. In this episode, Barrett and I discuss how our organization is going to gather again, as well as what we are seeing in companies across the country. We talk through a few of the toughest questions, debunk some “remote working” myths, and discuss what we’ve learned over the past two years. We’re calling the return to work the Great Awkward—it’s going to be weird and, at times, full-on cringey. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1E2OsaHD6JllUl8mvtlOBD</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2039</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with America Ferrera on Identity and Integrated Leadership, Part 2 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0Y5QRYUZQitSnnpaDBvVeo?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>My conversation with America Ferrera was so good that I didn’t want it to end, so here we are with the second episode with the renowned actor, director, producer, activist, and leader. We continued our discussion about the importance of integration and how transformative it can be to bring all of our identities to our leadership journey—and in the process, the conversation goes where really neither of us expected it to go. You’ll also hear that the Rapid Fire questions were not so rapid, but they are deep, burning, and fire! This is a special episode, and I'm glad you're here for us to listen and learn together. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0Y5QRYUZQitSnnpaDBvVeo</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2295</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with America Ferrera on Identity and Integrated Leadership, Part 1 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2VHppaYWIEw9LWPP5Ikv61?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I’m talking with America Ferrera—actor, director, producer, activist, and leader—in the first of a two-part series about leading with your whole self. I have done a lot of work with integration and leadership over the past decades, and I hadn’t heard it so clearly captured and explained as America did in this episode. Every transformational leader that I've ever worked with refuses to compartmentalize who they are, and America has profoundly, publicly, and professionally integrated her identity into her process and her presence to create real change. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2VHppaYWIEw9LWPP5Ikv61</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2390</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Dr. Laurie Santos on Creating Meaningful Connection at Work</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3mVJ8JbqZqo7z5Uikk1ZWo?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I’m talking to Dr. Laurie Santos, professor of psychology and Head of Silliman Residential College at Yale University and the host of the popular podcast, The Happiness Lab. We talk about her experiences with university students and how it connects with the research that I’ve done for my new book Atlas of the Heart. We discuss how that data predicts what we can expect when we return to the workplace, as well as evidence-based strategies for how we can use this moment to create and cultivate meaningful connection at work. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3mVJ8JbqZqo7z5Uikk1ZWo</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3307</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with James Clear on Atomic Habits, Part 2 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7yizll01yfsBY5iOQztpkd?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>It’s part 2 of our two-part episode with James Clear author of Atomic Habits, which has sold more than 5 million copies worldwide and been translated into more than 50 languages. In part 1 of our series, we talk about building systems to create habits, and in this episode, we talk about how and why habits are atomic and how to build a habit or break a habit. We also look at our environments and how we can tweak them to support the habits we want to have, and then dive in and talk about organization habits and how we create habits in a team and in organizations. I took multiple pages of notes on this memorable conversation on forming habits that last. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7yizll01yfsBY5iOQztpkd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3278</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with James Clear on Atomic Habits, Part 1 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1FCDXnrrXo9d7VTTX7bi4E?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Even before James Clear and I met, I knew this would be a two-part series. I just had so many questions for the author of Atomic Habits, which has sold more than 5 million copies worldwide and has been translated into more than 50 languages. Not surprisingly, this turned out to be exactly the type of conversation I’d anticipated. In part 1 of our series, we talk specifically about developing identity-based habits and how we can become the architects of those habits, not the victims of them. We also talk about the intersection of his work and mine, the collective stories we make up, and how our mindsets and our systems can set us up for success. It was so meaningful to finally meet James, to hear his story, and to take in his insights into how he developed such a deep understanding of the importance of consistency over intensity when it comes to forming habits that last. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1FCDXnrrXo9d7VTTX7bi4E</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2991</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Dr. Maya Shankar on Courage in the Midst of Change</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1h1v36jum1GU94tE2hvYQK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I am talking with Dr. Maya Shankar, a cognitive scientist who served as chair of the Social and Behavioral Science Team during the Obama administration and as the first behavioral science adviser to the United Nations. We talk about what happens when change knocks us off our charted path. How do we get back up? How do we figure out who we are without that path? And how do we start building a new way to walk through the world? Join us as we connect on all these questions and more in this meaningful conversation about the science behind change, how change affects our identities, and what it means for the way we live, love, and lead. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1h1v36jum1GU94tE2hvYQK</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4371</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené and Barrett on BRAVING Trust, Part 2 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5XzGGv7kji91Hfhs7FbGnN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Barrett is back to talk more about trust and how we approach it at our company. We call it BRAVING trust—BRAVING is the acronym we use for the seven attributes of trust. And in part 2 of this two-part series, we really dig into the core elements of BRAVING: boundaries, reliability, accountability, vault, integrity, nonjudgment, and generosity. We talk frankly about awareness, experiences, and hacks that we have found to be helpful in cultivating trust, and we get really personal about how all of these BRAVING elements show up in our own lives and leadership. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5XzGGv7kji91Hfhs7FbGnN</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2886</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené and Barrett on BRAVING Trust, Part 1 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3gJqM6Tw5t3rVcfypvV39R?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, Barrett Guillen, Chief of Staff at Brené Brown Education and Research Group, is joining me to talk about trust, what trust means, and how we approach it at our company. We call it BRAVING trust---BRAVING is the acronym we use for the seven attributes of trust. We have shared this with organizations all over the world, and today we're going to dig into what we've learned about practicing BRAVING trust, what we've learned from teaching it, and what we've learned from the barriers that we often see in our training and in our practice. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3gJqM6Tw5t3rVcfypvV39R</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2352</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Liz Wiseman on Impact Players</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3DUXemFbKXo1zTTxtI0nnJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I’m talking with Liz Wiseman, author, researcher, and executive adviser about her new book Impact Players: How to Take the Lead, Play Bigger, and Multiply Your Impact. Liz has done research across organizations around the world, talking to managers about what impact players look like, what sets them apart, and how they contribute. With this research, she gives us language to recognize the attributes of an impact player and to grow those characteristics in our own lives to make our work and our impact more fulfilling. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3DUXemFbKXo1zTTxtI0nnJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4134</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Jodi-Ann Burey and Ruchika Tulshyan on Imposter Syndrome</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2RGICGdqwdTVlD8N472qzh?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I’m talking with Jodi-Ann Burey and Ruchika Tulshyan about imposter syndrome and the articles they have written together on the topic, including “Stop Telling Women They Have Imposter Syndrome,” which is among the Harvard Business Review’s top 100 most-read articles in history. We talk about the contexts in which imposter syndrome was originally defined, as well as how it continues to be defined and experienced. We also talk about how the problematic myths, required masks, and systemic mindsets connected with the term and how they directly work against creating a culture of belonging. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2RGICGdqwdTVlD8N472qzh</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4217</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Charles Feltman on Trust: Building, Maintaining, and Restoring It</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/60RPcjZaENorfqwWOX0Jlk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I’m talking to Charles Feltman, author of The Thin Book of Trust: An Essential Primer for Building Trust at Work, which is based on his nearly three decades of work with individuals and teams to build, maintain, and restore trust. I have used his definitions of trust and distrust in every book I've written, because they are practical and actionable, and, at the same time, deep and meaningful. It was important to me to dig into these definitions and explore how they play out at work, in relationships, and in our everyday lives. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60RPcjZaENorfqwWOX0Jlk</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3236</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Barrett Guillen on the Hardest Feedback I’ve Ever Received, Part 2 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/58iYEfKV11Xw1mzba8WR1R?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This episode is the second of a two-part series on feedback, and Barrett is back to take it to the next level and dig in to engaged feedback with me. As you know, Barrett is Chief of Staff for Brené Brown Education and Research Group and one of my sisters, and together, we go through the eleven elements of the Engaged Feedback Checklist. It’s a super practical tool, and we talk about the real and tangible ways it’s changed the way we approach giving feedback and leading tough conversations. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58iYEfKV11Xw1mzba8WR1R</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2334</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Barrett Guillen on The Hardest Feedback I’ve Ever Received, Part 1 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2UhaEjLNsI2P1fsDych1QH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This episode is the first of a two-part series on feedback, and I’m talking with my sister Barrett Guillen, Chief of Staff for Brené Brown Education and Research Group, about professional feedback. We get very honest about the feedback that we have received over the years, as well as how it felt, what we've tried to do about it, where we slip up, and where we've made strides. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2UhaEjLNsI2P1fsDych1QH</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2686</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Amy Cuddy on Pandemic Flux Syndrome</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1TLBltRKU6v8xzCcsaNZ4u?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week I’m talking to Dr. Amy Cuddy, social psychologist, best-selling author, award-winning Harvard lecturer, and expert on the behavioral science of power, presence, and prejudice. We discuss her recently published Washington Post article, “Why This Stage of the Pandemic Makes Us So Anxious,” and how working through this collective, constant pandemic flux affects us as individuals and as leaders. We also talk about developing a flux mindset and how important it is to facilitate a sense of agency as we make decisions about how we return to work. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1TLBltRKU6v8xzCcsaNZ4u</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3814</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dare to Lead Programming Note</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3JnFzsxDZKSz1YCNynLRfN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Barrett is here today with a note to let you know that Brené is still heads down under a book deadline, so we’re going to take a few more weeks off from Dare to Lead. We hope this a good opportunity for you to catch up on episodes from Brené’s two podcasts-- Dare to Lead and Unlocking Us -- because we have some really excellent new episodes coming this Fall that you’ll want to be ready for. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3JnFzsxDZKSz1YCNynLRfN</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>156</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Charles Duhigg on Habits and Productivity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0VULjc8uCCUTUdKBoTGxgj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, as I’m writing a book and thinking about habits that are getting in my way of being more productive, I call upon Charles Duhigg, who is a New York Times bestselling author on habits and productivity with The Power of Habit and Smarter Faster Better: The Secrets of Being Productive in Life and Business. We talk about how we are in an interesting time to think big picture about what we’re doing well and what we’d like to work on, and what he believes is the “greatest productivity app” that we can all access for free. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0VULjc8uCCUTUdKBoTGxgj</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5433</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Priya Parker: A Meeting Makeover</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5Ky8LCMrZYY77CZzFn6Tcw?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This episode is the second of a two-part series with Priya Parker, master facilitator, strategic advisor, and the author of The Art of Gathering: How We Meet and Why it Matters. We hold a weekly meeting in our organization that doesn't seem to be serving everyone in a consistent way, so Priya helps me figure out what's going on and why. It's a tough and vulnerable conversation. And, exactly what I needed. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5Ky8LCMrZYY77CZzFn6Tcw</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4007</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Priya Parker on How We Return and Why It Matters, Part 1 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2zHey9HxjX4HSCgGr0rVUG?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Join me for Part 1 of a two-part series with Priya Parker on gathering together again. Priya is a master facilitator, strategic advisor, and the author of The Art of Gathering: How We Meet and Why It Matters. We talk about the real, big and small challenges we’ll see when we return to workspaces, the need we’ll have to use our creativity and ingenuity to figure out how to be together, and the opportunity we’ll get to ask how we can be together better. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2zHey9HxjX4HSCgGr0rVUG</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3772</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Patrice Gordon on Reverse Mentorship</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1oBZnRqBZ1ZYda9fYPOFHL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week I’m talking with Patrice Gordon about reverse mentorship, a practice that sets up a junior team member, often a member of an underrepresented group, to mentor senior staff. Patrice did a TED talk last fall on how reverse mentorship can help create better leaders, and I loved the approach. We talk through best practices and how to set up a program that provides psychological safety for individuals and for the organization. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1oBZnRqBZ1ZYda9fYPOFHL</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3064</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Doug Conant on Finding &amp; Telling Your Leadership Story</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/30elYlQiSV03LUiU5mzFwF?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week I’m talking with Doug Conant, the only former Fortune 500 CEO who is a New York Times best-selling author, a Top 50 Leadership Innovator, a Top 100 Leadership Speaker, and one of the 100 Most Influential Authors in the World. We talk about the principles and practices in the new book he co-authored with Amy Federman, The Blueprint: 6 Practical Steps to Lift Your Leadership to New Heights, as well as how to create an entourage of excellence, how to find our individual leadership stories, and how to bring those stories to life. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30elYlQiSV03LUiU5mzFwF</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4345</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Michael Bungay Stanier on The Advice Trap and Staying Curious Just a Little Longer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4CrIqIUZphQfjfUbOE4Suh?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week I’m talking with Michael Bungay Stanier, author of six books, including The Coaching Habit and The Advice Trap. We talk about taming our Advice Monsters - you know, that insatiable thing that fuels our need to offer advice and answers when curiosity and good questions are way more powerful. We also share a very vulnerable, impromptu role play, where I ask him for help on a real issue that I'm struggling with at work, and he models incredible coaching and curiosity. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4CrIqIUZphQfjfUbOE4Suh</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4104</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Dr. Angela Duckworth on Grit and the Importance of Trying New Things</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5zrRTA8BU4AUJm5qgW8Xwv?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week I’m talking to Dr. Angela Duckworth, professor, founder and CEO of Character Lab, and author of Grit: The Power of Passion and Perseverance. We dig into what grit is, but also what grit is not. We talk about taking the windy path, the danger of oversimplifying complex ideas, and why ruling out what does NOT bring you joy is part of finding what does. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5zrRTA8BU4AUJm5qgW8Xwv</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4262</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené on Armored versus Daring Leadership, Part 2 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2QTUy1OkJ5v4LM7zScecLO?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This is Part 2 of our two-part series on daring leadership, where I unpack four more common types of armor that we use to self-protect when we're in fear. These barriers include creating a fitting-in culture versus a belonging culture; fostering a scarcity-based culture versus modeling that we are enough and have enough; leading reactively versus leading strategically; and resisting change versus accepting and embracing change. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2QTUy1OkJ5v4LM7zScecLO</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1817</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené on Armored versus Daring Leadership, Part 1 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4Oo3T5ryR3i005ocQwtkyB?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The greatest barrier to daring leadership is not fear; the greatest barrier is armor, or how we self-protect when we're in fear. This is Part I of a two-part series, where I unpack the most common types of armor, including being a knower versus being a learner, tapping out of hard conversation versus skilling up and leaning in, and using shame and blame to manage others versus using accountability and empathy. Join me for a conversation that includes real examples and actionable strategies about how we can dare to lead. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4Oo3T5ryR3i005ocQwtkyB</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2371</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Dr. Pippa Grange on Fearing Less</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/10Xj93VCNNvioiivCNFg1f?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This episode feels like a conversation with an old friend who happens to be an expert on fear, anxiety, and perfectionism. Pippa is a highly sought-after sports psychologist, culture coach, and author of the bestselling book, Fear Less: How to Win at Life Without Losing Yourself.  As Head of People and Team Development at The Football Association, she worked closely with the England team for the World Cup in 2018 (remember when they finally broke that penalty kick curse?). Join us as we talk about what it means to live with an open heart versus clenched fists. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10Xj93VCNNvioiivCNFg1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4543</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Emily and Amelia Nagoski on Burnout and How to Complete the Stress Cycle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5n3wvqU0Tt9eKWAZZX9Vww?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Dare to Lead is Unlocking Us this week about burnout. We’re all experiencing it and we’re all desperate for a way through it. In this episode, I talk to Drs. Emily and Amelia Nagoski about what causes burnout, what it does to our bodies, and how we can move through the emotional exhaustion. This has been a game-changer for me and for my family! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5n3wvqU0Tt9eKWAZZX9Vww</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3829</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Emmanuel Acho on Uncomfortable Conversations with a Black Man</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7IZHKzX1opwipOzG45i9R7?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Dare to Lead is Unlocking Us! In this episode, I talk with Emmanuel Acho, creator, host, and producer of Uncomfortable Conversations with a Black Man, a web series about racism to drive open and uncomfortable dialogue. His book with the same name is a thoughtful manifesto, a mandate, and a playbook that’s both generous and full of love. We get personal, and we talk about what these important questions mean in context of history and for culture today. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7IZHKzX1opwipOzG45i9R7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3598</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Dr. Susan David on The Dangers of Toxic Positivity, Part 2 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0x2Le3owpM5QMsNPPwwmHL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This is part two of my conversation with Dr. Susan David, author of the bestselling book, Emotional Agility: Get Unstuck, Embrace Change, and Thrive in Work and Life. In part one, we talked about how emotional granularity and agility benefit us as leaders. This episode is another fun "emotions researcher extravaganza!" Susan and I talk about how to build emotionally agile teams, how to lead from a place of awareness, and the power of the choice that we can find in the space between stimulus and response. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0x2Le3owpM5QMsNPPwwmHL</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3132</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Dr. Susan David on the Dangers of Toxic Positivity, Part 1 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2TS6yDEPmQREcCWdnHz9IG?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week I’m talking to Dr. Susan David, author of the bestselling book, Emotional Agility: Get Unstuck, Embrace Change, and Thrive in Work and Life. This is a full-on emotion researcher geek out on how emotional granularity and agility benefit us as individuals and as leaders. It's such a good conversation that we made it into two episodes, and this is part one. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2TS6yDEPmQREcCWdnHz9IG</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3883</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Veronica and Miguel Garza on Food, Family, and Scaling a Business</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7oeKlrAUw9JYCVpfLRC7ul?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>You can’t spell podcast without tacos. I'm talking to Veronica and Miguel Garza, the co-founders of Siete Family Foods, a family-owned Mexican American food brand of heritage-inspired products. Their story is one of family, love, tenacity, and how you build a successful company that is fueled by authenticity and servant leadership to make food approved by abuelas everywhere. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7oeKlrAUw9JYCVpfLRC7ul</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4476</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Adam Grant on the Power of Knowing What You Don’t Know</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/683bEXlSWMNSU3oQ26UXIL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>It's a total geek-out, nerd-fest conversation with my friend Adam Grant about his new book Think Again: The Power of Knowing What You Don't Know. Adam weaves together research and storytelling to help us build the intellectual and emotional muscle we need to stay curious enough about the world to actually change it. This is such an important book for the world we live in today. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">683bEXlSWMNSU3oQ26UXIL</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5117</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Aiko Bethea on Creating Transformative Cultures</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7K47gQF5Ruc7MAXxENq6jI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This is Part Two of my conversation with Aiko Bethea, friend, colleague, and Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion expert. We take the foundations from our first conversation and build upon them with strategic and sustainable action items that we can take to create non-reactive, intentional, accountable, and transformational change. It’s a masterclass in the power of integration and the importance of a learning mindset. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7K47gQF5Ruc7MAXxENq6jI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4443</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Chad Sanders on What Black Leaders Learned from Trauma and Triumph</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7pbvwKiBckfcvSf6Fd0iVT?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>A heartfelt and honest conversation with writer, creator and former tech entrepreneur, Chad Sanders on Black Magic: What Black Leaders Learned from Trauma and Triumph. Chad shares his stories and interviews from fifteen leaders across industries on transformative leadership. There are critical teachings here for all of us - in fact, it's our organization’s first group read of 2021. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7pbvwKiBckfcvSf6Fd0iVT</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4529</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Dr. Sarah Lewis on Creativity, Surrender, and Aesthetic Force</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5nlFwMOk61e9xAOOLmFQoq?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Join me for Part II of a conversation with one of my favorite thinkers and writers, Dr. Sarah Lewis. We’re talking about her book, The Rise: Creativity, the Gift of Failure and the Search for Mastery. I first talked to Sarah on our November 30th episode about the creative process and the difference between mastery and success, but the conversation was so thought provoking, that we had to record a second episode. This time we talk about the impact of protecting creative time and the power of surrender. We also talk about aesthetic force and the role of imagery in creating change. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5nlFwMOk61e9xAOOLmFQoq</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4288</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Simon Sinek on Developing an Infinite Mindset</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/33e8nzO5QcYAor2JrO0aNn?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I’m talking with Simon Sinek, visionary thinker, speaker and the author of multiple best-selling books, about his latest book The Infinite Game. We talk about finding our why, the infinite mindset versus the finite mindset, and five essential and super actionable practices of infinite thinkers and infinite leaders. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33e8nzO5QcYAor2JrO0aNn</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4806</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Kevin Oakes on Cultural Renovation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0YFqo5j8bRHa55gqxFgMMY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I’m talking with Kevin Oakes, the head of the world’s leading HR research firm, the Institute for Corporate Productivity, about his new book Culture Renovation: 18 Leadership Actions to Build an Unshakeable Company. The best playbooks are a combination of reliable research, relatable examples, and actionable strategies. And this is the best playbook I’ve seen when it comes to creating organizational cultures that create competitive advantage, unlock performance, and rehumanize work. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0YFqo5j8bRHa55gqxFgMMY</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4874</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Jim Collins on Curiosity, Generosity, and the Hedgehog</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6fjipwsohxCpKUD8r2vIIL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This episode is a two-hour, deep-dive conversation with Jim Collins on his work and how it shaped who I am as a person, as a leader, and as a researcher. We talk about our values, our shadow values, the power of curiosity, decades of grounded theory research and comparative analysis, and how he explains thirty years of research with one integrated framework called The Map. Jim's books, including his new one, Beyond Entrepreneurship 2.0, have captured the hearts and minds of his readers and changed how we think about building and leading organizations. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6fjipwsohxCpKUD8r2vIIL</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7763</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with President Barack Obama on Leadership, Family and Service</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1d1AI5Fsrn3mAdetQEe8iL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I talk with President Barack Obama about his life, his work, and his new book A Promised Land. We dive into the power of leaning into uncertainty, and why the rare skill of holding the tension of opposites makes us better leaders, partners, and parents. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d1AI5Fsrn3mAdetQEe8iL</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3602</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Dr. Sarah Lewis on The Rise, the Creative Process and the Difference Between Mastery and Success</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/002OXyawiR8K1imFEivJsm?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Join me for a conversation with Dr. Sarah Lewis for Part I of a two-part series on her book, The Rise: Creativity, the Gift of Failure and the Search for Mastery. We talk about why the word “failure” doesn’t quite capture the often-transformative experience of falling and beginning again, the difference between success and mastery, and the power of setting audacious goals that are right outside our grasp. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">002OXyawiR8K1imFEivJsm</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3199</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Eric Mosley on Making Work Human</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2lrHMtKQQtJECVWcDSuudd?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I talk with Eric Mosley, CEO and co-founder of Workhuman, about his new book, Making Work Human: How Human-Centered Companies are Changing the Future of Work and the World. His transformative work is based on 50 million data points and is leading the charge to dismantle old HR processes and challenge organizations to build new ways to connect the modern workforce. This is data with a heart and research with a goal to rehumanize. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2lrHMtKQQtJECVWcDSuudd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3360</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Guy Raz on How I Built This</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6z4YweMcQYDIEc5RqHTEaC?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I talk with Guy Raz, the creator and host of the popular podcasts How I Built This, Wisdom from the Top and The Rewind. Guy and I dig into the importance of an entrepreneurial mindset, what gets in the way of innovation, and the transformative power of story. I think his new book, HOW I BUILT THIS: The Unexpected Paths to Success From the World's Most Inspiring Entrepreneurs should be mandatory reading in business schools - it's an incredible playbook! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6z4YweMcQYDIEc5RqHTEaC</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3508</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Aiko Bethea on Inclusivity at Work: The Heart of Hard Conversations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3IODQ37EurkFf0zMNhazqI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I talk to friend, colleague and Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion expert, Aiko Bethea. We discuss empathy, accountability, and the power of listening and believing (including a very real role play). We also dissect the differences between transactional leadership and transformational leadership, and why courage is a prerequisite to lasting, meaningful change. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3IODQ37EurkFf0zMNhazqI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2812</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Jon Meacham on the Soul of America</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1HMThOBdjVcnS2Q7pG8QKk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I talk to Pulitzer Prize–winning historian Jon Meacham about what history can teach us about leading through crises and deep political divides. We discuss the importance of humility, candor, and how our history reflects the ongoing fight between our better angels and our worst instincts. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1HMThOBdjVcnS2Q7pG8QKk</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3825</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Abby Wambach on the New Rules of Leadership</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0eRgnFdCcK93WNhzd6e9EL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I connect with Olympian, activist and author Abby Wambach on the new rules of leadership. Her book WOLFPACK, I kid you not, is on my top five must-read leadership books. I buy this book for everyone. It’s leadership gold. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0eRgnFdCcK93WNhzd6e9EL</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4023</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Heart of Daring Leadership</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4bUbBHpdBonWxoKtVZGee1?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this first solo episode of the Dare to Lead podcast, I talk about my passion for this work, what we're learning about courageous leadership and skill building, and the differences between armored and daring leadership. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4bUbBHpdBonWxoKtVZGee1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2484</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dare to Lead Podcast with Brené Brown Trailer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2xefzw7nooPEOqdEgfNfUX?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Brené’s newest podcast is based on her book, Dare to Lead, which debuted at #1 on the New York Times, and Wall Street Journal bestseller lists, and has become the ultimate courage-building playbook for leaders at every level. Brené writes, “The Dare to Lead podcast will be a mix of solo episodes and conversations with change-catalysts, culture-shifters, and as many troublemakers as possible. Innovating, creating, and building a better, more just world, requires daring leadership in every part of our daily lives – from work to home to community. Together, we’ll have conversations that help us show up, step up, and dare to lead.” Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2xefzw7nooPEOqdEgfNfUX</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>123</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

