<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Deathbed Confessions</title>
    <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/7uJesNgQL4E3r60Rl1Bsfo</link>
    <description>Imagine living with a secret so big, if anyone were to find out, it would change everything. From illicit affairs and fake identities to heists and murder — do you think you could take a secret like that to the grave? Every week, discover the most explosive things people have admitted to moments before the end. Deathbed Confessions is a Spotify Original from Parcast.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8aa4b585eba979afeade869cec</url>
      <title>Deathbed Confessions</title>
      <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/7uJesNgQL4E3r60Rl1Bsfo</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:34:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Man Who Hid From Justice: Christopher Smith</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3Np9mRSA4giHrJXQRh1Mz9?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In Preston, a city tucked away in the North of England, the brutal murder of a young sex worker sparks terror that a violent killer is on the loose. But although DNA and blood samples are left on her body, forensic testing is too basic to match any suspects — so the murderer, Christopher Smith, escapes. He leads a peaceful life surrounded by family until, just 6 days before his death, police arrest him for driving while drunk. Smith leaves a guilty deathbed confession that will finally re-open the unsolved murder case and question how police let a deadly criminal slip through their grasp for so long. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3Np9mRSA4giHrJXQRh1Mz9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2622</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Brabant Killers: Christiaan Bonkoffsky Pt. 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/29SgDaNNhAbUWiC2H6l3qu?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The Brabant Killers had the country of Belgium living in fear in the early eighties. They robbed and killed with little regard for their victims. After eighteen months of chasing them, police had little to show in the way of suspects, and conspiracy theories abounded that suggested the killers might even come from their own ranks. But things were about to get a whole lot worse. Everything that has happened so far was merely a warm-up by comparison to the fresh wave of violence the gang was about to unleash.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29SgDaNNhAbUWiC2H6l3qu</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2558</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Brabant Killers: Christiaan Bonkoffsky Pt. 1</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6XiAMbhBWpaGiIfEz8bAfs?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Belgium in the 1980s was divided in so many ways, but one thing citizens had in common was a fear of a group of spree killers known as the Brabant Killers. A gang of three unknown men targeted supermarkets, and thought nothing of leaving bodies littered behind them. Were these men common criminals out for a fast buck? Or could there be any truth to the rumors that members of law Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6XiAMbhBWpaGiIfEz8bAfs</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1861</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guilty Until Proven Innocent: Michael Lee Wilson</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0KXlr0sD6sqX4alI2I5ZeU?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In 1994 in the city of Tulsa, a 19-year-old is murdered when she’s caught in a gang crossfire. Police investigate and find the weapon on Michael Lee Wilson, but instead of arresting him, they frame two innocent teenagers. While they suffer behind bars, Wilson is on death row for another murder. He uses his final hours to tell the true story about what happened that fatal day. The case is retried, and new evidence is given to try to understand why police sent two innocent people to prison. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0KXlr0sD6sqX4alI2I5ZeU</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2502</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood in the Streets: Ianto Parker</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5e5rh5U3yqy0tdqerikvKl?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In 1874, a Methodist minister traveling in Pennsylvania is called to the bedside of a dying man. Ianto Parker tells the minister how he came to America from Wales in 1831, after taking part in a violent riot in which around 24 people died. For more than forty years, Parker has been haunted by what happened that day. He is desperate to confess a shameful secret that forced him to flee his native land. He escaped British justice once, but soon, he believes, he will have to face divine judgment. The time has come to unburden his soul. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e5rh5U3yqy0tdqerikvKl</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2466</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder or Hallucination?: James Washington</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3CVRxEe5yyPQ4LodeipXQk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In 1995 Joyce Goodener was brutally murdered, her body rolled up in a rug and set on fire. The police were desperate to find her killer, but the case went cold in less than a month. Twelve years later, when Nashville, Tennessee convict James Washington begins to experience chest pains, he is rushed to the local hospital. Afraid to take what he knows to the grave, his deathbed confession reopens Goodener’s investigation…but is Washington’s confession the truth or the result of drug-induced hallucinations? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3CVRxEe5yyPQ4LodeipXQk</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2099</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian Gangster: Mark “Chopper” Read Pt. 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5bqc3TvtEoqpelytEQZG8N?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>After decades in prison, Mark Read vows to go straight. He swaps bullets for words, becoming an author, a musician, even having his life story hit the silver screen. But old habits die hard. Read was never far from trouble, bouncing back in and out of jail. For every offense he’s convicted of, he’s suspected of a dozen more. Some of these he denies outright, some appear as stories in his books. The tales he saves for the end call everything that’s come before into question. We already knew he was a bad man – but there’s no doubt, his last performance is his most explosive. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5bqc3TvtEoqpelytEQZG8N</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2174</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian Gangster: Mark “Chopper” Read Pt. 1</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6DMAXuxDz53gxQAD3vUgVU?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Mark “Chopper” Read was one of the most feared criminals in Australia in his day. A man who shocked even fellow criminals with his brutality. He preyed on anyone who earned a dishonest living, serving time in one of the country’s toughest prisons for everything from assault to arson. The one thing they never pinned on him was murder, despite him being suspected of as many as nineteen, and acquitted of one. Read was a natural storyteller, and as it turns out, he saved his best stories till last. In a shocking series of confessions on national television just weeks before his death, he opens up old wounds on not one, but four killings. But was this just another of his tales, or has Read pulled the wool over the eyes of Australian police for over forty years? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6DMAXuxDz53gxQAD3vUgVU</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1925</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sins of the Father: Alexander Gartshore</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0YDrRzqk3NIWR8dFiv816U?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In the sleepy town of Coatbridge, Scotland a little girl named Moira Anderson disappears during a snowstorm. Police hunt for her abductor, but no culprit is ever found. Decades later, a local woman begins to suspect her father, Alexander Gartshore, of the crime, and starts unraveling a conspiracy that goes straight to the top. But the only way she can prove it is to get her aging father to confess his crimes on his deathbed. Can she succeed where police have failed? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0YDrRzqk3NIWR8dFiv816U</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2619</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Liverpool Librarian: Harvey Richardson</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7MLw0nXtuPCx2cw0D9pumR?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Any murder is difficult for a family to come to terms with, let alone a cold case that drags on for decades. Lorraine Jacob was only nineteen when she was found dead in a Liverpool alley back in 1970. No arrests were ever made and police didn’t even have a main suspect. While her family was left to grieve, a quiet family man named Harvey Richardson held onto a secret — one he kept for almost forty years. One that, when revealed, could be the key to giving Lorraine, and her family, the peace they all deserve. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7MLw0nXtuPCx2cw0D9pumR</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1951</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roswell Revealed: Walter Haut Pt. 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6pGooCmMMbGMlEcGYiaeb4?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>For years, an army of conspiracy theorists probed and prodded the army’s official explanation for the debris they found outside Roswell. It’s hard to prove anything when you’re up against a machine as big as the U.S. military. But as the years go by, something shifts. The men who were on the base back then start to open up. Share details they’ve kept close all these years. None more so than First Lieutenant Walter Haut. The words he wrote before he died might just be the sledgehammer that cracks open one of the biggest conspiracy theories of all time. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6pGooCmMMbGMlEcGYiaeb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2376</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roswell Revealed: Walter Haut Pt. 1</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1PelwKyzl1ziaXmxsGJcYk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>After something crashed to Earth on a remote cattle ranch in Roswell, the Army declared they’d recovered debris from a downed flying saucer — only to u-turn 24 hours later. The man who issued those press releases was First Lieutenant Walter Haut. He was one of a select group of men who attended closed briefings… Who saw the debris… Who for years after, would say very little on the matter. But Haut did have opinions of his own. Ones he has recorded in a sealed affidavit, only to be released after his death. And if true, what he has to say could paint the Roswell incident in a very different light. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1PelwKyzl1ziaXmxsGJcYk</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1784</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunted in the Outback: Ivan Milat Pt. 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3rlWULRE7P5pMIywucmn2U?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In 1993, the remains of more missing backpackers were found in the Belanglo Forest. Despite an overwhelming amount of leads, police were unable to find the killer — until Ivan Milat’s only surviving victim, Paul Onions, came forward and positively identified him. Ivan Milat finally got his day in court, but he and his family claimed his innocence. In 2019, Australian police continued to try and get a deathbed confession from Ivan before he succumbed to terminal cancer. But it appeared less likely with each passing day that the sadistic killer would finally give his victims’ families the closure they so desperately need. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3rlWULRE7P5pMIywucmn2U</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2327</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunted in the Outback: Ivan Milat Pt. 1</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1Lnx2U8bPlhnGTF6tRhqht?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In the late 1980s and early 1990s, a spate of young backpackers began going missing in the Australian outback. Their families' pleas for help fell on deaf ears until the gruesome discovery of their remains was found deep within the Belanglo Forest. The crimes are pinned on serial killer Ivan Milat in 1996 but he never confessed to any of the murders despite irrefutable evidence. In May 2019, as Milat lay dying of terminal cancer, police raced against the clock to elicit a deathbed confession. Will Milat finally give the victims’ families closure? Or continue to toy with them? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1Lnx2U8bPlhnGTF6tRhqht</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1879</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pockmarked Killer: Francois Verove</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7FQ4MQz973hDvyM0YnHg3s?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>For a decade, a man known only as the Pockmarked Killer terrorized women and children in and around Paris. Despite police having witnesses, a detailed description, and even his DNA, he remained at large; a ghost. Then, as suddenly as he’d burst onto the scene, he simply stopped. Was he dead, or in prison? For thirty-five years, his photo-fit is pinned to the wall in police headquarters, mocking investigators. It isn’t until officers follow up a routine missing persons report that they find the answers they’ve been looking for in a note left beside a body, and the Pockmarked killer, a man who has hidden in plain sight all his life, is finally unmasked. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7FQ4MQz973hDvyM0YnHg3s</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2015</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smalltown Secrets: Sharron Diane Crawford Smith</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2RycTkfN6QBKQ87379oxge?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In 1967, the murders of 20-year-old Carolyn Hevener Perry and her sister-in-law, 19-year-old Constance Smootz Hevener, at an ice cream shop confounded the citizens of Staunton, Virginia, for years. The police hunt for a killer but no culprit is ever found. The families of the victims resolve themselves to the fact that they may never have answers — but four decades later all is revealed when a local outcast begins confessing on her deathbed.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2RycTkfN6QBKQ87379oxge</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2492</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best of 2021: The Disappearance of Michael Rockefeller</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2olrTOFBFFTzOXrszHBefO?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>As we look ahead to the new year, we want to take one last chance to say thank you for the year that was — and present our "Best of 2021"! Please enjoy this episode from Disappearances with Sarah Turney, one of our favorite new shows this year. Officially, 23-year-old Michael Rockefeller drowned off the coast of New Guinea in 1961. But disturbing rumors add another dimension to his death.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2olrTOFBFFTzOXrszHBefO</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2651</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“The Christmas Rapture” from Cults</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0FvMZlpmjpcaC0YO2hEXXp?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On Christmas Eve nearly seventy years ago, Dorothy Martin and the Seekers stood outside in Chicago and sang carols. They were waiting for a spacecraft that would shepherd them away from Earth — and the impending apocalypse. In this Christmas Special from Cults, join us for a look into a doomsday cult awaiting deliverance. And if you like this episode, follow Cults — a Spotify Original from Parcast — for more chilling insights every week!  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0FvMZlpmjpcaC0YO2hEXXp</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2313</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Stolen Violin: Julian Altman</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1nIdGwpfGO39oLttSM3Gka?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In 1936, a daring theft takes place at Carnegie Hall. A valuable Stradivarius violin is stolen from the dressing room of Polish virtuoso Bronislaw Huberman while he is on stage. The whereabouts of the Stradivarius remain a mystery for 50 years, until one day another musician, Julian Altman, lies dying in a Connecticut hospital. In his final days, he tells his wife the secret of the violin he has been playing for most of his career. It’s a story so incredible it can only be true. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1nIdGwpfGO39oLttSM3Gka</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2278</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Barber’s Basement: Vernon Seitz</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/26pyFWzJxnkA14b4SwHmYC?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>A barber from Milwaukee was known by locals for taking an unusual interest in missing persons cases, especially those of children. What they didn’t know was that Vernon Seitz had a secret he’d been keeping for fifty years — one he’d kept under lock and key until confessing to his psychiatrist days before his death. He’d had a traumatic childhood experience of his own. What police officers later find in his basement is the most baffling, yet chilling, discovery of their careers. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26pyFWzJxnkA14b4SwHmYC</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2203</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norwegian Nightmare: Tor Hepso</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4KBoGKlCSpBPPd9tWpndjS?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In late 1970s Norway, two young women were brutally murdered. Demand for justice was swift, and despite what some saw as a prosecution case built on shaky foundations, a man spent the best years of his life paying for those crimes. Balance was restored, or so police thought, until almost thirty years later, when Tor Hepso's final words blew the case wide open again... Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4KBoGKlCSpBPPd9tWpndjS</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2386</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yoga Cults Pt. 1</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2cQOKfZ1enwEHY6EPYOn2Z?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>How do quests for enlightenment get so sinister? In this three-part special from Cults, a Spotify Original from Parcast, we’re looking at three stories of yoga gurus who were loved — then loathed — for their practices. We start in Romania, charting the rise of Gregorian Bivolaru: an allegedly all-powerful mystic who remixed religions for an ever-expanding cache of followers across Europe. But the price of following him was more than devotion… If you like this episode, search and follow Cults to delve into the minds of more notorious cult leaders every Tuesday. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cQOKfZ1enwEHY6EPYOn2Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1901</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yoga Cults Pt. 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1X84PWO2lY0tvAtweqKJ2G?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Hosts Vanessa Richardson and Lanie Hobbs explore the story of Geshe Michael Roach and Christie McNally — the so-called king and queen of Diamond Mountain who used tantric yoga to lure hundreds to their Arizona desert retreat. This episode is a collaboration between Cults and Crimes of Passion, two Spotify Originals from Parcast. Every week, Cults analyzes the minds and movements of notorious cult leaders, and Crimes of Passion follows love stories that turn into crime stories. Search and follow to catch new episodes! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1X84PWO2lY0tvAtweqKJ2G</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2343</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yoga Cults Pt. 3 </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1T4lO36rwGPzr2LSjeraWK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In Japan, a yoga teacher named Shoko Asahara claimed he had special DNA, developed the battery-powered “Perfect Salvation System,” and directed his cult, Aum Shinrikyo, to carry out chemical attacks in Tokyo. This is the final episode in the three-part series — if you enjoyed it, search and follow Cults to hear what really happens behind the closed doors of covert societies. New episodes Tuesdays. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1T4lO36rwGPzr2LSjeraWK</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2410</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guilty Knowledge: E. Howard Hunt Pt. 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7dtd0UNDYpToD4fEdIH1UV?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Who killed JFK? If you believe the authorities, the president’s killer was Lee Harvey Oswald, acting alone. But if so, why was Oswald himself murdered in police custody just 48 hours after his arrest? One man claimed he had all the answers: former CIA agent E. Howard Hunt. And in his explosive deathbed confession, he laid out a conspiracy that went right to the top. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7dtd0UNDYpToD4fEdIH1UV</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2433</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guilty Knowledge: E. Howard Hunt Pt. 1</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0bpE060I4568mowAdnCorS?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>President John F. Kennedy was assassinated in Dallas on November 22, 1963. According to the official version, he was killed by a lone gunman, Lee Harvey Oswald. But right from the outset, conspiracy theories were rife. For decades, a rumor persisted that the CIA itself was behind the president’s assassination. Then, in 2003, as he believed himself about to die, former CIA agent E. Howard Hunt wrote down the bare bones of a plot that involved not just the CIA but also Kennedy’s successor, Lyndon B. Johnson. Was this, at last, proof of the conspiracy that many had suspected for so long? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0bpE060I4568mowAdnCorS</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2298</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Monstrous Deception?: Christian Spurling</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4em7DT7BnFOYmG4cPThtav?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In April 1934, an amazing photograph appeared on the front page of the Daily Mail newspaper. For many, the photo proved the existence of the Loch Ness monster. Decades later, investigators track down a man almost as reclusive as Nessie herself. Christian Spurling is the only person still alive who knows the truth about that famous photograph. But by now he is an old man, close to the end of his life. Will he reveal all before he dies? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4em7DT7BnFOYmG4cPThtav</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2357</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Special: Christine Kett</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0vuD92aeccooJJ7zvJQqTj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In 1867, 18-year-old Christy Kett was found brutally murdered in her home. Police are shocked by the savagery of the attack, but have little real evidence to go on. The list of suspects ranges from her brother Fred to Christy’s sweetheart and a local bad boy. Even her mother comes under suspicion. But the mystery is never solved — not until 17 years later, when a sick old woman gasps out a stunning confession to her son as she lies dying.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0vuD92aeccooJJ7zvJQqTj</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2258</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Nation in Crisis: John Wilkes Booth Pt. 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3Q83fqRytMJzJ8A7JFqkVH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>After the assassination of President Lincoln in 1865, the nation believed federal soldiers killed his assassin on April 26th 1865. Forty-two years later, shocking claims are made that Booth evaded capture and has been living under the fake name John St Helen. Thinking he is dying, St Helen gives a deathbed confession detailing the plot to kill Lincoln and how he evaded capture. He also alleges the conspiracy to kill Lincoln was conceived at the highest levels of his administration. When federal authorities disregard the confession, a bizarre series of events unfold which will see the supposed mummified body of Booth tour the country before disappearing altogether a hundred years later. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3Q83fqRytMJzJ8A7JFqkVH</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2380</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Nation in Crisis: John Wilkes Booth Pt. 1</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/49Jc4qJ8U367cidLBKF6fM?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>As the American Civil War comes to a close, the renowned stage actor John Wilkes Booth decides it's time to enter the theatre of war. He assassinates President Lincoln, plunging the country into one of its darkest moments. Booth is later shot at a farm in Eastern Virginia and dragged out onto a porch so that everyone can hear his dying words: a final message for his mother. Forty-two years later, a lawyer claims the man shot at the farm was not the president’s assassin. The lawyer gives a detailed deathbed confession of a man claiming to be the real John Wilkes Booth. If true, it will rewrite American history. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49Jc4qJ8U367cidLBKF6fM</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2487</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Irishman Who Got Hoffa: Frank Sheeran</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1KOUIVaE5HQR4hLPSo7I7d?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In 1975, the notoriously corrupt union leader Jimmy Hoffa vanished without a trace. Due to his various dirty dealings, the FBI assumed it was a mob hit but could never find evidence to back it up. For decades it seemed the question "Who got Hoffa?" would never be answered — until 1999, when Hoffa's old right-hand man, Frank Sheeran, begins confessing on his deathbed... Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1KOUIVaE5HQR4hLPSo7I7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2328</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where’s Dad?: Geraldine Kelley </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/601GWKoeYKgCV2z8CSxePL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The estranged adult children of “Geri” Kelley long suspected foul play in their father’s death. Though she had told them that John Kelley had died in a road accident, Geri revealed on her deathbed in 2004 that she’d shot him in the head and kept his body in a storage facility freezer for years. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">601GWKoeYKgCV2z8CSxePL</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2181</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confession of an Alcatraz Escapee: John Anglin</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0vDtogjcTqiuxCqwFO7wCW?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In 2013, the San Francisco Police Department received a written deathbed confession from a man claiming to be John Anglin — one of the famed fugitives from America's "most inescapable" prison, Alcatraz Federal Penitentiary. Back in 1962, John, along with his brother Clarence and friend Frank Morris, disappeared from Alcatraz never to be seen again. The FBI has long claimed the three men must have died during the escape… But the letter that police received says they all lived well into old age. Is it the missing piece to one of America’s biggest mysteries? Or is it just another hoax? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0vDtogjcTqiuxCqwFO7wCW</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2409</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death of a Rolling Stone: Frank Thorogood Pt. 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3yoxqsygnkDSn1rJyOA8En?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Musician Brian Jones was a talented but deeply troubled man. We look into the events leading up to his death in 1969, in particular his difficult relationship with Frank Thorogood, the man who will one day allegedly confess to killing Jones. We also shine a spotlight on the role played by someone close to the heart of the Rolling Stones organization: behind-the-scenes fixer Tom Keylock. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3yoxqsygnkDSn1rJyOA8En</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2469</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death of a Rolling Stone: Frank Thorogood Pt. 1</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5majigygLBcHhctoUoqG0M?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>When founding Rolling Stones member Brian Jones was found dead in a swimming pool on July 3, 1969, police immediately ruled his death an accident. One man was in the pool with him that night, a building contractor named Frank Thorogood. Many years later, in his final moments, Thorogood will make a startling confession about the night Jones died. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5majigygLBcHhctoUoqG0M</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1746</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deathbed Survivor: Jeffrey Gafoor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/28YhPP5qsBqfK06CSGzJBb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In 1988, British police found the remains of a gruesomely murdered woman in a flat in Cardiff, UK. The woman had over 50 stab wounds on her body. The murder went unsolved until 2003, when a man named Jeffrey Gafoor confessed after taking a lethal dose of paracetemol tablets… Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28YhPP5qsBqfK06CSGzJBb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2745</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Innocence: Ottis Toole Pt. 3</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/218JmX4cJGqVcg3hKpbbJh?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Ottis Toole is arrested for arson and confesses to a string of murders committed with his lover Henry Lee Lucas. Detectives come from all over to talk to him. Toole confesses to taking a little boy from a mall in Florida, but later denies it. Though Toole takes police to various locations connected with the crime, detectives are unable to discover decisive forensic evidence. Everything hinges on his deathbed confession. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">218JmX4cJGqVcg3hKpbbJh</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2674</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Innocence: Ottis Toole Pt. 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5u5BSvCTPEIqUurZLzhl19?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The case takes a dramatic turn with the discovery of a severed head positively identified as Adam's. This is no longer a kidnapping, it's murder. We explore the twisted relationship between Ottis Toole and fellow serial killer Henry Lee Lucas. The sighting of a blue van brings another serial killer into the frame... a certain Jeffrey Dahmer. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5u5BSvCTPEIqUurZLzhl19</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2073</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Innocence: Ottis Toole Pt. 1</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/12pVU94TiOcrM6i9LtUBIa?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>While serving multiple life sentences in prison and dying of liver failure, convicted serial killer Ottis Toole made a deathbed confession to a prison health administrator. He claimed sole responsibility in the 1981 murder of six-year-old Adam Walsh. This was not the first time Toole had confessed to the crime. But this time was different. This time he had no reason to lie. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12pVU94TiOcrM6i9LtUBIa</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1940</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Cold Case: Margaret Gibson Pt. 3 </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5tYGdR9n3CjLyKoq6rgaXq?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Long after the William Desmond Taylor murder case grew cold researchers uncovered new information on Margaret Gibson's criminal history and her potential involvement in the killing...and how she may have capitalized on William Desmond Taylor's secret life... Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5tYGdR9n3CjLyKoq6rgaXq</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2611</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Cold Case: Margaret Gibson Pt. 2 </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3h7oAZfNBWurCryXypmBRD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>As the investigation into William Desmond Taylor's murder amps up, lead investigator Detective King examines the evidence and begins to suspect three of the most powerful women in 1920s Hollywood: comedy queen Mabel Normand, ingenue Mary Miles Minter, and notorious stage mother Charlotte Shelby. To get answers, he'll need to go up against one of the most powerful industries in America — the Hollywood movie studios. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3h7oAZfNBWurCryXypmBRD</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2418</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Cold Case: Margaret Gibson Pt. 1 </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1AG5afLOCsbskDlX6OIC4V?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>When famed director William Desmond Taylor was murdered in 1922, the LAPD rushed to find his killer — compiling a long list of suspects that included some of the silent film era's biggest stars. Actress Margaret Gibson always flew under their radar… But could her dying words finally solve one of Hollywood's longest-running cold cases? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1AG5afLOCsbskDlX6OIC4V</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2098</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Deathbed Confessions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0oLP4AseI7Pa7p1Tpzy9dO?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Starting July 21st, Deathbed Confessions brings you into the stories of last-ditch attempts to clear consciences. Crimes are solved. Mysteries become clear. And the cases that haunted collective imaginations are put to rest. Or are they? New episodes weekly. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0oLP4AseI7Pa7p1Tpzy9dO</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>79</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

