<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Every Little Thing</title>
    <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/2dY2l2v95zz9HTlYvDSAdA</link>
    <description>Why do we cry? Did cavemen really carry clubs? Can swearing make you stronger? On ELT, you call with a question, we find you an answer. Our helpline is open 24-7. Call 833-RING-ELT or send an audio message to elt@gimletmedia.com.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8afb746c0c706effd032d75360</url>
      <title>Every Little Thing</title>
      <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/2dY2l2v95zz9HTlYvDSAdA</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:28:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Black Holes: Free Your Mind</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6T8bcksgNHdv9I8AzAGIgQ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In honor of this week’s festivities, we’re taking a trip back to black hole country. Listener Kyle wants to know: are black holes really holes? Professor of physics at the University of Southern California Clifford Johnson has answers that will loosen your third eye and blaze up your mind. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6T8bcksgNHdv9I8AzAGIgQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1248</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living Underwater: Extreme Deep Diving</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/12JAFfWvAoJa0r14qITkL6?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>When scuba divers go deep, it can take a full day to resurface. Caller Daniela wants to know: how do they drink, eat and excrete while underwater? Fish biologist Richard Pyle gives us the lowdown on deep diving. Plus, saturation diver Michael Meusel lives in an underwater chamber for a month at a time for his job. He tells us about the challenges of deep sea work, like hammering underwater and breathing helium-laced air. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12JAFfWvAoJa0r14qITkL6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1320</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Do Strangers Keep Talking to Me?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1sJ51arvS2mihpTwaVzI6C?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Brittany has a problem. No matter where she goes, strangers open up to her. She can’t get through the grocery store without a heart-to-heart. ELT consults a panel of experts to understand why this happens to Brittany, and what she can do about it. Pixar character designer Deana Marsiglese performs a facial analysis; celebrity presentation coach Glenn Kinsey offers repulsive communication techniques; and herpetologist Dusty Rhoads has an extreme solution guaranteed to stop a conversation short. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1sJ51arvS2mihpTwaVzI6C</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1437</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Are Cats A-holes?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2RWgBwYEWcEUvXO9d8rx30?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Winter wants to know why her cat Creepy Bones likes to knock things over. Jackson Galaxy, cat behavior expert and host of the TV show “My Cat From Hell,” decodes this common cat activity. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2RWgBwYEWcEUvXO9d8rx30</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>160</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Makes a Good ELT Question?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3VzdMX4tWU688kQC0Broxq?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>How do we track down the perfect guest? How do we live with our terrible puns? What makes a good question? We’re answering every little question you have about Every Little Thing.Episodes we reference: How To Be Less Clumsy Fruit Flies: Seriously, Where Do They Come From? Space Trash: Is It Coming For Us? How a Superbowl Ref Works the Game Auctioneers: Why Do They Talk Like That? Tooth Worms and Tooth Pullers: Dentistry's Rotten History F*ck Yeah: Can Cursing Make You Stronger? How Did Dogs Land in Our Laps? Cheese: Why Do We Worship Rotten Milk? A NSFW History  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3VzdMX4tWU688kQC0Broxq</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1286</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Want to Hear the Voicemail You Can’t Delete</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3bZLW60LaZjn4lHEHZuowf?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Do you have a voicemail you just can’t delete? Maybe it’s from your ex, or it’s a butt dial from your best friend that makes you cry-laugh every time you hear it. Maybe it’s a message your mom left when you went into labor. Maybe it’s a message you listen to when you need a pick-me-up, or when you want to remember the person who left it, or when you just want to fuel your rage. No judgment! If you have a voicemail you can’t get rid, we want to hear about it. Call and leave us a message: 833-RING-ELT. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3bZLW60LaZjn4lHEHZuowf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>62</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is Elvis Marrying People in Vegas?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7I7QOeKkNfejC3sKOBmXQn?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Garrett wants to know how Elvis impersonators and Las Vegas weddings tied the knot. Las Vegas-torian Larry Gragg tells us how Vegas became a wedding hot spot, and how Elvis rose to royalty in Sin City. The singer and the city seemed like a match made in heaven. Plus, Garrett and Swiggs say “I mew” with help from Mobile Minister Roland August. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7I7QOeKkNfejC3sKOBmXQn</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1538</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nail Polish Naming: Who Does That?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1BRZrCebysOOErK4raolyc?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, we’re revisiting a favorite episode. From “Crawfishin’ for a Compliment” to “Gouda Gouda Two Shoes,” how do nail polish colors get their quippy names? ELT digs into this FAQ with fashion historian Suzanne Shapiro and OPI co-founder Suzi Weiss-Fischmann. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1BRZrCebysOOErK4raolyc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1004</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Glam Shots: How Real Are They?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6zAmzJiuLZAvOiyvu8Zlfq?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The images NASA publishes of outer space seem too good to be true – are they? Joe DePasquale, the star-tist who prepares the cosmos for its close-ups, paints us a picture of how those images are made. Plus, NASA astronomer Michelle Thaller describes NASA’s brand new eye-in-the-sky. She says it’s about to blow our earthly little minds. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6zAmzJiuLZAvOiyvu8Zlfq</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1391</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cards: Solving a Shuffle Kerfuffle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5i9aNUlIqieO17SQUGxFed?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, we’re bringing back one of our favorite episodes. Listeners Marmie and Ryan want to know — how many times should you shuffle a deck of playing cards? Marmie says three, but Ryan says four or more. The couple places their bets and goes all in with applied mathematician Steven Strogatz and a full house of card-world VIPs. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5i9aNUlIqieO17SQUGxFed</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1415</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valentine’s Day, Massacred</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0SVVNNPXIcHkDdeVWTQvVl?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We asked for your Valentine’s Day fail tales, and our heart-shaped voicemail box is full. From a poisoning to a wax-museum meltdown, you exposed Valentine's Day for the helliday it is. Thanks to callers Candace, Sam, Reina, Lauren, Ronni and everyone who helped us give Valentine's Day a big F you. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0SVVNNPXIcHkDdeVWTQvVl</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1609</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a Super Bowl Ref Works the Game</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7AUKg5zmAF7LysgvXzUAgm?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Every year millions of people take part in an American tradition: eating wings, drinking beer, and watching the Super Bowl. While most fans focus on the players, listener Erika wants to know about the other people on the field – the officials. How do referees get the job? What’s it like to be at the center of the action? And what does it take to make it to the Super Bowl? Retired NFL official and Coordinator of Football Officials at SIAC Tom Symonette fields some questions. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7AUKg5zmAF7LysgvXzUAgm</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1424</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Do We Shake Hands?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6sy8NgjkP3neFVQpIYVJvd?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Alberto wants to know how handshakes became the go-to greeting in many parts of the world, and why extended shakes often take center stage when world leaders meet. Paleoanthropologist and handshake expert Ella Al-Shamahi hands us some answers, and deconstructs a handshake so bad it’ll leave you shook. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6sy8NgjkP3neFVQpIYVJvd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1377</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Be Less Clumsy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/19jFA7TurZWsgtraII8tmD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today, we’re rerunning one of our favorite episodes. Listener Gab is clumsy: white sweaters, stemmed wine glasses and sharp edges are off the table. Can Gab learn to be less clumsy? Professional steady-hand Bryan Berg and kinesiologist Priscila Tamplain share tips for foiling fumbles. Special thanks to Carl Gabbard and Michael Wade. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19jFA7TurZWsgtraII8tmD</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1052</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help Us Ruin Valentine’s Day</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2NpSjiQA39YkxUnFM9nHe1?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>To honor this Hallmark helliday, we want your stories of Valentine’s Day fails. Did you suffer third-degree burns from your vanilla-scented candle tower? Or discover your rose petal allergy… the hard way? Maybe you found out your friend with benefits was actually your friend with bedbugs? Call us with your best bad Valentine’s Day story: 833 RING ELT, or send a voice memo to elt@gimletmedia.com. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2NpSjiQA39YkxUnFM9nHe1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>69</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Did Netflix’s “Ta-dum” Sound Come From?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4HUOxHIkVzgVyA7ZtRFGq5?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today’s episode comes from our friends at the podcast Twenty Thousand Hertz. They investigated the Netflix “ta-dum” – the sound effect that rings out when you queue up a Netflix show. It’s so iconic you probably can hear it in your head, but it almost sounded very, very different (think bleating goats). Find more episodes from Twenty Thousand Hertz here. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4HUOxHIkVzgVyA7ZtRFGq5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1311</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slithering Heights: Big Snake, Big Problems</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7yjmm8rIGook6rosu8mItG?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>During a late-night internet search, caller Brenna stumbled across an ancient super-sized snake. It got her wondering: why doesn’t it slither among us today? Where’d it go? Snake hiss-perer Jason Head tells us about the life and times of Titanoboa, the biggest snake ever found. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7yjmm8rIGook6rosu8mItG</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1052</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Embarrassing Story in All of Human History</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4Ql4ME1dD8DhfFvZRnr6dN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>A New Year’s resolution: Last year, hundreds of you submitted your mortifying tales. This week, we announce the winner. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4Ql4ME1dD8DhfFvZRnr6dN</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>299</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Old is Winnie-the-Pooh?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2sQLkKmufZCTiDz8dc3vge?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We’re revisiting one of our favorite episodes this week. A few years ago, listener Annie asked ELT to settle a longstanding family debate: exactly how old is Winnie-the-Pooh? To hunt down an answer, we consult with professional age-guesser Ben Ramey, bear biologist Rae Wynn-Grant, and Sarah Shea, a professor who has studied this question. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2sQLkKmufZCTiDz8dc3vge</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1343</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Ice-Age Bison Mummy Yummy?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1UVhvwxoR84wJbE7izXQf4?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Taylor is back with a question about dining on ancient finds. Mary Lee Guthrie tells us about the 1980s dinner party that served up Ice-Age-era meat. Special thanks to Dale Guthrie, Eirik Granqvist, Julie Meachen, and Grant Zazula. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1UVhvwxoR84wJbE7izXQf4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1029</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Did People Eat 10,000 Years Ago?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/194EYMWMrtPTFgJBl08D47?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>After unearthing a 10-year-old bottle of maple syrup in his pantry, listener Taylor wants to know: What sorts of ancient foods do archaeologists find? Pothead and biomolecular archaeologist Julie Dunne cracks the case on ancient diets and tells us how we know what people ate thousands of years ago. Warning: the answers are NSFL (not safe for lunch). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">194EYMWMrtPTFgJBl08D47</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1111</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeremy’s Muscle Car: An Update</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0wvQcuyiJjTn6JMmWsgF3j?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On our “I Did it For Love” episode, listener Jeremy told us about a 1968 AMX that he was buying to surprise his dad. This week, they go for their first ride. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0wvQcuyiJjTn6JMmWsgF3j</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>221</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Did It for Love</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0EbATZCbUFpi7s2r1vT7k7?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>What have you done for love? Hear about the impulsive, expensive, inspired and illegal things our listeners did for love. Thanks to Erica, Mario, Beth, Jeremy and everyone who called in with a heart-felt tale. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0EbATZCbUFpi7s2r1vT7k7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1943</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kangaroo Pouch: A Four-Star Hotel of Horrors</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4hrPBJIWVU4lvdjD6KACQy?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Caller Sophia needs to know: What’s it like inside a kangaroo pouch? We get the inside scoop from marsupial expert Robin Beck. Plus, should Flora’s sister Ruth fear her squash? Professional pumpkineer Steve Reiners has a tip: if it smells like cat urine, beware. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4hrPBJIWVU4lvdjD6KACQy</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1365</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auctioneers: Why Do They Talk Like That?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1Za4LwBAeT0SapyYRnJQYY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, an episode from the archives: Why do auctioneers talk the way they do? And what are they actually saying? Professional auctioneer Junior Staggs tells us about the psychology behind auction-speak, and gives caller Katie some tips for developing her own auctioneer chant. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1Za4LwBAeT0SapyYRnJQYY</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1200</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Important Message from Flora</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0B0zxxx01dMWDhejdPu8Rz?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Flora is back with some news, and a request. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0B0zxxx01dMWDhejdPu8Rz</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>66</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can I Bury a Body in My Yard?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0cP8dzY2NKfjKrdZEMPWW9?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Jake wants to know if he can bury a body in his tiny, suburban backyard. Grave expert and archaeologist Hal Hassen has the scoop on how we went from burying grandpa out back to the giant park-like cemeteries we have today. Plus, local zoning officer Sonya Abt walks Jake through the red tape. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0cP8dzY2NKfjKrdZEMPWW9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1486</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worms and Pelicans: Dentistry’s Rotten History</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6wRRFKn4FqvJliVutf0hZA?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, we brush off an ELT favorite on the gory history of tooth care. For most of human history, chomper maintenance has been bloody and brutal. So how'd we go from charlatans yanking teeth in a public square to the soft light and high-tech of the modern dentist's office? ELT asks retired dentist and dental historian J. Henry Clarke and historian Richard Barnett to open up and say how. Plus Chris Lyons tells us his secrets for making movie stars' teeth look terrible. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6wRRFKn4FqvJliVutf0hZA</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1431</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What the Flock Is in My Chimney?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6CKBHYysOLRFof5knXDrs1?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Every evening at dusk, listener Tara watches clouds of tiny birds dive-bomb into her boyfriend’s chimney. What are these creatures, and are they going to destroy the house? Ornithologist Margaret Rubega introduces us to these notoriously mysterious birds, and to the stubborn 19th-century artist-turned-scientist who was determined to study them. Special thanks to Barbara Boyle. Thanks also to songwriter Jay Ungar for the use of Ashokan Farewell, ©1983 by Swinging Door Music. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6CKBHYysOLRFof5knXDrs1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1262</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Squirrels Track Their Nuts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4xJfRgsSvsFUmSwv87SfJe?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, we dug up a favorite episode on the secret life of squirrels. The average tree squirrel can bury up to 10,000 nuts every fall. How do they keep tabs on that stash? Animal behaviorist and pro squirrel watcher Mikel Maria Delgado exposes the secrets of squirrel pantry maintenance. Thanks to caller Cayra. This episode of Every Little Thing was produced by Stephanie Werner, Emily Forman, Phoebe Flanigan, Annette Heist and Flora Lichtman, with help from Nicole Pasulka and Doug Barron. Our consulting editors are Caitlin Kenney and Jorge Just. Mixed by Dara Hirsch and Enoch Kim. Scored by Dara Hirsch, Bobby Lord and Emma Munger. ELT is a Gimlet production and a Spotify original podcast. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4xJfRgsSvsFUmSwv87SfJe</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>858</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symphony Secrets: Dirt from the Pit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4RcwNa0CYBld39Nemxs1sB?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, an encore of a favorite episode: What happens behind the scenes at the symphony. Does a triangle player get the same pay as a violinist? Do conductors ever fall off their podiums? Which section do the other musicians love to hate? ELT dishes symphony secrets with violinist Akiko Tarumoto and conductor Rob Kapilow. Special thanks to Nathan Cole and danke schön to caller Laszlo. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4RcwNa0CYBld39Nemxs1sB</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1428</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Astronauts Come Home</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6yfX3H0s0k4lUr29gSN1OT?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, we’re revisiting an intergalactic favorite: Preparing for a mission to space takes astronauts years, but listener Daniel wants to know — what does the other end of that journey look like? Record-holding NASA astronaut Christina Koch tells us what happens when space travelers come home.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6yfX3H0s0k4lUr29gSN1OT</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1520</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do Streets Get Named?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7w7KVTCl7lUKnbFRRRJZ16?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Caller Jessica lives on a street with an unwieldy name, and she wants to know: Who gets to name the streets? Deirdre Mask, author of “The Address Book: What Street Addresses Reveal About Identity, Race, Wealth, and Power,” tells us about a project to name all the streets in rural West Virginia, and why having a street address matters. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7w7KVTCl7lUKnbFRRRJZ16</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1217</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELT Presents: Not Past It</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3JujbaDrEmwT4tweoNnf5S?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Hey ELT fans! There’s a new Gimlet podcast that we think you’ll love. It’s called Not Past It, and it’s the kind of deep-dive into history that we live for at ELT. This episode, Rated PG-13 for Sex and Violence looks at the birth of the PG-13 rating, and how the movie rating system came to be. It’s a story about Indiana Jones and Gremlins, and hidden Puritan agendas. Enjoy! And don’t forget to follow Not Past It on Spotify.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3JujbaDrEmwT4tweoNnf5S</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1695</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is It Weird to Be Nice to Alexa?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7LROHpWXrXOHXfZ4EkyYZD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week we’re hitting repeat on one of our favorite episodes: Listener Elizabeth wants to know if it’s weird to say “please” and “thank you” to her Google voice assistant. ELT talks to former Alexa insider Daren Gill (now senior director of product at Spotify), and human-robot interactions expert Leila Takayama to find out whether people are typically polite to machines. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7LROHpWXrXOHXfZ4EkyYZD</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1041</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Any Animals Dance?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5KqxKkwAX4Pwll31wvTIcX?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>After trying (and failing) to start a dance party with her dogs, listener Heather wants to know: are there beasts that can boogie? Irena Schulz and Ani Patel break it down. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5KqxKkwAX4Pwll31wvTIcX</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1184</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheese: Why Do We Worship Rotten Milk? A NSFW History</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6EBRMpmwrCcsQtR7gNUhUF?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, we’re re-heating one of our ooey-gooey all-time favorite eps: We re-trace the delicious and X-rated history of... cheese, with cheese biochemist and historian Paul Kindstedt. Plus, tips on how to make the most of the dairy aisle from processed cheese expert Lloyd Metzger. And a cicada killer update from cicada killer wasp biologist Chuck Holliday. Thanks to callers Kurt and Judy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6EBRMpmwrCcsQtR7gNUhUF</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1026</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Horrible Sound that Haunts Reality TV</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5hmtc1LolTFj2xRZHTpkpc?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We’re revisiting one of our favorite eps this week, to find out who put the tension in reality TV. ELT tracks down the man behind the nail-biting sound you can’t unhear. Plus, a listener’s backyard horror story turns into an intervention, with cicada killer wasp expert Chuck Holliday. Thanks to callers Caitlin and Stephanie. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5hmtc1LolTFj2xRZHTpkpc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1012</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What It’s Like To Live in the White House</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/35Iv5nzONSERwpKwZq8TkB?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>What’s life really like in the White House? How does the president get snacks? Who walks the first dogs? What happens when the first family fights? Kate Andersen Brower, reporter and author of The Residence, takes us behind-the-scenes. Thanks to callers Lauren, Rachel, Iris, Zach and everyone who sent in a question. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35Iv5nzONSERwpKwZq8TkB</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1326</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Is This Goose Out to Get Me?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6yJnQpzGkKH893GF8yFln1?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Corey needs to know if a goose named Dave is targeting him. Goose expert Tony Fox tells us why Dave’s feathers may have gotten ruffled, and offers his advice for dealing with unhappy geese. Special thanks to Casey Williamson, Steve Davis, and Dan Potoczak. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6yJnQpzGkKH893GF8yFln1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1113</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Is This Toy Talking?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6biEcsAEv2RSeUTFv3ZxvH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Megan wants to know who writes the bizzaro lyrics for her son’s talking toys. Talking humans Jay Elkinton and Patrick Feaster tell us all about these earworm emitters — from modern plastic jabber-jaws to the nightmare-inducing doll who started it all. Special thanks to Toby Phillips. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6biEcsAEv2RSeUTFv3ZxvH</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1209</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sand: What’s It Really Made Of?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3fhPVDp38ff1tyC38R2R2S?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We’ve dug up one of our favorite episodes this week: Caller Hank wants to know where the sand on his central California beach came from. Beach buff Kiki Patsch gives us the surprising scoop on how beaches are born. Special thanks to Gary Griggs. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3fhPVDp38ff1tyC38R2R2S</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1024</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Is the Ocean Glowing?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/68vURk3QpKaEif5zvAIget?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>While Flora’s away, we’re shining a light on some of our favorite episodes. Listener Erik saw a mysterious glow in the water during a trip to the beach, and he wants to know more. ELT talks to the “Jacques Cousteau of glow,” a scientist who has spent decades deep diving for answers. Guest: biologist and ocean researcher Edie Widder. Thanks to Eelke Dekker for the seagull and ocean sounds we used in this episode. Thanks also to Steven Haddock, Michael Latz, Matt Davis, Vincent Pieribone, and Severine Martini. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68vURk3QpKaEif5zvAIget</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1196</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hummingbirds: Magical Fairies or Vicious Little Drones?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1dWxenKxGUmJOVCCuegGtK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Caller Makaila needs to know about the hummingbirds that frequent her father’s feeders. Hummingbird expert Alejandro Rico-Guevara fills us in on their feeding, flying, and fighting feats. Photo credit: Kristiina Hurme Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1dWxenKxGUmJOVCCuegGtK</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1482</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is My Cat Trying to Murder Me?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/19m6ROyKKBFVxL1xtoITQ1?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>While Flora’s out, we’re revisiting an old favorite — caller Megan’s cat has zero empathy and tries to trip her on the stairs. Could he be a psychopath? Jon Ronson, author of The Psychopath Test, and cat psychologist Eva Waiblinger help Megan assess if she's got a killer just a whisker's length away. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19m6ROyKKBFVxL1xtoITQ1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1161</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ever Felt Someone’s Pain… In Your Butt?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0Wt97HW65s4M22dL1QVx4r?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>While Flora's out on parental leave, we're unswaddling some of her favorite babies. Favorite podcast babies. Like this one: Caller Lisa wants to know why her butt hurts whenever she sees someone else get injured. Neuroscientist Stuart Derbyshire shares the cold hard truth about whether some people really can feel your pain. Thanks to queen of Chapped Cheeks Lisa, and to researchers Natalie Bowling, Melita Giummarra, Helena Hartmann, Marina López-Solà, Bridget Rubenking, Jamie Ward, Scott Vrana, and Jamil Zaki. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0Wt97HW65s4M22dL1QVx4r</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1532</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory Game: Did This Meal Really Happen?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3CxblS9NfhvxaHbiHFoKoP?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Caller Liz has a cherished childhood memory about a special meal with her great-grandmother. But she isn’t sure it really happened. How can she tell? Memory researcher Charan Ranganath, director of the Dynamic Memory Lab, fills in the blanks about the memory in question. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3CxblS9NfhvxaHbiHFoKoP</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1249</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When a Million Ants Come Marching In</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6d6JCsnfUPquE43VmvkeWe?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Gĩtaũ has a serious problem: every so often his home in rural Kenya is invaded by an army of ants. They coat the floors, climb the walls, and rain down on Gĩtaũ and his family while they sleep. Gĩtaũ wants to know: Why are these ants torturing us? Entomologists Dino Martins and Piotr Naskrecki have ant-swers. Special thanks to Caswell Munyai, Caspar Schöning, and Daniel Kronauer. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d6JCsnfUPquE43VmvkeWe</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1156</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Message From Flora</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6uGuixFIKQEsfjAEQ3BhKC?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Flora has a 6- to 9-pound piece of news to drop! She’ll be out on parental leave for a little while. Meet the hosts who’ll be filling in while she’s away. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6uGuixFIKQEsfjAEQ3BhKC</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>115</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog Show Drama: Is There an Anti-Dachshund Conspiracy?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/22N5AOQu2XrBO1dswdio1r?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Terriers have won Best in Show at the Westminster Kennel Club dog show 48 times. Dachshunds? Never. Listener Yona wants to know why terriers triumph but dachshunds don’t get their due. Dog show judge Laurie Williams and dachshund-diehard Kim McCalmont take us behind the scenes of the dog show world. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22N5AOQu2XrBO1dswdio1r</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1500</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Ghosts: Searching For Endangered Animals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0uZYR3l9CN2n7ATE3pQvIN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Diksha wants to know: when an animal species is endangered, how do we know when it’s really gone? Professional frog counter and disease ecologist Jamie Voyles has answers. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0uZYR3l9CN2n7ATE3pQvIN</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1110</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skewed Smells: A Weird COVID Mystery</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6an502tBxlKzbQzOZWD4tr?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Caller Leña had COVID-19 last October and temporarily lost her sense of smell. As it started to come back, she noticed something strange — fruity things smelled like burnt hair and condoms. Where are Leña’s mystery smells coming from? Rhinologist Simon Gane fills us in on COVID-related smell loss. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6an502tBxlKzbQzOZWD4tr</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1115</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embarrassing Little Tales: The Finalists</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4rGTnlQdk5opzWVPtZ1NfS?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We asked you to share your fail tales, and you delivered. Now we need your help picking a winner. Thanks to Erica, Dallas, Ryan, Mary, Nasja, David, Samantha, and everyone who called to share their worst moments. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4rGTnlQdk5opzWVPtZ1NfS</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1286</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Trash: Is It Coming For Us?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3jpc5BEzXrhwGAUoKaruO5?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The Earth is surrounded by a halo of trash — defunct satellites, discarded fuel tanks, one of Elon Musk’s Teslas. Listener Ryan wants to know: Does any of it ever fall down to Earth? ELT talks trash with Lottie Williams, the only person known to have been hit by falling space debris, and Ted Muelhaupt, director of the Center for Orbital and Reentry Debris Study at The Aerospace Corporation. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3jpc5BEzXrhwGAUoKaruO5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1042</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vodka, Spit, and Coke: How to Spring-Clean Like an Adult</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5JeISbWHR7Ss4s6YGQ5UjH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>It’s spring-cleaning time! To help get you in the mood, we’re dusting off an episode from our archive. Cleaning expert Jolie Kerr tells us when it’s OK to use your own saliva as a cleaning agent, and addresses some listener “cleanspiracies” like: Will vodka clean my clothes? For more cleaning tips, check out Jolie’s podcast Ask a Clean Person. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5JeISbWHR7Ss4s6YGQ5UjH</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1278</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Nasal-Gazing Mystery Solved</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4oDR2vPp7mpJuFuiive7oM?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Paige heard a rumor: we only breathe through one nostril. Can it be true? ELT gets an answer from someone in the nose — rhinologist Simon Gane. Plus, Science Vs. host Wendy Zukerman joins Flora for an important wombat-butt update. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4oDR2vPp7mpJuFuiive7oM</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1262</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Did Dogs Land in Our Laps?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5rwitDrQbTZydgC7DTUWvQ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Malik wants to know how wolves became pugs, poodles, and chihuahuas. Zooarchaeologist Angela Perri digs up the answers. Special thanks to Michael Worboys. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5rwitDrQbTZydgC7DTUWvQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1375</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Punches: How to Make a Knockout Sound</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4KLseXT2cbePucGzMsgeZJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Charlotte has been rewatching “The Sopranos” and the punches keep hitting her ear. Why do Hollywood wallops sound so punched up? Foley artist and Emmy Award-winning sound editor Joanna Fang shares her punch recipe. Plus, do real-life investigators actually connect the dots with red string and thumbtacks? Retired FBI agent Jerri Williams solves the evidence-board mystery. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4KLseXT2cbePucGzMsgeZJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1199</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scrabble’s Scramble to the Top</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7rURz0otr0kDMKX1SSU4fw?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Malenia wants to know how her favorite word game came to be. It turns out it took a while for Scrabble to score big. Stefan Fatsis, author of Word Freak, fills in the blanks. Plus, can you beat Flora's most embarrassing story? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7rURz0otr0kDMKX1SSU4fw</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1025</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Old is Winnie-the-Pooh?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5HhDOvwRJxcwYlOYWdprUb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We’re revisiting one of our favorite episodes this week. A few years ago, listener Annie asked ELT to settle a longstanding family debate: exactly how old is Winnie-the-Pooh? To hunt down an answer, we consult with professional age-guesser Ben Ramey, bear biologist Rae Wynn-Grant, and Sarah Shea, a professor who has studied this question. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5HhDOvwRJxcwYlOYWdprUb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1343</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Potatoes Took Over the World</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0SdOJ1FTuZABe2w3HyTT1g?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Taylor was making a medieval stew when she noticed a prominent ingredient was missing from the recipe: potatoes. Potato biologist Maria Scurrah and journalist Charles Mann explain the potato’s twisting route to stewpot domination. Special thanks to Graham Thiele, Bruce Owen, Alan Covey, and Gary Urton. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0SdOJ1FTuZABe2w3HyTT1g</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1079</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Does the Wind Make Me Angry?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0VjXzgMBjna7TCHrerM6UP?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Christina gets ruffled by a stiff breeze and wants to know if she’s alone in her wind rage. Atmospheric science historian Vladimir Jankovic introduces Christina to her people, and iconic couples therapist Esther Perel, host of “How’s Work” and “Where Should We Begin,” helps Christina rethink her relationship with the wind. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0VjXzgMBjna7TCHrerM6UP</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1236</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essential Workers 8 Months Later</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5ZFyCg1bc2viQmpA0wrmiE?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>How are essential workers doing now? We check in with some of the essential workers we talked to back in April and hear what it’s been like to teach, fly on planes, ship packages, and drive a truck during a pandemic. Thanks to Rob, Justin, Tamasha, Lucy, Jacob, Kaleb, Ian, and Dawn. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ZFyCg1bc2viQmpA0wrmiE</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1616</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Be Less Clumsy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2ry2dqmulJkGS8MwlvTMNr?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Gab is clumsy — white sweaters, stemmed wine glasses, and sharp edges are off the table. Can Gab learn to be less clumsy? Professional steady hand Bryan Berg and kinesiologist Priscila Tamplain share tips for foiling fumbles. Special thanks to Carl Gabbard and Michael Wade. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ry2dqmulJkGS8MwlvTMNr</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1053</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dirt on Houseplants</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/72BzS03nWTdqmVtuYKGB8j?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Attention all you #hortihotties, this week caller Esther asks about houseplants: When did we start keeping them, and has there ever been another houseplant heyday? Guests Catherine Horwood, author of Potted History, and Charlotte Salter-Townshend of the National Botanic Gardens in Dublin sift through the facts and expose the shady side of houseplant history.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72BzS03nWTdqmVtuYKGB8j</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1194</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crashing Your Most Memorable Meals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2t6K5KOWXVad6MHG6f7bn1?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, some comfort food. For a lot of us, the holidays won’t be the same this year. Instead of arguing around the table with our extended families, we’ll be stuck at home with a single-serving of mashed potatoes, face-timing the people we love. So we invited ourselves to your place. We asked you to tell us about a meal you can't forget. And you delivered. Your stories made us laugh, cry and get very hungry. Thanks to callers Margaret, Janae, Brandon, Johnny, Jameson, and Oz, and all of you who left us a message. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2t6K5KOWXVad6MHG6f7bn1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1294</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WTF Happened to My Pumpkins?  </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4sQW2kCjPdGARPr4GMfTHa?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Flora’s sister Ruth claims last year’s jack-o'-lantern seeds sprouted... a litter of decorative gourds. ELT gets to the bottom of this pumper stumper. Plus, a spooky Face ID mystery, and a peek under the husk of corn mazes. Guests: professor of horticulture and pumpkin expert Steve Reiners; farmer and corn maze designer Angie Treinen. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4sQW2kCjPdGARPr4GMfTHa</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1460</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Sparked That Wildfire?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3h2jvgsQ2Zv5jIqABp9dAJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Caller Sadera has a burning question: When there’s a wildfire, how do we figure out what caused it? Fire investigator Paul Steensland tells ELT what he searches for in the burnt landscape, and the clues that can lead him to the cause. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3h2jvgsQ2Zv5jIqABp9dAJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1179</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Do We Cry?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6BYapVmJfSe9vbTGx8hP9c?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Lily called in about a crying shame: She thinks she cries too much. ELT investigates why we cry, and whether wet cheeks were once très chic. Ad Vingerhoets, crying researcher and clinical psychologist, and Tom Lutz, author of Crying: The Natural and Cultural History of Tears, talk through tears. Listen to the episode then vote in the poll below to let us know if you’re a mighty mister. Voting closes on Monday, October 5, 2020. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6BYapVmJfSe9vbTGx8hP9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1252</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Your Pet a Righty or a Lefty?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1Fwv2C7XKxdzYMUKv3LaAN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Caller Juanita wants to know if her cats are southpaws. ELT calls in animal behavior researcher Deborah Wells and neuroscientist Sebastian Ocklenburg for an answer. Plus, why would slugs ditch the shell? Biologist Robert Cowie fills us in. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1Fwv2C7XKxdzYMUKv3LaAN</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1303</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frozen Food: How Long Is Too Long?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2KEy0ztYdPr6zu6jueWt6d?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>After their dad served 4-year-old fish for dinner one night, listener Max wants to know how long you can safely keep food in the freezer. Food safety expert Haley Oliver serves up the juicy details. Plus, can tiny eyes see things we can’t? Spider expert Sebastian Echeverri takes us behind some of the most impressive peepers in the animal kingdom. Thanks to listener Miles. In the original version of this episode, we made an error about the types of light jumping spiders can see. All jumping spiders that have been studied are able to see UV and green light. Some species, including Oregon’s paradise jumping spider, can see red as well. We apologize for the error and have corrected it in this version of the show.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2KEy0ztYdPr6zu6jueWt6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1318</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cards: Solving a Shuffle Kerfuffle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2MNXmrEavBCwFFbFvMqiKG?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listeners Marmie and Ryan have a quarantine quibble: How many times should you shuffle a deck of playing cards? Marmie says three, while Ryan says four or more. The couple place their bets and go all-in with applied mathematician Steven Strogatz and a full house of card-world VIPs. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2MNXmrEavBCwFFbFvMqiKG</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1427</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Is the Ocean Glowing? </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0PFLidMkkcOLtXgZTQ2lUA?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Erik saw a mysterious glow in the water during a trip to the beach, and he wants to know more. ELT talks to the “Jacques Cousteau of glow,” a scientist who has spent decades deep diving for answers. Guest: biologist and ocean researcher Edie Widder. Thanks to Eelke Dekker for the seagull and ocean sounds we used in this episode. Thanks also to Steven Haddock, Michael Latz, Matt Davis, Vincent Pieribone, and Severine Martini. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0PFLidMkkcOLtXgZTQ2lUA</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1202</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sand: What’s It Really Made Of? </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3jWsjlRvs3bwcUrD83Gn3W?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Caller Hank wants to know where the sand on his central California beach came from. ELT gets the surprising scoop on how beaches are born. Guest: Kiki Patsch, California State University Channel Islands. Special thanks to Gary Griggs. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3jWsjlRvs3bwcUrD83Gn3W</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1032</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F*ck Yeah: Can Cursing Make You Stronger?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6Gn9YBrcq1DFeK1Ux4Z55R?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Flora is out this week force feeding her niblings flamingo facts, so we’re rerunning one of our favorite episodes. Does swearing make you more powerful? Plus, we talk to someone who turns the “mother f*ckers” into “manhole covers” for the TV versions of movies. Guests: Cognitive scientist Ben Bergen, author of What the F***; Gwen Whittle, supervising sound editor at Skywalker Sound. Thanks to caller Mark for the monkey flippin’ question, and to Mark’s dad Steve.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6Gn9YBrcq1DFeK1Ux4Z55R</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1570</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stamps: Tiny Squares Full Of Secrets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/77OR0qsOkQAP1xLN7KV54a?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Flora is hosting the Chapped Cheeks Book Club this week, so we’re revisiting one of our favorite episodes: How do U.S. postage stamps come to be? ELT explores the secret world of the Citizens’ Stamp Advisory Committee, the group that decides what gets stuck on America’s envelopes. Guests: Bill Gicker, manager of stamp development at USPS; Jessica, ex-CSAC member; Kam Mak, artist and stamp illustrator. Thanks to caller Elizabeth. “Mr. Stampman” performed by Bobby Lord, Matthew Boll, MR Daniel, and Julia Kaplan. Mail your stamp idea to: Stamp Development / Attn: Citizens' Stamp Advisory Committee / 475 L’Enfant Plaza SW, Room 3300 / Washington, DC 20260-3501. Remember: One idea per letter! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77OR0qsOkQAP1xLN7KV54a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1624</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fruit Flies: Seriously, Where Do They Come From? </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7nVUF5Vwew9UauK2kSFOge?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Flora is away this week, so we’re revisiting one of our favorite episodes — about a summer visitor no one wants. Caller Jeremy has a problem: fruit flies have moved into his apartment, and he needs to know how they got there. ELT finds out where Jeremy’s freeloading flatmates came from. Guests: Biologist Marcus Stensmyr, Lund University. Chemical ecologist Kevin Cloonan, Acadia University, Nova Scotia, Canada. Thanks to Jeremy and all the listeners who shared their gnat knowledge. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7nVUF5Vwew9UauK2kSFOge</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1334</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Pompoms: Cheerleading’s Checkered Past</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7ue9yY4FXWFSujSACJq07Y?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Flora is away this week at a flamingo fanciers convention, so we’re revisiting one of our favorite shows — a two-part, deep dive into cheerleading. It’s not all smiles and ponytails. Guests: cheerleading researcher and professor at the University of Alabama Natalie Adams; Barbara Hazlewood; Sharita Richardson, cheerleading researcher, instructional coach at North Carolina A&amp;T State University, and founder of Black Girls Cheer. Thanks to caller Jessica for the question. Special thanks to Vonciel Baker, one of the original seven Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders and to Dee Brock, former manager of the Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ue9yY4FXWFSujSACJq07Y</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2258</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is a Sense of Direction a Thing?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2vdOULP7AKKP29QAlXQ98k?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Amy gets lost a lot. She wants to know if some people are naturally better at finding their way, and whether there’s hope for her. An expert locates some answers. Plus, how the best navigators in the world get around. Guests: navigation and orientation researcher Giuseppe Iaria; former London cab driver David Styles. Thanks to caller Amy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2vdOULP7AKKP29QAlXQ98k</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1091</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Squirrels Track Their Nuts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/00KA5rZRfZtrcMvQKtdBbj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The average tree squirrel can bury up to 10,000 nuts every fall. How do they keep tabs on that stash? Guest: animal behaviorist and pro squirrel watcher Mikel Maria Delgado exposes the secrets of squirrel pantry maintenance. Thanks to caller Cayra. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00KA5rZRfZtrcMvQKtdBbj</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>955</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Astronauts Come Home</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2SD4fjWLBSErvwISEIIXx1?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This weekend, SpaceX and NASA successfully launched the first crewed spacecraft from U.S. soil in almost a decade. Preparing for a mission to space takes astronauts years, but listener Daniel wants to know — what does the other end of that journey look like? What happens when space travelers come home? Guest: record-holding NASA astronaut Christina Koch. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2SD4fjWLBSErvwISEIIXx1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1518</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old Life, This One’s For You</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6p0R3GauycUt6msDFzJndt?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We’re celebrating the little things you miss from life before quarantine. Those small joys you can’t stop thinking about, in the midst of such big sadness. Thanks to listeners Ron, Sophia, Karen, Hayden, Priyanka, Melissa, Kim, Kai, Will, and everyone who called in to share, shout, and sob into the void. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6p0R3GauycUt6msDFzJndt</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2021</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream Your Way to a Better You</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0SCbTeDU4f0gMMQAoq5QzV?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Natalie had a dreamy question: can you change something in your waking life by dreaming about it? ELT talked to a lucid dream expert to find out if we can optimize our snooze time. Guest: Daniel Erlacher, sports scientist at the University of Bern, Switzerland. Thanks to Natalie for the call. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0SCbTeDU4f0gMMQAoq5QzV</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1217</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Jigsaw Puzzle Factory</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7M3CLtpnOv71GRztepOtiQ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In the time of “puzzle and chill,” listener Myco needs to know: how are jigsaw puzzles made? Plus, why are clouds of terrifying black birds gathering in listener Amanda’s neighborhood every evening? ELT puts the pieces together. Guests: Thomas Kaeppeler, President of Ravensburger North America, Inc.; bird expert Judith Bailey. Thanks to callers Myco and Amanda. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7M3CLtpnOv71GRztepOtiQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1283</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Holes: Free Your Mind</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/54MOmIQ9AVZlQ3I6D5ZXWo?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Are black holes really holes? In honor of 420, ELT takes a trip to black hole country. Thanks to caller Kyle. Guest: Clifford Johnson, professor of physics at the University of Southern California. Happy 420, dudes. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54MOmIQ9AVZlQ3I6D5ZXWo</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1286</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Did Prehistoric Parents Feed The Kids?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2Ka79RKDh5yH6dauC1BJ5C?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>If a baby couldn’t nurse, what did prehistoric parents do before baby bottles? Julie Dunne, a biomolecular archaeologist and pot lady, analyzed some adorable ancient artifacts to answer the question. Plus, a big day for niblings. Thanks to callers Kate and Michael. Guest: Pot lady Julie Dunne. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2Ka79RKDh5yH6dauC1BJ5C</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1200</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essential Workers Call In</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7LI7WAs930ZnC6s9vx0Z3Z?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Fear, pride, relief, anger — what’s it like for the people out working so the rest of us can stay inside? Listeners who deliver packages and stock shelves tell us how their lives have changed. Thanks to Jacob, Megan, Ian, Lucy, Tamasha, Justin, Kaleb, Jane, Dawn, Rob, and everyone else who called in. And a gigantic thank you to everyone risking their own health to keep the rest of us safe. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7LI7WAs930ZnC6s9vx0Z3Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2347</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is It Weird to Be Nice to Alexa? </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7jwbB62tTuMtN03MgDcUZ5?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Elizabeth always says “please” and “thank you” to her Google voice assistant, and her husband says she’s weird. ELT talks to former Alexa insider Daren Gill and expert in human-robot interactions Leila Takayama to find out just how weird Elizabeth is. Plus, we right a #noboe wrong. Thanks to caller Elizabeth. Guests: Daren Gill, director of product at Spotify; human-robot interaction researcher Leila Takayama; oboe player Marcus Phillips. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7jwbB62tTuMtN03MgDcUZ5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1381</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symphony Secrets: Dirt from the Pit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7tt3FiYYgfq0hUuFAnQVEo?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Does an orchestra’s triangle player get the same pay as a violinist? Do conductors ever fall off their podiums? Which section do the other musicians love to hate? ELT dishes symphony secrets from two orchestra insiders. Guests: violinist Akiko Tarumoto and conductor Rob Kapilow. Special thanks to Nathan Cole and danke schön to caller Laszlo. Correction: This episode has been updated to replace the #noboe music with oboe music. Additional thanks to Marcus Phillips for helping us right this wrong. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7tt3FiYYgfq0hUuFAnQVEo</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1428</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anesthesia and a Mysterious Chili Cheese Fry Craving</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5ycbjj3B4EN8Z8nRB50ytA?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>A troubling image of a flamingo family has the flam world in a frenzy. ELT’s resident flamingo expert tells us what’s really happening in that viral pic. Plus, listener Paul goes in for an appendectomy, and wakes up with a bizarre craving. What happened when he went under the knife? Guests: Flamingo expert Felicity Arengo and anesthetist Kate Leslie. Thanks to caller Paul. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ycbjj3B4EN8Z8nRB50ytA</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1225</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Police Sketch Artists Read Your Mind</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4AjsAMZJ7pwwuzaj8UX6N6?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>A police sketch artist reveals how she turns your fuzzy memory into a sharp drawing. Sketch artist Kelly Lawson from the Georgia Bureau of Investigation walks us through the process. Thanks to Gary Wells, Gil Zamora, and caller Lex. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4AjsAMZJ7pwwuzaj8UX6N6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1112</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Scrunchie Queen</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/19RnjcAwNJKV62UPKt30Lg?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Kate, a “hair is life” kind of person, asks about the invention that keeps her hair out of her face. Guests: Hair stylist and hair archaeologist Janet Stephens; Scrunchie queen Rommy Revson. Thanks to caller Kate. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19RnjcAwNJKV62UPKt30Lg</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1246</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drugs on Screen: A Prop Master Tells All</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3hb25lN2aq156FpLV1GO3T?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Emily is dying to know: what are actors actually using when they do drugs on screen? A prop czar takes ELT behind the scenes. Plus, a tribute to percussionist Emil Richards. Guest: prop master Lynda Reiss. Thanks to caller Emily. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3hb25lN2aq156FpLV1GO3T</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1381</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America’s Next Top Word</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0X93S8yVIi7Udo7FktdKoP?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We asked you, the ELT family, to share your favorite underutilized words -- words that you love and want other listeners to love too. And you delivered. Now, with your help, we want to get one of those words into the dictionary. A professional word nerd tells us which of your submissions have the best chance of making it into the big book. Guest: former Merriam-Webster Dictionary editor Kory Stamper. Thanks to everyone who called in with a word. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0X93S8yVIi7Udo7FktdKoP</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1543</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caveman Confidential</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1NPCtwqUBS7AzqH1ndPhqJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Did cavemen really carry clubs? Live in caves? Wear leopard-print one-shouldered dresses? Paleoanthropologists Melanie Chang and Genevieve von Petzinger help bust our biggest cavemen myths — and tell us what our ancestors were really like. Special thanks to caller Lauren, and to historian Matthew Goodrum. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1NPCtwqUBS7AzqH1ndPhqJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1239</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel Secrets: Airplane Seats, Cheap Gas, Dirty Toilets </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3mhA0dbO6JU0R6UTSuKwtD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We’re clearing out our inbox and answering some of your burning follow-up questions for our last episode of 2019. Guests: Captain Nick Anderson, retired Virgin-Atlantic airline pilot, Airline Pilot Guy Show; microbiologist Jenny Hayden, Cedar Crest College; Jason Torchinsky, senior editor at Jalopnik. Thanks to callers Mattie, Toku, Piper, Aviv, Meghan, Anna, Liz, Kathi and Carl. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3mhA0dbO6JU0R6UTSuKwtD</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1402</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can You Learn to Taste Better? </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4PKXfkWeOhNeiJBNGAyyiI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Caller Shannon is at a loss for words when it comes to describing her favorite vegetable -- corn. ELT enlists a professional food describer to help expand Shannon’s tasting vocabulary. Guest: sensory evaluator Gail Vance Civille of Sensory Spectrum. Special thanks to Shannon for venturing outside of her palate’s comfort zone. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4PKXfkWeOhNeiJBNGAyyiI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1368</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ever Felt Someone’s Pain… In Your Butt? </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5Dq3xnK6zMr088lBwl7ytH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Caller Lisa wants to know why her butt hurts whenever she sees someone else get injured. ELT finds out whether some people really can feel your pain. Guest: pain researcher Stuart Derbyshire. Thanks to queen of Chapped Cheeks Lisa, and to researchers Natalie Bowling, Melita Giummarra, Helena Hartmann, Marina López-Solà, Bridget Rubenking, Jamie Ward, Scott Vrana, and Jamil Zaki. May your cheeks be ever free — hashtag booboobottom. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5Dq3xnK6zMr088lBwl7ytH</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1585</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ants: Tiny Brains, Full Hearts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0zLj01o41mZ5PY3QxngEPJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Wendy Zukerman, host of Science Vs, has a burning question: Do ants help each other out? ELT goes down the anthole to find the antswer. Guests: ant researchers Erik Frank at Université de Lausanne and Christina Kwapich at Arizona State University. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0zLj01o41mZ5PY3QxngEPJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1616</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twinspiracies: The Truth About Twinspeak and More</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3pM0vaWJE6lpNB5yIS5cOs?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Do twins communicate in the womb? Can they read each other’s minds? ELT tackles listeners’ twin questions and investigates some burning twin-spiracies. Guest: Nancy Segal, psychology professor at California State University, Fullerton, and author of Twin Mythconceptions. Thanks to twins Kelly and Kristina, Reply All’s Phia Bennin, and everyone who called with twin questions. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3pM0vaWJE6lpNB5yIS5cOs</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1633</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinkholes: How Scared Should I Be? Plus, Amy Sedaris</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/27W9Cgf3wHY6Z68MmD9RkT?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>ELT tackles some animal, vegetable, mineral mysteries with special guest Amy Sedaris. Plus, caller Maria is troubled by a hole in front of her condo — will she be swallowed by the earth? And the scoop on spinach tooth. Guests: Comedian and rabbit expert Amy Sedaris; Jim Correll, plant pathologist, University of Arkansas; geologist and sinkhole expert David Wilshaw. Thanks to callers Anthony, Eddie and Maria.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27W9Cgf3wHY6Z68MmD9RkT</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1303</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiders: How Many Can There Be? </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4JxTK8orfPp5tszbyOmeR4?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>A mass spider invasion at his office left accountant Steven with a burning question: How many can there be? ELT does some spider number-crunching, and meets the man who discovered one of the largest spider gatherings on record. Guests: Freddie Gowin, retired park ranger, Lake Tawakoni State Park, Texas; Linda Rayor, arachnologist at Cornell University. Thanks to caller Steven. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4JxTK8orfPp5tszbyOmeR4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1385</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand Theft Water Lily</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2a9puHxWGYYd1wY2yd4i37?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Why would a garden-gloved thief lift a water lily from a botanical garden in London? ELT gets to the root of a rare plant heist. Guests: Carlos Magdalena, botanical horticulturist at the Royal Botanic Gardens, Kew, London, and author of The Plant Messiah. Nick Johnson, horticultural manager of Queen Elizabeth II Botanic Park, Grand Cayman. Thanks to caller Carl.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a9puHxWGYYd1wY2yd4i37</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1241</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nail Polish Naming: Who Does That?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1qMgggV8VwgRaDduDYcAO2?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>How do nail polish colors get their names? ELT digs into this FAQ, and finds out how painting our nails became a thing. Plus, an update on Jeremy’s reported fruit fly infestation. Guests: Fashion historian Suzanne Shapiro, author of Nails: The Story of the Modern Manicure; Suzi Weiss-Fischmann, co-founder and Brand Ambassador of OPI Products Inc., and author of I’m Not Really a Waitress; chemical ecologist Kevin Cloonan, Acadia University, Nova Scotia, Canada. Thanks to caller Olivia and all the callers who shared their gnat knowledge.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1qMgggV8VwgRaDduDYcAO2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1356</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alien Invasion: How Little Green Men Took Over </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/52IjGZYNWe0sUNnC5xKRY4?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Images of little green aliens are everywhere: Area 51, bongs, your ‘90s chain wallet. But why did we start depicting extraterrestrials that way? ELT uncovers the moment that beamed little green aliens into our homes (and hearts).Guests: sociologist of science Pierre Lagrange; Kentucky resident Bill Thomas; literature professor Roger Luckhurst.Special thanks to caller Willie. Thanks also to Sarah Scoles and Geraldine Sutton Stith. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52IjGZYNWe0sUNnC5xKRY4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1401</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Limbo: The Haunting Backstory of Getting Low</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3k0yAxh8awQPU0mnwg1s5C?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Where did the limbo first get off the ground? This week, ELT reveals how it went from funerals in the Caribbean to shag-carpeted basements across American suburbia.Guests: Performer, choreographer, and documentarian Sonja Dumas; and Shane Vogel, professor of English and Theater at Indiana University.Special thanks to listener Aurelia. Thanks also to Kieron Sargeant and Ray Funk.To hear the songs featured in this episode, head over to our Spotify playlist at elt.show/limbo. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3k0yAxh8awQPU0mnwg1s5C</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1417</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putting a Phantom Tune to Rest</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5HW40OdqacAScjAIhX8nhV?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Caller Austin had a fragment of a song stuck in his head, and he needed our assistance. ELT listeners help him name that tune and put this mystery to rest. Guests: Singer and songwriter Sondre Lerche. Thanks to Dave Heilman and all the listeners who tried to help Austin.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5HW40OdqacAScjAIhX8nhV</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>879</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Rid of an Earworm</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4UEhh3UkmiKsmu4JLebd3M?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>An earworm expert explains how to unstick that song that’s stuck in your head, and why it got lodged there in the first place. Plus, your earwormholes — the songs that transport you through time and space.To hear the songs featured in this episode, head over to our Spotify playlist. http://www.elt.show/earworm Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4UEhh3UkmiKsmu4JLebd3M</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1513</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fruit Flies: Seriously, Where Do They Come From? </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3LOh73DS6oBdJ37KU1Od1O?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Caller Jeremy has a problem: fruit flies have swarmed his apartment, and he needs to know where they came from. ELT finds out how Jeremy’s red-eyed roommates landed in his life. Plus, please help caller Austin name that tune. Guest: Biologist Marcus Stensmyr, Lund University. Thanks to callers Jeremy and Austin.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3LOh73DS6oBdJ37KU1Od1O</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1239</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Underestimate the Flamingo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3gPmcLS3mRQSjDVi9k1Spc?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>While they may look like dainty, dorky birds, flamingos deserve respect. Flora brings the flamingo facts, and launches ELT’s campaign to bring a flamingo mascot to professional sports.Guests: Comedian Prashanth Venkataramanujam; Producer Katherine Wells; Mascot maker Jennifer Smith of Avant Garb; Renbert Mortimer, creator of the University of the Bahamas mascot. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3gPmcLS3mRQSjDVi9k1Spc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1303</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA Treasure Chest: What Happens To Your Confiscated Stuff?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2BJDVyv5W5RRVNqFtqnV0B?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Every year the TSA confiscates millions of pounds of pocket knives, sunscreen and snow globes from airport travelers. Where does it all go? ELT investigates. Plus, tips for sneaking your weed onboard from a former TSA agent.Guests: Ex-TSA “Taylor”; TSA spokesperson Lisa Farbstein; surplus agents for the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania Patrick Knight and Mike Starr; press secretary for the Pennsylvania Department of General Services Troy Thompson. Thanks to caller Kimberly. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2BJDVyv5W5RRVNqFtqnV0B</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1328</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public Toilets: To Sit or To Hover?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/73Yvp8Gx2XrBdBYlpDWYB7?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>ELT answers an age-old question: When you have to use a public toilet, should you sit on the seat? A team of microbiologists weigh in. Plus, the rise, fall, and re-rise of cargo shorts. Guests: Microbiologist Jack Gilbert; comedian Prashanth Venkataramanujam; cargo pantsologist Joe Hancock; Wall Street Journal reporter Nicole Hong. Special thanks to caller Jenny and the biology experts we surveyed: Jason Tetro, William Schaffner, Chuck Gerba, Rob Dunn, Jenny Hayden, Steffanie Strathdee, Liz Scott, Kimberly Page, and Maria Gloria Dominguez-Bello. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73Yvp8Gx2XrBdBYlpDWYB7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1624</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseball and Organ Music: How’d That Happen? </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/05phn7Hmsf2eO78w6P0T6e?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>When did organ music and baseball become an item? ELT talks to some pro organ players to find out how organs and ballparks got together. Plus, meet Nancy Faust — the legendary organist who brought trolling to modern baseball music.Guests: Steven Ball, organist and Director of Sacred Music at The Oratory of St. Francis de Sales in St. Louis, Missouri; Josh Kantor, organist for the Boston Red Sox; Nancy Faust, retired organist for the Chicago White SoxThanks to caller Robert. Thanks also to Judy Scott.You can see a photo of Nancy's donkeys on twitter and instagram. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05phn7Hmsf2eO78w6P0T6e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1638</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Lurks Under Our Cities?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0oz4zMkaPFffm3Ip3Czlid?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>ELT goes underground to meet the creatures living in our subways and sewer systems. Plus, the 411 on another underground underdog: prairie dogs.Guests: Urban evolutionary biologist and rat expert Jason Munshi-South; animal behavioral scientist Jennifer Verdolin.Thanks to caller Jessica, and to all the listeners who demanded prairie dog facts.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0oz4zMkaPFffm3Ip3Czlid</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1336</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tooth Worms and Tooth Pullers: Dentistry’s Rotten History</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0nNLrSDCrnyCZljieBEA1y?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>For most of human history, tooth care has been pretty bare bones. How did we go from charlatans pulling teeth in a public square, to the modern dentist’s office? ELT exposes the roots of tooth care. Plus, meet the technician who makes movie stars’ teeth look terrible.Guests: Dental historian and retired dentist J. Henry Clarke; historian Richard Barnett. Thanks to callers Amanda and Tess for the questions.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0nNLrSDCrnyCZljieBEA1y</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1428</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F-ck Yeah: Can Cursing Make You Stronger?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6alLItrXhOG3RHzUNXBErj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Does swearing make you more powerful? Caller Mark’s dad thinks a well-timed “word of power” is the key to efficient yardwork. ELT asks a swearing expert about that theory. Plus, we talk to someone who turns the “mother f*ckers” into “manhole covers” for the TV versions of movies. Guests: Cognitive scientist Ben Bergen, author of What the F***; Gwen Whittle, supervising sound editor at Skywalker Sound. Thanks to caller Mark for the monkey flippin’ question, and to Mark’s dad Steve.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6alLItrXhOG3RHzUNXBErj</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1560</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pink for Girls, Blue for Boys — Why?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3JHOkvfIaD7L4HzOmJ9dHy?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Through the 1800s, babies in the U.S. were dressed in gender neutral clothing — you couldn’t tell the girls from the boys based on their outfits. So why did parents start color-coding their kids in pink and blue? Plus, ELT’s long quest to get a sports team to have a flamingo as their mascot is finally over… or is it? Guests: textiles and clothing historian Jo Paoletti; cultural historian of medicine, gender, and the body Hanne Blank; and Kuba Krzyzostaniak, Director of Fan Engagement for Forward Madison FC.Thanks to caller Elle Ve and Paige — and to scholars Elizabeth Sweet, Katherine Parkin, and Valerie Steele. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3JHOkvfIaD7L4HzOmJ9dHy</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1668</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cockpit Confessions: The Truth About Airplane Mode (and More)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1CBGNVUg1GPy0KC0x9GK7z?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>When you fly do you really need to put your phone in airplane mode? Should you fear the tray table? What’s happening in the cockpit while you’re fighting over the armrest? Two airline pilots answer your burning air travel questions. Guests: Pilot Sandy Williams of Skydive Deland; Pilot Nick Anderson of the Airline Pilot Guy podcast. Thanks to everyone who called in with their airplane questions.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1CBGNVUg1GPy0KC0x9GK7z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1549</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buried Treasure: How to Make the Most of Your Booty</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2l9HwxIv9FcZwvhLEt5Raj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>If you found millions of dollars worth of buried treasure, what would you do next? Take it to the bank? Sell it on eBay? Call 60 Minutes? ELT unearths the tale of the largest buried treasure ever found in North America. Plus, practical tips for dealing with newfound millions, and a nationwide treasure hunt, ELT-style.Guest: David J. McCarthy, numismatist.Special thanks to listeners Kurt, Elizabeth, Travis, Vicki, Nikki, Kimberly, Robert, and Rachel for helping us with our treasure hunt. And thanks to listener David for the question. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2l9HwxIv9FcZwvhLEt5Raj</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1576</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Pompoms: Cheerleading’s Checkered Past (Part 2) </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7w7hOuJXPCdN4g2rGKRHXJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Who decides what a cheerleader looks like? Or sounds like? In part two of a two-part episode, ELT digs into the complicated legacy of an American archetype.Guests: Natalie Adams, cheerleading researcher and professor at the University of Alabama; Sharita Richardson, cheerleading researcher, instructional coach at North Carolina A&amp;T State University, and founder of Black Girls Cheer. Thanks to caller Jessica for the question. Special thanks to Vonciel Baker, one of the original seven Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders and to Dee Brock, former manager of the Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7w7hOuJXPCdN4g2rGKRHXJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>966</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Pompoms: Cheerleading’s Checkered Past (Part 1)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/69BmyQxpgfTwmoELWO9xsc?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>How did one style of cheerleading come to dominate in so many American schools? In part one of a two-part episode, ELT flips through the history of cheerleading and meets the man who held cheerleading in the pompom of his hand.  Guests: Cheerleading researcher and professor at the University of Alabama Natalie Adams; Barbara Hazlewood; Thanks to caller Jessica for the question.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69BmyQxpgfTwmoELWO9xsc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1494</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Did Pants Become a Thing? </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3hZO0GPaKnpk4OZ3lrNZMu?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>While there’s some evidence clothes go back 170,000 years, pants are a relatively recent addition to our wardrobes. Why were pants developed and who wore them first? ELT unravels the surprising story of pants.   Guests: Artist and clothing researcher Ulrike “Rike” Beck; folklorist and historian Adrienne Mayor; artist and writer Emily Spivack. Thanks to caller “Elle” for the question.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3hZO0GPaKnpk4OZ3lrNZMu</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1249</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duct Tape MacGyver: The Sticky Secrets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1euJluajxysR6BWqE4a7YS?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Can duct tape really fix every little thing? ELT tests the limits — and gets to the bottom of a duct tape story that’ll blow your socks off. Plus, your most ingenious MacGyver stories. Guests: Daniel Munson, Senior Product Development Specialist at 3M; Gary LaRose, lodge owner and hunting guide on the Alaska Peninsula; Luke Miller, Anchorage-based pilot and guide. Thanks to callers Ian, Hunter, David, Whitney, Leanne, Stacie, Elena, Diana, Ashley, Lauren, Lucy —  and to all the listeners who shared their MacGyver stories.Got a burning question of your own? Call 833-RING-ELT. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1euJluajxysR6BWqE4a7YS</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1576</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forks: One Utensil’s Battle for Respect</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5M2OBQ28epJzCK7jrp6wXh?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>While spoons, knives, and chopsticks have been commonplace for centuries, forks didn’t make it to most silverware drawers until the mid-1800s. What took so long? ELT investigates.Guest: Darra Goldstein, food historian, cookbook writer, and founding editor of Gastronomica, Thanks to caller Nicole. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5M2OBQ28epJzCK7jrp6wXh</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1176</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseball and Organ Music: How’d That Happen?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1iNTVVBVHwBYADnWizZ1AN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>When did organ music and baseball become a thing? ELT talks to some pro organ players to find out how organs and ballparks got together. Plus, meet Nancy Faust — the legendary organist who brought trolling to modern baseball music.Guests: Steven Ball, organist and Director of Sacred Music at The Oratory of St. Francis de Sales in St. Louis, Missouri; Josh Kantor, organist for the Boston Red Sox; Nancy Faust, retired organist for the Chicago White SoxThanks to caller Robert. Thanks also to Judy Scott.You can see a photo of Nancy's donkeys on our twitter feed. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1iNTVVBVHwBYADnWizZ1AN</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1598</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thrift Store Smell: What Is It? Plus, Your Cleanspiracies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5v9XDBMGzYJnXdx2AfTyX7?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>ELT gets to the bottom of a familiar aroma -- thrift store smell. Why do thrift shops all smell the same? Plus, is washing your clothes better than freezing them? ELT investigates listener cleanspiracies with expert cleaner Jolie Kerr.Guest: Jolie Kerr, writer and host of Ask a Clean Person. Thanks to callers Theresa, Rachel, Jeremiah, Nikki, Vicki, Mark, Juliana, Ben and all the listeners who called in with cleanspiracies. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5v9XDBMGzYJnXdx2AfTyX7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1268</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waterphone: The Sound That Haunts Hollywood</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0msUN8YazfDgzdyXJuD7fA?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>One eerie sound has been haunting Hollywood movies — from Poltergeist to Jurassic Park to Let the Right One In — and 14 seasons of Unsolved Mysteries. ELT tracks down the source of the scary sound.Guests: Rayme Waters, daughter of the spookiest sound in Hollywood’s inventor; percussionist Emil Richards; composer Gary Malkin.Thanks to caller Marianna. Thanks also to Brooks Hubbert, who runs the waterphone business, and musician Lee Charlton. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0msUN8YazfDgzdyXJuD7fA</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1308</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stamps: Tiny Squares Full Of Secrets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5Z6duI27ZOWPInUxOwW2Mb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>How do U.S. postage stamps come to be? ELT explores the secret world of the Citizens’ Stamp Advisory Committee, the group that decides what gets stuck on America’s envelopes. Plus, Bigfoot gets his due. Guests: Bill Gicker, manager of stamp development at USPS; Jessica, ex-CSAC member; Kam Mak, artist and stamp illustrator. Thanks to caller Elizabeth. “Mr. Stampman” performed by Bobby Lord, Matthew Boll, MR Daniel, and Julia Kaplan. Have a question that needs answering? Call the ELT Help Line at 833-RING-ELT. See Kam's stamp here: https://twitter.com/eltshow/status/1089959537434681344 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5Z6duI27ZOWPInUxOwW2Mb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1624</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auctioneers: Why Do They Talk Like That?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3FuqyayDrKEaM8JNU6h59d?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Why do some auctioneers talk so fast? And what are they actually saying? ELT gets the low-down on auction talk from a professional auctioneer. Plus, pro-tips for developing your auctioneer chant. Guest: Junior Staggs, professional auctioneer. Thanks to caller Katie.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3FuqyayDrKEaM8JNU6h59d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1159</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🛩TSA Treasure Chest : What Happens To Your Confiscated Stuff? 💸</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1eDpMhxoC6IQ3cl7ZiyLmX?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Every year the TSA confiscates millions of pounds of pocketknives, sunscreen and snow globes from airport travelers. Where does it all go? ELT investigates. Plus, tips for sneaking your weed onboard, from a former TSA agent.Guests: Ex-TSO “Taylor”; TSA spokesperson Lisa Farbstein; surplus agents for the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania Patrick Knight and Mike Starr; press secretary for the Pennsylvania Department of General Services Troy Thompson.Thanks to caller Kimberly. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1eDpMhxoC6IQ3cl7ZiyLmX</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1106</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Egg the Only Nog? Plus, Discovering the 8th Continent</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5gBYJLcSBY55Joge8taMej?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>How did cold uncooked eggs become a festive beverage? Plus, coquito for the nogged out. And one of the first scientists to hoist herself into the treetops describes life in the canopy.  Guests: Chef and food writer J. Kenji López-Alt; Chef and Noshery.com founder Meseidy Rivera. You can find Kenji’s eggnog recipe here and Meseidy’s coquito recipe here. Biologist Meg Lowman, Director of Global Initiatives, Lindsay Chair of Botany &amp; Senior Scientist in Plant Conservation at the California Academy of Sciences. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5gBYJLcSBY55Joge8taMej</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1063</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pumpkin Spice: The Science Behind the Invasion. Plus, What’s the Next Big Flavor Fad?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4VY7li8zNpr7kwJlUOBpvX?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Why is pumpkin spice a thing? Flavor scientists explain why this particular combination is so appealing -- or not. Plus, how to make a new flavor, and ELT listeners pitch their ideas for the next flavor fad. Guests: Food scientist Kantha Shelke; flavor chemist Bill Aslanides.Thanks to caller Ally, and to flavor forecasters Hunter, Travis, Amelia, Kassy, Rachel, Brooke, Wyatt, Thomas, and to all the listeners who submitted ice cream ideas. Special thanks and congrats to Just Ani.Additional thanks to Michelle Gillespie of SPINS Research and to Genevieve Aronson of Nielsen Research.If you want to hear more about pumpkin spice, and flavor science, check out this episode of Science Friday. Thanks to our sponsor, Cole Haan. You can hear more of Flora and other Gimlet hosts in conversation at ExtraordinariesOnTheMic.com, produced in partnership with Cole Haan. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4VY7li8zNpr7kwJlUOBpvX</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1335</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garbage: What Did We Do Before the Bag? Plus, A Trash Bag Moonshot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2fZWiSQPFvCIP4uI2LtYUO?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>A Bulletin Board of Glory™ nomination from comedian Josh Gondelman takes ELT down a trashy rabbit hole, to a time before sanitation workers, when pigs roamed the streets. Plus, we meet the man who defied all odds to bring us the bag that cinches. Warning: Explicit.Guests: comedian and Last Week Tonight writer Josh Gondelman; trash historian Carl Zimring; engineers Steve Tallman and Dana Boyd.Thanks to our sponsor, Cole Haan. You can hear more of Flora and other Gimlet hosts in conversation at ExtraordinariesOnTheMic.com, produced in partnership with Cole Haan. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2fZWiSQPFvCIP4uI2LtYUO</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1174</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Bubblegum: What’s That Flavor? Plus, What’s the Deal With Turkey Eggs?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1tJHFSXZfoQFcfiJNJyclH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Where does bubblegum flavor come from? A bubblegum bush? A beaver’s butt? We track down the original bubblegum flavor formula, and find out what’s in there. Plus, why turkey eggs aren’t a thing.Guests: Philadelphia events expert Scott Bruce, confectioners Bob Boutin and Mauricio Bobadilla, turkey biologist James Dickson and birder Laura Erickson. Thanks to callers Arrie and Chiara, and also to Phillip Clauer and Christine Alvarado for their egg-spertise.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1tJHFSXZfoQFcfiJNJyclH</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1183</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Goldfish Swam Into Our Living Rooms. Plus, Best Pet Vocalist</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3WlT1onA0z5DgGIhnDhvCp?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>How did goldfish come to dominate our fish bowls and pet stores? We dive into the history of America’s favorite finned pet. Plus, the fanciest goldfish money can buy, and the best pet in a vocal performance. Guests: Katherine "Kasey" Grier, the pet historian; Dave Mandley, goldfish freak.Thanks to caller Liana, pet owners Kerry Ann, Stephanie and Diane, and all the listeners who shared their pet’s special talent. Additional thanks to Katrina Gulliver, Mary Mannix, Liz Thomas, James Rada, Prosanta Chakrabarty, Konrad Dabrowski, Zachary Sperstad, Andrew Simons, Loren Miller, Barbara Mable, Peter Hundt, Norman Stacey, Larry Cleveland, Margaret Thomas Koogle, Charles B. Thomas, Jim Bland, Stephen Eaton, and Mike Rice. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3WlT1onA0z5DgGIhnDhvCp</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1044</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old Graves: What Would You Find In There? Plus, the Scariest Creature Under the Sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2ImMkNo1WIJRMokG4eivoD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>If you dug up the graves of our founding fathers, what would you find? Tri-corner hats and puffy shirts? A grave expert fills us in on what remains. Plus, a terrifying sea creature that lurks in the waters off northern Australia.  Guests: Nicholas Bellantoni, former Connecticut State Archaeologist and author; jellyfish expert Lisa-ann Gershwin. Thanks to callers Brenda and Keira and all the listeners who shared their final wishes. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ImMkNo1WIJRMokG4eivoD</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1114</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Made ‘The Wave’ a Thing? Plus, a Mammal Mix-Up Made Right</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2riWgHX0yjg5LJo78UaDq8?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>When did “the wave” become a staple of stadium crowds? ELT talks to the professional cheerleader who first got fans out of their seats. Plus, the egg-laying mammal that is not a marsupial. We give monotremes their due.Guests: professional cheerleader “Krazy” George Henderson; weird-Australian-mammal expert Robin Beck.Thanks also to callers Leslie, Natalie, and Manuel.Got a burning question that needs answering? Call now: 833-RING-ELT. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2riWgHX0yjg5LJo78UaDq8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1058</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do You Need to Warm Up Your Car? Plus, a Teeny, Glorious Car Hack</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2zgOWFsr14z4AgTq5c0Kge?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Tucked into your car’s dashboard is a tiny arrow that points to the side of the car with the gas tank cap. Who came up with it? ELT tracks down the inventor of this tiny, brilliant car hack. Plus, do you really need to warm up your car?Guests: Automobile aficionado Jason Torchinsky of Jalopnik; gas tank-indicator arrow inventor Jim Moylan. Thanks to caller Jonathan, the listeners who shared their car-spiracies, and the car experts who answered our questions.Have a tiny but important invention you want to know more about? Tell us who belongs on ELT’s Bulletin Board of Glory™. Email us at elt@gimletmedia.com. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2zgOWFsr14z4AgTq5c0Kge</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1162</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T. Rex Roar: How Is It Made? Plus, Would Dinosaurs Taste Like Chicken?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6er51PHsmfrZ7KI2OabI3e?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>How did they make the dinosaur roars in the Jurassic Park movies? Flora talks with the sound engineers behind the bellows. Plus, ELT goes deep into the Mesozoic to find out what what dinosaurs looked (and tasted) like. Guests: Al Nelson and Pete Horner of Skywalker Sound; dinosaur expert Thomas R. Holtz Jr.; paleontologista Jingmai O’ConnorThanks to callers Gwen and Lilah and all the listeners who sent us dinosaur questions. Send audio of your animal star to elt@gimletmedia.com  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6er51PHsmfrZ7KI2OabI3e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1093</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheese: Why Do We Worship Rotten Milk? A NSFW History</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3rt0yCTZXrYcpFvuejcdoZ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>When did someone first see a cheese curd and think, “Yeah, I’m going to eat that"? ELT traces the delicious and X-rated history of cheese. Plus, a professional processed cheese maker on how to make the most of the dairy aisle.Guests: cheese biochemist and historian Paul Kindstedt; processed cheese expert Lloyd Metzger; and cicada killer wasp biologist Chuck Holliday.Thanks to callers Kurt and Judi. Have a question that needs answering? Call the ELT Help Line #(833) RING ELT. To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.media/OurAdvertisers.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3rt0yCTZXrYcpFvuejcdoZ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1064</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why One Horrible Sound Haunts Reality TV. Plus, Is That Bug Threatening Me? </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5hVL1c2XlK0jAWsU1oCV7v?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Who put the tension in reality TV? ELT tracks down the source of the nail biting-sound you can’t unhear. Plus, cicada killer wasps — a backyard horror story, turned intervention. Guests: sonic puppetmaster Rick Livingstone; cicada killer wasp expert Chuck Holliday.Thanks to callers Caitlin and Stephanie.Have a question that needs answering? Call the ELT Help Line #(833) RING ELT.  To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.media/OurAdvertisers.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5hVL1c2XlK0jAWsU1oCV7v</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1009</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cha Cha Slide: How One Uncle Changed Weddings Forever</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4WWwoYKSAUCX224WNOw4wK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>DJ Casper tells us the origin story of the Cha Cha Slide. Plus, The Nod’s Brittany Luse is astonished by the unreleased Cha Cha Slide Pt. 1.Guests: The Nod’s host, Brittany Luse; Willie Perry Jr. (aka DJ Casper aka Mr. C the Slide Man); former gym rat David Wilson; radio personality and actress La Donna “Tittle in The Middle” Tittle; and BBC Radio 1 host Scott Mills.Thanks to caller Rachael and line dance guru Kenny J.Have a question that needs answering? Call the ELT Help Line #(833) RING ELT.To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.media/OurAdvertisers. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4WWwoYKSAUCX224WNOw4wK</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1289</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Invented the Bloomin’ Onion? Plus, Biology’s Best Butt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3xwZnkxkIeYWTL33b8TfHZ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>ELT goes down under, to expose one of the most impressive butts in the animal kingdom. Plus, the multi-layered origin story of the Bloomin' Onion.Guests: Science Vs. host, Wendy Zukerman; Wombat specialists, Alyce Swinbourne and Julie Old; ELT producer and fried appetizer fanatic, Phoebe Flanigan; Outback Steakhouse co-founder Tim Gannon; chef George BarnesThanks to fact buddy Ivy.Have a question that needs answering? Call the ELT Help Line #(833) RING ELT.To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.media/OurAdvertisers Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3xwZnkxkIeYWTL33b8TfHZ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1029</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Do Dogs Say When They Bark?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5iaDcrOgnOjfWjv7CsGnO7?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Is it possible to interpret what dogs are saying when they bark? We have the tools to help you do some ruff decoding. Plus, listeners share their real-life, unconventional Lassie stories.Guests: Dog bark researchers Péter Pongrácz and Kathryn Lord; behavioral scientist Susan Friedman.Thanks to dog callers Jacob, Alan, Katie R., Katie K., and Oren — and to everyone who sent in their pet stories.Have a question that needs answering? Call the ELT Help Line #(833) RING ELT.To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.media/OurAdvertisers Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5iaDcrOgnOjfWjv7CsGnO7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1167</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WTF Do the ⏹ 🔼 ⏺ on My 👕 Tag Mean? </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6ufOTc29MGrrqMqyFIon8l?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Plus, koala fingerprints, lobster pee and other hot facts.There are mysterious symbols inside your tee-shirt -- do you know what they mean? ELT reveals the secrets of The DaLaundry Code. Plus, lobsters pee from their faces, and other cocktail party fodder from our fact buddy exchange. Guests: Symbol whisperer John Langdon; Pascale Florant of GINETEX; Patrick A. Ayers of Vartest Labs.Thanks to laundry caller Ellen, Fran Kozen of Cornell University’s College of Human Ecology, and to our fact buddies Josh, Angela, Greg, Olivia, Chad, Kathryn, Rachel, Amber, Ivy and Lia.  Have a question that needs answering? Call the ELT Help Line #(833) RING ELT.To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.media/OurAdvertisers Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ufOTc29MGrrqMqyFIon8l</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1459</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Spot a Spy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6tVvYuCjvNTWKnvkv91Jax?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Does that person sitting next to you on the airplane REALLY work in IT? Plus, a tribute to the bedazzled sausage of the desert southwest, and more fun with pirates.Guests: ex-CIA operative Robert Baer, gila meister Dan Beck, and lady pirate expert Laura Sook Duncombe.Special thanks to callers “anonymous” and Eric — and to all of the listeners who sent us pirate questions. Have a question that needs answering? Call the ELT Help Line: #(833) RING ELT.To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.media/OurAdvertisers  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6tVvYuCjvNTWKnvkv91Jax</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1170</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Genius of Birds: Live From the Aspen Ideas Festival</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7yo431rexIFIMVtOIGkD6y?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Some birds can fashion tools and create tiny works of art, so why do we always underestimate their bird brains? In this panel discussion, recorded at the 2018 Aspen Ideas Festival, Flora talks with writer Jennifer Ackerman and crow expert Alex Taylor about the genius of birds.  Guests: writer Jennifer Ackerman and New Caledonian crow expert Alex Taylor.Have a question that needs answering? Call the ELT Help Line #(833) RING ELT.To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.media/OurAdvertisers Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7yo431rexIFIMVtOIGkD6y</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1134</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clowns and Crows: Weirder and Scarier Than You Think</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/064wAHYJp1nCajTEGyP7H5?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>ELT goes into the mind of a crow to find out if scarecrows work. Plus, a look at how clowns protect their clown IP with fact buddy Prashanth VenkatGuests: Julie "Lovely Buttons" Varholdt; crow expert Kevin McGowan. Thanks to Bruce Johnson (aka "Charlie the Juggling Clown") and Alan Zerobnick (aka “Zerbo the Clown” and “The Shoemaker to the Clowns"). Thanks also to callers Brian and Jordan.Find a link to the clown egg photos on our show page, and on Twitter and Facebook.Have a question that needs answering? Call the ELT Help Line #(833) RING ELT. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">064wAHYJp1nCajTEGyP7H5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1058</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARRRRR Pirate Peg Legs Really A Thing?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3XsS8ZH53KKthozGT3l9Rt?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Pirate historian Laura Sook Duncombe tells us about the golden age of pirates. Plus, a tunnel follow up with Dr. Mole: where do the emergency exits in underwater tunnels go?Thanks to lady pirate expert Laura Sook Duncombe and tunnel afficionado Gary Brierley, aka Dr. Mole. Thank also to callers Captain Yarb and Kirsten. To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.media/OurAdvertisers Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3XsS8ZH53KKthozGT3l9Rt</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1109</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Babies Born With Tails?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5XdXyo5a8HTatvfIJBxzDI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Plus, learn how to lie like a dad.Guests: Fake parenting expert Adam Mansbach; belly whisperer Tamara Duker Freuman; bird-watcher extraordinaire Amar Ayyash. Special thanks to Nicolas, Marisa, and everyone who called in with their Old Dad's Tales.To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.media/OurAdvertisers Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5XdXyo5a8HTatvfIJBxzDI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1157</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is There a Secret Sixth Taste?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/32Fq0kMNpuiV71cPbTVuKJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Is there more to your taste buds than you thought? ELT tackles a fat question. Plus, a #yesflamingo campaign update.Guests: Richard Mattes, taste czar; Sarah Laskow, reporter for Atlas Obscura. Special thanks to caller Samantha. *Correction: The Vegas Golden Knights mascot is not, in fact, a golden knight. It is Chance the gila monster. Our apologies to Chance and fans for the error. To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.media/OurAdvertisers Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32Fq0kMNpuiV71cPbTVuKJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1023</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are You Living With a Psychopath?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5GRPIOsbxMwbiEJMLwvl2D?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Is your roommate trying to kill you? Learn how to spot the telltale signs of a psychopath.Guests: Jon Ronson, author of The Psychopath Test; cat psychologist Eva Waiblinger. Special thanks to caller Megan. *No animals were harmed in the making of this episode. To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.media/OurAdvertisers Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5GRPIOsbxMwbiEJMLwvl2D</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1157</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Invented the Scratch Ticket?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2n3vCB00B9kFLd8nYoxSRv?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Plus, a look at lottery history, and your strangest raffle winnings.Guests: Jonathan Cohen, lottery historian; John Koza, co-founder of Scientific GamesCallers: John Henry, D., Lisa, Megan.  Hear your favorite Gimlet shows LIVE at Gimletfest this June 16-17 in Brooklyn. Buy tickets at gimletfest.com.To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.media/OurAdvertisers Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2n3vCB00B9kFLd8nYoxSRv</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1251</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Does Popcorn Pop?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1AWLGZ5gyExWYpk4giMdko?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>A kid caller pops the question: How does popcorn pop? Plus, the uncomfortable truth about baby corn. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1AWLGZ5gyExWYpk4giMdko</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1030</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public Toilets: To Sit Or To Hover?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1nbj42Ladv640BZZvKsDjG?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Plus, how to pee in zero-G.To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.media/OurAdvertisers. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1nbj42Ladv640BZZvKsDjG</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1143</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Are Used Car Ads So INSAAANNNE?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6aDpqrwE1DJc0t6ZpS5Ypw?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>One man is to blame. Plus, vanity plates in the wild: IC A GR8 PL8.To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.media/OurAdvertisers Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6aDpqrwE1DJc0t6ZpS5Ypw</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1365</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underwater Tunnels: HOW?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7jsSEnAQFDHhDDbBnVySAr?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>How they get that tunnel under there. Plus, a centuries-old scientific debate: why ice is slippery.Guests: Dr. Gary Brierley (aka Dr. Mole), tunnel engineer, Dr. Miquel Salmeron, physicist at Lawrence Berkeley National Laboratory, Special thanks to callers Nikki and Erin.Check out the Terrifying Tunnel Video referenced in today's show. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7jsSEnAQFDHhDDbBnVySAr</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1081</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Dogs Have Belly Buttons?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5h5eDNtDEn1UV8I826Bz3L?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Plus, dog clothes: where did they come from?To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.fm/sponsors Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5h5eDNtDEn1UV8I826Bz3L</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1153</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Paid to Clap on TV</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6y1EK8p2E5zsGJI6aU0ZAT?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Listener Mack asked about the unfamous people who fill empty seats at the Oscars.To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.fm/sponsors Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6y1EK8p2E5zsGJI6aU0ZAT</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1198</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Does Music Give Us the Chills?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0NXGr5dFnk7oO9EMyp3l8y?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Why do we get goosebumps from music and other emotional experiences? Plus, the strangest things to give ELT listeners goosebumps.To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.fm/sponsors Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0NXGr5dFnk7oO9EMyp3l8y</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1279</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Old Is Winnie the Pooh?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1nwKoRUsIpA1yKJxvLaIRd?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>No, really - how old is he?To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.fm/sponsors Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1nwKoRUsIpA1yKJxvLaIRd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1370</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Would Happen to Your Body in Space?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4JOAEJ3GrdiLXUeCPfn1Qg?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Flora finds out what would happen if she stepped into the vacuum of outer space. Then, an (Earth) vacuum paradox to end all paradoxes: which came first, the vacuum or the carpet?To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.fm/sponsors Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4JOAEJ3GrdiLXUeCPfn1Qg</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1573</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are "Speed Enforced by Aircraft" Signs a Lie?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3FLmr2WuIWhqY8VaWtpN02?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>First, Flora uncovers a feud about butterflies. Then, a question from the Help Line about aircraft patrol.To find a list of our sponsors and show-related promo codes, go to gimlet.fm/sponsors. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3FLmr2WuIWhqY8VaWtpN02</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1275</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Bedtime is Killing You </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2L7oHvkL4fj9crTbwwypp6?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Flora stages a fact intervention with Prashanth. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2L7oHvkL4fj9crTbwwypp6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1081</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Voices Hiding in Your Favorite Movies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2w5YaF12bcWhAKwtjVoJcK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Invisible actors create worlds of sound in everything you watch - from Jaws to The Wire. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2w5YaF12bcWhAKwtjVoJcK</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1546</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Not Ruin Thanksgiving</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2MIMAbwvGlX5NGPnuUFSu8?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Tips for being the #1 guest in the history of the universe. Plus, prunes. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2MIMAbwvGlX5NGPnuUFSu8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1688</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invasion of the Self-Checkout Machines</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1GH0xDijMDCuPI8yLeb3SJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Self-service began in a Piggly Wiggly 100 years ago. How’d it become a way of life? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1GH0xDijMDCuPI8yLeb3SJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1323</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Case of the Missing Armadillos</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1avn717e8UX548GUXjXcsv?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Flora answers questions from the help line about an armadillo paradox and the DaVinci Code of pasta. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1avn717e8UX548GUXjXcsv</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1347</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bonus: Zombie Flamingo </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3yk5ZdQq05m0a9QGa9YL4n?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Flora continues to champion the flamingo. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3yk5ZdQq05m0a9QGa9YL4n</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>335</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six O'Clock Soundtrack</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3GAcVXBb5pn4pI5MNXpKk8?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>How TV news got a score. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3GAcVXBb5pn4pI5MNXpKk8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1272</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Killed Cargo Shorts?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/30043SO1i2vZ0TVmPxRx0L?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Flora and fact buddy Prashanth talk about spiders, which leads to a cargo short investigation.Listen to Gimlet's newest show, Uncivil, wherever you get your podcasts:Apple Podcasts | Overcast | Pocketcasts | Stitcher Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30043SO1i2vZ0TVmPxRx0L</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1432</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrity Crush with Bill Nye</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5vcG6tI6qLbL4hE68bju2k?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Bill Nye the Science Guy introduces us to an obscure historical figure. Plus, we revisit the eclipse. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5vcG6tI6qLbL4hE68bju2k</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1478</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ELT Help Line</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3KN3sh2ZJsoNNSJbD1QGgj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Flora and Katherine answer questions from listeners. ELT Help Line #: (347) 464-9626. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3KN3sh2ZJsoNNSJbD1QGgj</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1382</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chair, Misunderstood</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2XwyqVvdnNNwjdkx0q1BpF?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Learning to love a viral piece of furniture.Our Sponsors: Wordpress.com | Synchrony Financial | Casper Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2XwyqVvdnNNwjdkx0q1BpF</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1291</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dewey Decimal Drama</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/61MFACtq32aBneEpwEPN4K?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The trouble with the library cataloging system. Plus, slug-gate.Our Sponsors: Spotify | Synchrony Financial Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61MFACtq32aBneEpwEPN4K</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1307</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Underestimate the Flamingo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2c8VZHftpX2s08tQj1aBby?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Flora learns facts about the flamingo that change her. #YESflamingo  Listen to Mogul: The Life and Death of Chris Lighty, a hip-hop miniseries from Gimlet Media and Loud Speakers Network. Now available wherever you get your podcasts.  Apple Podcasts | Overcast | Pocketcasts | Stitcher Our Sponsors:   Ziprecruiter | Synchrony Financial | Hello Fresh | Sonos Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c8VZHftpX2s08tQj1aBby</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1272</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Society on Your Face</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0U4qyWOBiCmdEjf8R43tCH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Get to know your most intimate animal companions. They already know a lot about you.Listen to Gimlet's newest show, The Pitch, on Apple Podcasts or wherever you listen!Our SponsorsCasper – Get $50 towards any mattress purchase by visiting casper.com/elt and using promo code “ELT” | Synchrony Financial | WordPress – go to wordpress.com/ELT to get 15% off a new website Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0U4qyWOBiCmdEjf8R43tCH</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1078</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What the Government Stashes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7BKa6Rr6hywB38pBdXcrJz?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rummaging through the nation's attic to find out what the government stores and why.Our SponsorsPostmates - The app that can deliver anything from anywhere. Get $100 in Postmates delivery credit by downloading the app and using promo code ELT. New customers only.Ziprecruiter – Post jobs for free by visiting ziprecruiter.com/elt Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7BKa6Rr6hywB38pBdXcrJz</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1397</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Is an Activation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6LqB74PM0BTNO5Mg73Ufoq?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>A weird night in Dallas leads us to ask: what kinds of emergency systems are all around us?Our Sponsors eBay - Listen to their podcast, Open for Business wherever you get your podcastsEveryday Bravery by Prudential - Listen wherever you get your podcastsHello Fresh - Get $30 off your first week of deliveries visit hellofresh.com and enter promo code "ELT30"Virgin Atlantic - Listen to their podcast, The Venture, wherever you get your podcastsRealtor.com - Find your dream home before not-you does. Visit realtor.com/ELT. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6LqB74PM0BTNO5Mg73Ufoq</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1488</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Quest to Wipe Out a Virus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/65Ec3EP38o4po1UnFQMko5?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>What does it take to eradicate a disease from the planet? Plus, the horrifying hunting habits of weasels. Our Sponsors Casper – Get $50 towards any mattress purchase by visiting casper.com/elt and using promo code “ELT”WordPress – go to wordpress.com/ELT to get 15% off a new websiteRealtor.com – Realtor.com has more MLS listed homes for sale than any other national real estate app or site. Go to Realtor.com/ELT to learn more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65Ec3EP38o4po1UnFQMko5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1408</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Senate Whisperer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5dT4zNqUwG4FsrTkNvRokA?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>How rules can keep us from descending into chaos.Our SponsorsEbay - Listen to their podcast, Open for Business wherever you get your podcastsEveryday Bravery by Prudential - Listen wherever you get your podcastsZiprecruiter - Post jobs for free by visiting ziprecruiter.com/elt Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5dT4zNqUwG4FsrTkNvRokA</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1239</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hide Rug of the Plant World </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/26yTqXJa1pQBN1nQtwLLeV?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Producer Christine Driscoll meets an alleyway plant dealer and discovers an industry right under our noses.Our SponsorsEveryday Bravery - subscribe wherever you listen to podcasts Sonos - Sonos is a smart system of wireless speakers. To learn more go to sonos.comVirgin Atlantic - Listen to their podcast, The Venture, wherever you get your podcastsWordpress - To get 15% off your website go to wordpress.com/elt Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26yTqXJa1pQBN1nQtwLLeV</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1287</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapture Chasers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4epy52PdaOc81lG64UPEOb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>An event in August could bring millions of people to tears.Our SponsorsEbay - Listen to their podcast, Open for Business wherever you get your podcastsCasper - Get $50 towards any mattress purchase by visiting casper.com/elt and using promo code "ELT"Hello Fresh - Get $30 off your first week of deliveries visit hellofresh.com and enter promo code "ELT30" Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4epy52PdaOc81lG64UPEOb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1180</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello, We Are Every Little Thing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3MfsK9S6AkZLvO2r41JjIh?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Who invented pants? How did ‘pink for girls’ and ‘blue for boys’ happen? What do dogs say when they bark? If you have a question that needs answering, call the ELT Help Line at 833-RING-ELT or send an audio message to elt@gimletmedia.com. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3MfsK9S6AkZLvO2r41JjIh</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>115</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

