<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Forbidden Fruits with Julia Fox and Niki Takesh</title>
    <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/4iZGIW1kjyQ7QNgx9C1mSN</link>
    <description>Forbidden Fruits features no holds barred cultural commentary by Julia Fox and her co-host Niki Takesh, two influential, opinionated, and transgressive women with a keen understanding of the current intersection of pop culture, sex, and stigma. Through the course of the series, they will be treating taboo content and electrifying, culturally relevant guests with empathy and understanding in order to gain deeper insight into the controversial topics and figures featured.Subscribe now and never miss an episode of this Spotify exclusive series!</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8a5cabfdd470b342018af4e003</url>
      <title>Forbidden Fruits with Julia Fox and Niki Takesh</title>
      <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/4iZGIW1kjyQ7QNgx9C1mSN</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:47:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>FKA Twigs, the Most Wholesome Icon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2YuBc8yk7Bp99BBtlTdAsy?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Aside from being a bondage toting, pole dancing, London-based singer-songwriter that has made a Stan out of everyone here at Forbidden Fruits, there are also things about FKA twigs that are not common knowledge. For example, she happens to be one of Niki's best (and most wholesome) friends. Tune in to hear how they met, what they've been through together, and how Twigs is dealing with the challenges of her career. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2YuBc8yk7Bp99BBtlTdAsy</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3787</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caroline Calloway, the Engima</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3EPLGM4QxorMwtyApjsfot?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Is Caroline Calloway an influencer, a writer, a skincare saleswoman, a creativity coach, or just a low-down scammer? We have no clue. One thing is for certain though, Caroline Calloway likes rich bitch things. Answering a question is clearly NOT a rich bitch thing. Luckily, we were able to trick her into answering a few. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3EPLGM4QxorMwtyApjsfot</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3111</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Danielle Miller, the Horace Mann Swiffer Girl</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6IlbK1uuhmt94rKIPvQMVf?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today’s story started back in 2004, before “going viral” became something to aspire toward. The now alleged scammer and convicted felon, Danielle Miller, was a 13 year old girl who sent her crush videos of herself masturbating with a Swiffer mop. Of course the video circulated the school and before long, Danielle was known as the Swiffer Girl. On this episode, Julia and Niki learn how going viral has affected Danielle's life and how it relates to her current run-ins with the law. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6IlbK1uuhmt94rKIPvQMVf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4175</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carrie White, the First Lady of Hairdressing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6rS2BUQfBHf7RyQwlI9Ii0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>All of you will not have heard of Carrie White, but to list Carrie's credentials would be a lot like playing hopscotch on the Hollywood Walk of Fame and reading out all the names you step on. With a life as crazy as Carrie's, it comes as no surprise that her best selling memoir "Upper Cut" is now being developed into a biopic starring none other than our very own Julia Fox. Tune in to hear some of the wild stories that may (or may not) find their way into the pic. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6rS2BUQfBHf7RyQwlI9Ii0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3011</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexis Haines, the Pretty Wild Icon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4sa18BHBOdOkSbAGCD8DHO?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Our millennial listeners will almost certainly know the name Alexis Neiers, but even the younger among us must have been living under a rock to have missed the viral video of Alexis leaving a series of sobbing messages on journalist Nancy Jo's voicemail. Alexis' teenage years were "Pretty Wild" indeed as she struggled with drug addiction and a high profile lawsuit for being involved in a bling ring that robbed celebrity's homes. However, the Alexis you will hear today has changed in ways far more profound than her last name. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4sa18BHBOdOkSbAGCD8DHO</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3709</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anna Delvey, the German Heiress</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/59YwpIzzPJbViR59oIkWZP?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On this long awaited episode, Julia and Niki call into Orange County facility to talk to the fake German Heiress that took the media by storm: Anna Delvey. Although she was released from Rikers Island in 2021, she was picked up by ICE soon thereafter for overstaying her VISA. In the meantime, Netflix has released a series based on Anna's story and the media has been raving about her friendship with Julia. So we decided to set up a call to check in with Anna and to ask her all the burning questions. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59YwpIzzPJbViR59oIkWZP</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3238</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chloe Cherry, the Euphoria Phenom</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5RKXh22C6QnwqWoMwGeL4a?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>When season 2 of HBO's Euphoria dropped, it was one character in particular that stole the viewers' hearts: Faye. As a former adult actress with more than 600 scenes to her name, Chloe Cherry proved that she doesn't need to get naked to wow an audience. Julia and Niki talk to the new found superstar to learn more about her past and her transition into television. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5RKXh22C6QnwqWoMwGeL4a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2817</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lydia Dupra, the Heaux Mentor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5hEAE3XkHh2rF5zG6Z8KEG?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On this episode, we talk to Lydia Dupra a.k.a. the Heaux Mentor. A sex worker turned entrepreneur that launched Heaux Cosmetics, a line of cosmetic products that contains oxytocin and other chemicals that mimic the effect of pheromones. Aside from running a successful business, the Heaux Mentor offers free advice and mentoring to sex workers that are trying to navigate the industry. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5hEAE3XkHh2rF5zG6Z8KEG</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3455</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zola, the Story Savant</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1IBSEQxKpIIHbaM0t4BI3s?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Julia and Niki sit down with the one and only Zola, the Detroit stripper that went viral when she told the story of her "hoe trip" to Florida in a 148-tweet thread. The story, told in a way only Zola could have, caused such a stir that it drew the attention of filmmakers the likes of James Franco and A24. Deciding to partner up with the latter, Zola is now credited an executive producer of her self-titled movie and is showing no signs of slowing down any time soon. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1IBSEQxKpIIHbaM0t4BI3s</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3722</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benita Alexander, the Love Conned Power Woman</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/62quIRIR3wDDwPl6aLB6Q1?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Julia and Niki sit down with Benita Alexander, an award winning producer who fell victim to one of the most outrageous love scams of our time. Her relationship with the Italian "super surgeon", Paolo Macchiarini started off as something out of a fairytale, but things took a turn for the worst just weeks before the wedding. What follows is a plot that involves the Pope, a trip to Barcelona, and a back seat full of wine. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62quIRIR3wDDwPl6aLB6Q1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3358</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ILoveMakonnen, the Queer Trailblazer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6uoutIObE07OJ3fpv7YXZ3?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In 2014, ILoveMakonnen took the club by storm with his mega hit "Tuesday". Although he seemed to have solidified his succes by signing to OVO Sound that same year, the relationship proved to be short lived. He left the label in 2016 and never rose to the prominence he seemed destined for. On this episode, Forbidden Fruits check in with Makonnen to see how his life has changed since his big succes and what his views are on queer culture within the industry. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6uoutIObE07OJ3fpv7YXZ3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4106</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azriel Clary, an R. Kelly Survivor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/68ZDw0QqnjpurWs7m5HCmW?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>While R. Kelly is found guilty on 9 counts and is facing life in prison, Forbidden Fruits sits down with the 23 year old Azriel Clary who had been with the R&amp;B singer from the time she was 17 until she was 22. Azriel, who first went public by defending R. Kelly in an interview with Gayle King in 2019, came back two years later to admit that she was coached and manipulated into defending him. On this episode, we check in with Azriel to see how her life has changed since she reclaimed her individuality. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68ZDw0QqnjpurWs7m5HCmW</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2906</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ava Louise, the Messy Legend</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1UARcw5YanqiGORh495tgm?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Julia and Niki sit down with Ava Louise, a clout culture queen that has mastered the art of trolling like none other. Faithfully giving us at least one annual scandal since 2019, the self proclaimed sociopath is back with another juicy story, this time involving NFL Hall of Fame wide receiver Antonio Brown. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1UARcw5YanqiGORh495tgm</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4047</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind The Scenes with Julia Fox</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5MnXLWHFgzGEZ51gECy9Vu?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today, we come to you with a PSA that can't wait til Friday! Julia has been all over the internet this week, so it's only right for her to address some of the controversies and set the record straight. From a hotel room in LA, Julia talks about her romance with Ye and sends a heartfelt message to her ex-husband, Peter. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5MnXLWHFgzGEZ51gECy9Vu</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1635</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natassia Dreams, the Black Trans Queen</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1eUxxnVWrhh8GzijU8hceD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On this episode of Forbidden Fruits, Julia and Niki have a talk with Natassia Dreams, one of the world first black transsexual adult actresses. We discuss transitioning, her early days as a sex worker, her experiences with Ballroom culture, and the challenges she has faced as a black trans woman in the adult industry. In short, an episode you definitely would not want to miss! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1eUxxnVWrhh8GzijU8hceD</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3642</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Happenings, a 2021 Recap</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/58xKoxaIUlykzwDj0KQbPT?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Sure, 2020 was an unusually crazy year. And while the virus spread, so too did the expectation (or should we say hope) that 2021 would somehow be better. But was it? Hear what Julia and Niki have to say as they recap the events that were most memorable to them, along with some of their personal experiences - all in PERFECT chronological order. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58xKoxaIUlykzwDj0KQbPT</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2671</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jane Doe 15 vs. Jeffrey Epstein Pt.2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3Zk2DJv6B0wgvep4MFLq51?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>As we continue our conversation with Jane Doe 15, we talk about her experiences in court, her thoughts on Ghislaine Maxwell - who at the time of writing, is being tried for her involvement in this case - and the process of her recovery.CONTENT WARNING: This episode discusses adult subject matter, including descriptions of sexual abuse of a child, and is intended for adult consumption only. Listener discretion is advised. If you have been affected by sexual violence, free, confidential support is available 24/7 through RAINN's National Sexual Assault Hotline at 800.656-4673 and online.rainn.org. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3Zk2DJv6B0wgvep4MFLq51</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2823</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jane Doe 15 vs. Jeffrey Epstein Pt.1</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2xK4e61X3AotM1EBZ8eNMj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In 2020, the Netflix documentary "Filthy Rich" laid bare the egregious crimes committed by powerful financier Jeffrey Epstein, who allegedly took his own life after being found guilty on a number of counts in 2019. This week, Forbidden Fruits sits down with one of Epstein's survivors whose testimony helped put him in jail.CONTENT WARNING: This episode discusses adult subject matter, including descriptions of sexual abuse of a child, and is intended for adult consumption only. Listener discretion is advised. If you have been affected by sexual violence, free, confidential support is available 24/7 through RAINN's National Sexual Assault Hotline at 800.656-4673 and online.rainn.org. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2xK4e61X3AotM1EBZ8eNMj</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2581</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Niki Takesh, the Co-host With The Most</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/48tUywBvkOOkm5Mr0Dx2OF?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Those that have been listening to Forbidden Fruits know that our guests are some of the most fascinating people with the wildest stories. This episode is no different, save for the fact that this week, our guest is none other than our very own Niki Takesh! Listen in to learn how Niki rose to influencer-like fame in a pre-social media era, and how a rock and roll lifestyle has shaped her to be an ideal host for a show like Forbidden Fruits. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48tUywBvkOOkm5Mr0Dx2OF</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3279</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat Marnell, the HOT Mess</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0rARJJ9CKwm9YfTWsakxb9?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Julia and Niki chat with the New York legend who famously quit her job by writing "I couldn’t spend another summer meeting deadlines behind a computer when I could be on the rooftop of Le Bain looking for shooting stars and smoking angel dust with my friends..". The one and only Cat Marnell. Tune in to learn how this New York Times best selling author that once refused to get clean, did just that.Find Cat Marnell on Patreon. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0rARJJ9CKwm9YfTWsakxb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2728</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leah McSweeney, the Realest Housewife</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0L4XY2tNf0aLMbYx2RCCpp?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On this week's Forbidden Fruits, Julia and Niki chat with the Downtown legend and RHONY superstar, Leah McSweeney. We talk addiction, love life, and of course a whole bunch of RHONY. So if you want to know who Leah's least favorite housewife is, or how she turned a violent and bloody run-in with the NYPD into a successful clothing brand, make sure you check out this week's episode! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0L4XY2tNf0aLMbYx2RCCpp</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2910</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michele Hatchette, a NXIVM loyalist</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6EWklguFkkcnsC192XPL9o?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Julia and Niki sit down with Michele Hatchette, a former member of the controversial NXIVM cult and one of the women that joined DOS, the secret society that formed within NXIVM. Despite statements from her own friends claiming to be sexually abused, and the subsequent life sentencing of Keith Raniere, Michele has not denounced Raniere or the practices within DOS. She even formed a group called The Dossier Project through which she (and 7 other former members of DOS) are trying to “set the record straight”. Listen to her side of the story as Julia and Niki ask all the hard hitting questions in this week’s episode of Forbidden Fruits.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6EWklguFkkcnsC192XPL9o</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2430</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Forbidden Fruits with Julia Fox and Niki Takesh</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0xcOLc7vFi8CquobSwOBoM?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Since the inception of the original sin, the tree of sweet and juicy taboo has held its fruit over the heads of mankind. But much like the valiant individual that dared to take that first bite of durian, the world needs curious rebels to move us forward. Rebels like Julia Fox and Niki Takesh. Two influential, opinionated, and transgressive women with a keen understanding of the current intersection of pop culture, sex, and stigma. So if unadulterated opinion and juicy tea is your...well, cup of tea, subscribe to Forbidden Fruits with Julia Fox and Niki Takesh now to hear the first episode on October 28. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0xcOLc7vFi8CquobSwOBoM</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>60</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

