<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Jemele Hill is Unbothered</title>
    <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/1SXD1U55jqbK9HHoPvdbsw</link>
    <description>Emmy Award-winning journalist and Webby Award winner Jemele Hill shares her unbothered, nuanced opinions on news, pop culture, politics, and sports. She also conducts intimate interviews with some of the biggest names and most thought-provoking contributors to culture, music, and entertainment. New episodes air every Monday.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8aa89a9cec947c00d37c35210f</url>
      <title>Jemele Hill is Unbothered</title>
      <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/1SXD1U55jqbK9HHoPvdbsw</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:48:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 186: COCO JONES - Winning But Not Approved</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6eOO1w4Ge1coazMe1NucvI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Multi-talented star Coco Jones joins Jemele to discuss what she wanted to bring to her role as Hilary Banks on the hit show Bel-Air, and why she didn’t initially believe she could play Hilary. Coco also reveals what prompted her to record a YouTube video in which she shared the reasons her acting career didn’t kick into high gear following her Disney stardom, and how tricky navigating Hollywood can be. Plus, she discusses her new single, “Caliber,” and what she hopes to achieve in her musical career. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6eOO1w4Ge1coazMe1NucvI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3679</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 185: CASSANDRA FREEMAN - One Take For Me</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3FJ08uuRre1hg0Pmyb0xfG?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Cassandra Freeman joins Jemele to discuss her role as Vivian Banks, also known as Aunt Viv, on the hit television series Bel-Air. Cassandra shares what she wanted to bring to the dramatic version of Aunt Viv, and how she felt about the audience’s initial reaction to the show being reimagined. Cassandra also opens up some difficulties she experienced during her pregnancy, and the challenges black women face in seeking proper maternal health. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3FJ08uuRre1hg0Pmyb0xfG</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4661</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 184: D-NICE - The Power of Music</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5hje88e9bWVNYodc3zUR4N?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>World-renown DJ D-Nice joins Jemele to discuss what it meant to perform at this year’s Academy Awards, and how it aligned with the broader vision he’s always had for his career. D-Nice also shares what inspired him to start Club Quarantine, the social media phenomenon that exploded during the height of the quarantine and amplified his profile. He explains why he never commercialized Club Quarantine as it grew in popularity, and how he reacted the night former First Lady Michelle Obama made an appearance in his virtual nightclub. Plus, Jemele shares her thought on the Will Smith-Chris Rock debacle at the Oscars and why she’s tired of the wrong people complaining about high gas prices. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5hje88e9bWVNYodc3zUR4N</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4861</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 183: SYDNEY CARTER - Stepping on Necks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/60bLvTQIQ5PHHlRx2huMlt?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Sydney Carter, a player development coach and assistant recruiting coordinator for Texas A&amp;M’s women’s basketball team, joins Jemele to discuss the game-day outfit that turned her into a viral star. Sydney discusses how she handled the criticism as well as the sudden fame. She also shares her basketball origin story, and what it was like playing overseas in Latvia and Israel. Plus, Jemele has some strong words for the Republicans who came after Supreme Court nominee Kentanji Brown Jackson. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60bLvTQIQ5PHHlRx2huMlt</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4200</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 182: SHERYL LEE RALPH - A Real Diva Thrives</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/36RPFmPiFFNICtTg27asNM?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The multi-talented Sheryl Lee Ralph joins Jemele to discuss her role as Barbara Howard on the hit television show, Abbott Elementary. She also discusses her close relationship with Abbott Elementary creator and star, Quinta Brunson, and why this comedy has become such a smash success. Sheryl also shares her memories of the late Sidney Poitier, and how she’s successfully navigated Hollywood in her 40-plus year career. Plus, Sheryl reflects on her starring role as Deena Jones in Dreamgirls, the Broadway musical that led to the film adaptation in 2006. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36RPFmPiFFNICtTg27asNM</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4954</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 181: AUNJANUE ELLIS - I Don’t Know How To Be Anything Else</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4hqm87flWP9jOwkfHVfrFH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Aunjanue Ellis joins Jemele to discuss her Mississippi roots, and what led her to an acting career. Aunjanue also discusses what it means to be nominated for an Oscar for her outstanding performance in King Richard. She also shares why she chooses her roles with such intentionality, and why she waged a campaign to pressure the state of Mississippi into removing the confederate emblem from the Mississippi state flag. Plus, Jemele shares her thought on director Ryan Coogler’s false arrest. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4hqm87flWP9jOwkfHVfrFH</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4148</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 180: AMBER RUFFIN - From Hardest to Easiest</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2t9LtKnadp8UUTi0Zn79rc?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Amber Ruffin joins Jemele to discuss how she puts together her hit show, The Amber Ruffin Show, and why she chose not to have a talk show that included celebrity guests. Amber also discusses what it was like growing up in Omaha, Nebraska, how she got into comedy, and where she believes her career would be had she not been rejected as a Saturday Night Live cast member. Plus, Jemele shares her thoughts on how the media has failed in its coverage of the Russia-Ukraine conflict. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2t9LtKnadp8UUTi0Zn79rc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3963</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 179: TABITHA BROWN - Just Being Tab</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1wHNnU8H3jmlozQYIIq5q3?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Social media star Tabitha Brown joins Jemele to discuss her unique path to stardom, which started with a viral social media video about a vegan sandwich from Whole Foods. Tabitha discusses the many ups and downs she experienced as she struggled to make a career in the entertainment business. She also shares why she’s resonated with millions on social media, how becoming vegan saved her life, and how her faith has perfectly positioned her to handle success. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1wHNnU8H3jmlozQYIIq5q3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3904</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 178: CORI BUSH — The Politivist</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3AtZfixzS9a9zwm0mFvZmf?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>U.S. Congresswoman Cori Bush joins Jemele to discuss why securing voting rights is crucial to American democracy, and why she’s unwilling to abandon her activist mentality despite being in politics. Cori also explains how her humble beginnings, and being involved in the Ferguson protests led her to politics. Plus, Jemele also shares her thoughts on the hip-hop themed Super Bowl halftime show. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3AtZfixzS9a9zwm0mFvZmf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3366</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 177: STORM REID - The Light in the Darkness</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1Qc3dsmnjF3KFZXG6Ea8xI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rising star Storm Reid joins Jemele to discuss her already-prolific acting career, which includes starring roles in the blockbusters A Wrinkle in Time, and Suicide Squad. Storm also discusses her role in the hit HBO series Euphoria, her close relationship with Zendaya, and the auntie community she’s formed with Oprah Winfrey and Ava Duvernay. Storm also shares her insights on Generation Z, and why her generation seems to draw better boundaries than previous ones. Plus, Jemele has thoughts on the embarrassing performative gestures that have been made during Black History Month. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1Qc3dsmnjF3KFZXG6Ea8xI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4367</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 176: YAA GYASI - The Pressure Never Left</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4zhuoCuSN49u4rKAm0Jlia?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Novelist Yaa Gyasi joins Jemele to discuss her award-winning novel Homegoing and her highly-acclaimed follow-up project, Transcendent Kingdom. Yaa also shares how her passion for writing began, her creative process and how she established and maintained her close connection with her Ghanaian roots. Plus, Jemele shares her thoughts on polarizing podcast personality Joe Rogan. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4zhuoCuSN49u4rKAm0Jlia</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4722</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 175: RACHEL LINDSAY - I Came Here To Fly</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2ImcpqpU9tikNFWs5NrYwU?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Former Bachelorette Rachel Lindsay joins Jemele to discuss her new book, “Miss Me With That,” a collection of wide-ranging personal essays that cover pivotal moments in Rachel’s life. Rachel opens up about the fallout from her interview with former Bachelor host Chris Harrison and why she decided to step away from the Bachelor franchise. Rachel also discusses the criticism she’s received for being in an interracial marriage, why she chose to pursue a law career, and what it was like having a father who was a federal judge. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ImcpqpU9tikNFWs5NrYwU</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5005</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 174: PATRISSE CULLORS - A Courageous Conversation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3up9C38xXb3mbGNWrcqjSQ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Activist and artist Patrisse Cullors joins Jemele to discuss her departure from Black Lives Matter, the movement she co-founded in 2013. Patrisse shares how the constant barrage of right-wing attacks impacted her mental health, how she’s handled death threats and criticism from others within the black community. Patrisse also discusses her latest book, “An Abolitionist’s Handbook: 12 Steps to Changing Yourself and the World.” Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3up9C38xXb3mbGNWrcqjSQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4462</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 173: BREE NEWSOME BASS - Abolition for the People</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3YNRiN7WrNaax9UihBgdy0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Activist and organizer Bree Newsome Bass to discuss what inspired her to courageously climb the flagpole outside South Carolina’s state capitol and take down the Confederate flag that flew there. Bree also shares why she was drawn to activism, why she supports abolishing the police and how reality television became her guilty pleasure. Plus, Jemele and her friend, sports columnist Carron Phillips, debate and discuss the series finale of Insecure. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3YNRiN7WrNaax9UihBgdy0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5386</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EP 172: STEPHAN JAMES - Listen Rather Than Receive</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/34a3wVX39ljWpLfWnbfAe4?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Stephan James joins Jemele to discuss his new hit movie, “National Champions,” which explores player exploitation in college football. Stephan reveals what drew him to the project, and how he hopes college football players will receive the movie. He also discusses his relationship with the late Chadwick Boseman, and why he believes it’s an inspiring time for black men in Hollywood. Plus, he reveals the famous television character he’s named after. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34a3wVX39ljWpLfWnbfAe4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4193</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jemele's Holiday Message</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6DguWqM7me5UUIxAKCTefT?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p> Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6DguWqM7me5UUIxAKCTefT</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>70</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 171: NICOLE ARI PARKER - The Fabulous Woman with Three Names</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/21zU4AbkSXbzV7siXrCL45?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actress Nicole Ari Parker joins Jemele to discuss her role in the Sex and the City reboot, including the significance of the show adding several women of color to the cast. Nicole also discusses her starring role in the upcoming movie Safe Space, which was directed by her husband, Boris Kodjoe. She shares what it was like working with him, and reminisces about how the two met on the television drama “Soul Food.” Plus, Nicole opens up about the fears she has raising her teenage son in this racial climate. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21zU4AbkSXbzV7siXrCL45</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3528</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 170: MC LYTE — Godmother of Hip Hop</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4qZDy3BibMLbI5kjdrtKzT?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Hip hop legend M.C. Lyte joins Jemele to discuss her groundbreaking hip hop career, how attending an African-centered school growing up gave her a sense of self-awareness and made her stronger in her identity, and how the poetry she wrote became the foundation for many of her lyrics. Lyte also relives what it was like recording the remix and shooting the video for the iconic song, “I Wanna Be Down,” which also featured fellow rappers Yo-Yo and Queen Latifah. Plus, Lyte also discusses her new sitcom, “Partners in Rhyme,” which she co-created and is executive producing. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4qZDy3BibMLbI5kjdrtKzT</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4085</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 169: SUNNY HOSTIN - Leave it at the table</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0igBlM6yotDtF0bFCwY67A?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The View’s Sunny Hostin joins Jemele to discuss the The View’s legacy, what it means to celebrate the show’s 25-year anniversary, their search for a new co-host and what advice she would give the newest cast member. Sunny also shares what it was like being a child prodigy and starting high school at age 12, and how her family feels about her not using her real name in her television career. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0igBlM6yotDtF0bFCwY67A</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4708</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 168: A.J. JOHNSON - Life Therapy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6A7kySmoC7KEEr5mow4U69?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Wellness coach and actress A.J. Johnson joins Jemele to discuss her new show, “Life Therapy,” how she went from being a pre-med student to an actress, and how the death of her parents fueled her to further her passion for health and wellness. A.J., also reflects on her friendship with director John Singleton, her iconic role as Sharane in House Party, and she explains why she wasn’t part of the House Party sequels. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6A7kySmoC7KEEr5mow4U69</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4441</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 167: ANDRA DAY - The Tongue of the Learned</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7z6hvtqrRBoLE02TnbYEAo?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actress and singer Andra Day joins Jemele to discuss her award-winning, groundbreaking role as Billie Holiday in the critically-acclaimed movie, The United States vs Billie Holiday. Andra explains her extensive preparation, which included losing 40 pounds, speaking with recovering addicts and picking up smoking. Andra also shares why she’s chosen to be abstinent and the story of how music icon Stevie Wonder discovered her. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7z6hvtqrRBoLE02TnbYEAo</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3750</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 166: HOLLY ROBINSON PEETE - Gangsta Momma</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2z2p8N83cMC6pQtkrOc41E?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actress Holly Robinson Peete joins Jemele to discuss her storied acting career, including an idea she has for a 21 Jump Street reboot. Holly also offers her thoughts on the recent tragedy involving actor Alec Baldwin and how it will impact the television and film industry going forward. Plus, she also opens up about what she’s learned from her son, RJ, who has autism, and details how their family’s journey inspired their philanthropy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2z2p8N83cMC6pQtkrOc41E</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4790</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 165: AMANDA SEALES - Transparency As Philanthropy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5h6wGZve22nl7zkRlI4rZo?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Comedian and actor Amanda Seales joins Jemele to discuss why she created her groundbreaking variety show, “Smart, Funny, and Black,” and where she hopes take the show next. Amanda also talks about the controversy involving her character, Tiffany Dubois, on the HBO hit show Insecure, which resulted in a “beef” with the black sorority, Alpha Kappa Alpha. Plus, Amanda shares what it meant for her as a black woman to have a HBO stand-up comedy special, and she offers her thoughts on the Dave Chappelle controversy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5h6wGZve22nl7zkRlI4rZo</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5292</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 164: VIVICA A. FOX - Seasons of Shedding</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7nIvOTBhbKs9vfZjTGgVyq?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actress Vivica A. Fox joins Jemele to discuss her storied career, which spans multiple decades. Vivica also discusses her Lifetime movie franchise, transitioning into entrepreneurship, and why she chose acting. Vivica also reveals whether she’d like to see a Set It Off reboot, and why she initially turned down Two Can Play That Game multiple times. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7nIvOTBhbKs9vfZjTGgVyq</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4121</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 163: LISA LING - This is Life</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3mvV9iJxHkFSWQBwtL6V0r?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Journalist Lisa Ling joins Jemele to discuss the new season of her CNN show, “This is Life with Lisa Ling,” which will explore historical events that have largely been ignored. Ling also shares how the racial bullying she experienced as a child contributed to her identity struggles early on, and why she feels a responsibility to use her platform to speak out against the explosion of hate crimes toward Asians in America. Plus, Lisa shares how her vast international reporting experience helped her develop a different perspective of the world. Jemele also sounds off on former Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice for her recent comments about critical race theory. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3mvV9iJxHkFSWQBwtL6V0r</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4626</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 162: TIFFANY HADDISH - Gilding the Lilly</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6773jFUZIych0n3RlHTplC?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Celebrated actor and comedian Tiffany Haddish joins Jemele to discuss her new movie, The Card Counter, what it was like filming her first love scene, and her upcoming role as Olympic gold medalist and track icon Florence Griffith Joyner. Haddish also shares details about her relationship with rapper and actor, Common, and how her life experience has shaped her comedy. Jemele also gives thoughts on the recent controversy surrounding Dave Chappelle. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6773jFUZIych0n3RlHTplC</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5039</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 161: YVETTE NICOLE BROWN - My Mouth Got Hands</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2lTmLj9tGOkFpWkB86xfIL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actress Yvette Nicole Brown joins Jemele to discuss her hit Disney series “Big Shot,” why she decided to step away from the wildly-popular show “Community,” and her Twitter relationship with actor Chris Evans. Yvette also shares the story of how music mogul Michael Bivins once managed her singing career. Plus, Jemele gives her thoughts on Facebook’s recent shutdown. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2lTmLj9tGOkFpWkB86xfIL</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4373</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 160: PHOEBE ROBINSON - Hey Heauxs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/763TxIekdcL4ZxOhesGMWV?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Comedian, actress and author Phoebe Robinson joins Jemele to discuss her new book, Please Don’t Sit on My Bed in Your Outside Clothes. Phoebe also discusses what it was like to tour with former First Lady Michelle Obama on her book tour, how she found her voice in comedy, and how it feels to have her first stand-up comedy special debuting on HBO Max. Also, Jemele has some advice for the loud and wrong. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">763TxIekdcL4ZxOhesGMWV</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3977</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 159: TAMRON HALL - Fair Exchange, No Robbery</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/65StswtPbzGVIqFmwRA7iV?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Tamron Hall joins Jemele to discuss how her show, the Tamron Hall Show, has evolved after three seasons and why she chooses to be so vulnerable and open with her audience. Tamron also discusses her motherhood journey, her new fiction novel, As The Wicked Watch, and shares some memories of her close friend, Prince. Plus, Jemele weighs in on the Drake vs Michael Jackson debate. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65StswtPbzGVIqFmwRA7iV</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4279</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 158: JASMINE GUY - Evolution of a Revolutionary</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6IyiF4BYQtiJrbVLKfpSdm?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actress Jasmine Guy joins Jemele to discuss her portrayal of the iconic character Whitley Gilbert on the classic series, “A Different World.” Jasmine explains how authenticity was lacking in the show early on, and how the arrival of executive producer Debbie Allen changed the direction of the show and helped it become a cult classic. She also shares what the recent Different World reunion show meant to her, and why she decided to write a book about Afeni Shakur, the mother of her close friend, Tupac. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6IyiF4BYQtiJrbVLKfpSdm</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3999</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 157: JOY-ANN REID - The Race Lady</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1DThyx2E5EQ3C7N1kCVs96?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Political talk show host Joy-Ann Reid joins Jemele to discuss the success of her wildly popular nightly political discussion show, “The Reid Out,” what it’s like being the only black woman with a political show in primetime, and why having a previous show cancelled on MSNBC liberated her. Joy also breaks down why she went after Fox News host Tucker Carlson, and Jemele pays tribute to actor Michael K. Williams, who recently passed away at age 54. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1DThyx2E5EQ3C7N1kCVs96</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4590</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 156: JIMMY JAM &amp; TERRY LEWIS - Nothing to prove but a lot to say</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/34zd3Oj5O2ioSNTcvzz3Tm?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Iconic hit makers Jimmy Jam and Terry Lewis join Jemele to discuss their debut album, Jam and Lewis: Volume 1. They also discuss their career longevity, what it was like working with some of the biggest names in music, including Prince and Janet Jackson. They also share how the death of George Floyd impacted them, and if they plan on participating in a Verzuz battle. Plus, Jemele gives her thoughts on her recent dust-up with a cast member from Real Housewives of Potomac. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34zd3Oj5O2ioSNTcvzz3Tm</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5454</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 155: YAHYA ABDUL-MATEEN II - Hit that H</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2JN69Han5EqhOjxJoLPYcs?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Yahya Abdul-Mateen II joins Jemele to discuss his upcoming blockbuster projects, which include leading roles in Candyman, Matrix 4 and Aquaman 2. Yahya also shares why he began going to therapy, how he’s learning to celebrate his successes, and finding balance in fame. Plus, Jemele gives her thoughts on the Jeopardy controversy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2JN69Han5EqhOjxJoLPYcs</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3080</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 154: YARA SHAHIDI - Lifelong Learner</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/45OPYypTHoIqWU3uF8qNDB?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actress Yara Shahidi joins Jemele to discuss the fourth season of “Grown-ish,” and the growth of her character, Zoey. Yara also shares details about her college experience at Harvard, including how she feels heading into her final year and who her favorite professor is. She also discusses what it was like growing up around Prince, and what she hopes to accomplish with the production company she began with her mother.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45OPYypTHoIqWU3uF8qNDB</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4447</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 153: SANAA LATHAN - Meditate on This</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2f12zlkph8iatuDHsQujz2?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Acclaimed actress Sanaa Lathan joins Jemele to discuss her new Netflix series “Hit &amp; Run,” and making her feature directorial debut with her upcoming project, “On The Come Up.” She also shares what fans can expect from the next chapter of the cult classic “The Best Man,” and why her and her Best Man castmates have remained so close over the years. Plus, Jemele has some thoughts on the recent trend of celebrities sharing why they don’t bathe regularly. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f12zlkph8iatuDHsQujz2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3909</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 152: SAM JAY - Late Bloomer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4xFCwQb6Yp8h7rE6fPZay0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Comedian and talk show host and Sam Jay joins Jemele to discuss her groundbreaking HBO show, “Pause,” how she’s adapting to stardom, how losing her parents shaped her life and career, and why she chose to make her significant other a big part of her comedy act. Sam also discusses what it’s like writing for Saturday Night Live and Jemele gives her thoughts on DaBaby’s recent controversy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4xFCwQb6Yp8h7rE6fPZay0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4075</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 151: PATTI LABELLE - Just being Patti</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6TOXjLuX7hItww6ija0LhP?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Patti Labelle joins Jemele to discuss her iconic career, her Verzuz battle with Gladys Knight, and if it was fair to label her a “diva.” She also shares stories about her friendship with Aretha Franklin, the obstacles she had to become as a black female performer and why she chose not to marry Otis Williams from the Temptations. Plus, Jemele responds to the people who took issue with her tweet about restrictions for the unvaccinated. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6TOXjLuX7hItww6ija0LhP</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3941</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 150: TAMIKA MALLORY - Perfectly Flawed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2ceONb5L6zz4D3FOX7hrNf?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Activist, organizer and author Tamika Mallory joins Jemele to discuss her book, “State of Emergency,” which details her history with activism and how organizing is critical to freedom movements. Tamika also shares the personal demons she’s had to overcome, and how she stays the course during the country’s most challenging moments. She also responds to those who have criticized her for lacking transparency. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ceONb5L6zz4D3FOX7hrNf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4821</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 149: MICHAEL B. JORDAN - Defined by No</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0n9ggNoGlA7Syss4ivkJya?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Michael B. Jordan joins Jemele to discuss his starring role in “Without Remorse,” remaking the classic film, “The Thomas Crown Affair” and how he’s been able to succeed at playing roles that weren’t written for black characters. He also discusses what motivated him to start his own production company, and Jemele tries to pin him down about whether his notable character, Killmonger, will return in Black Panther 2. Plus, Jemele shares her thoughts on the race to space between billionaires Richard Branson and Jeff Bezos.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0n9ggNoGlA7Syss4ivkJya</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3901</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 148: JILL SCOTT - Discovering Shit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1RIUBYgSz28EaCKPzx9Nqj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jill Scott joins Jemele for a wide-ranging, candid conversation about her musical career, the fears she has a black woman raising a black son, and the aspirations she has beyond music and performing. Jill also reflects on her debut album “Who is Jill Scott?” turning 20 years old and how the pandemic has forced her to create more balance in her life.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1RIUBYgSz28EaCKPzx9Nqj</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5251</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUESS WHO'S UP NEXT?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4EQYkN79D71yrN7JKEwr7L?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Like most of the U.S., Jemele is kicking back and enjoying the day off. But before she broke out the red solo cups, she took a few minutes to reveal next Monday's amazing guest - and even provided a sneak peak of their spicy conversation. The podcast will resume on July 12th. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4EQYkN79D71yrN7JKEwr7L</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>194</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 147: MARY J. BLIGE - I Didn’t Know I Was Me</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1iOxTeDng8IhD7vvv9hJSt?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In the premiere episode of Season 3, R&amp;B icon Mary J. Blige joins Jemele to discuss her new documentary, “My Life,” which takes a deeply personal look at the singer’s signature album. Mary also discusses her upcoming acting roles, including her role as Dinah Washington in Aretha Franklin’s biopic, “Respect.” She also discusses how she dealt with insecurity and self esteem issues, and whether she’s open to being married again. Plus, Jemele debuts her new segment, “I Got A Story To Tell,” and offers her thoughts on the discord between Meg Thee Stallion and Da Baby. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1iOxTeDng8IhD7vvv9hJSt</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4684</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Season 3 Premieres Monday, June 28th w Mary J. Blige!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5GJck5cPYZVuUbdCnoxLXR?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Season 3 of Jemele Hill is Unbothered is here!Listen as Jemele talks about the exciting guests and conversations coming your way. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5GJck5cPYZVuUbdCnoxLXR</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>53</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 146: The Season 2 JHIUs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4Pdx8dv7eUSVE2YDDQcOBO?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele relives the best moments and interviews from Season 2 with the annual JHIUs (pronounced JOO-e). Jemele will give out awards for best story told on the podcast, realest moment, most memorable guest, and others. You’ll hear from some of the season’s best guests, including John Legend, Gabrielle Union, Taraji P. Henson, Questlove, Ellen Pompeo, Leslie Jones, Michael Smith and more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4Pdx8dv7eUSVE2YDDQcOBO</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4114</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPECIAL ANNOUNCEMENT</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/09sN7HMsVTaEjeXCRgY7IQ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele teases the Season 2 awards show finale, which premieres Monday, May 17th. She also discusses JHIU’s special vaccination episode and drops a few tidbits about what you can look forward to in our upcoming Season 3. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09sN7HMsVTaEjeXCRgY7IQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>175</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JHIU presents: The Shot - History, Hesitancy and Hope</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3ts1wNe8P81BxgWUSyoGno?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this special episode in collaboration with More Than A Vote, Jemele explores the hesitancy in the African-American community to take the Covid-19 vaccine. She unpacks how the medical community’s historical and current mistreatment of African Americans has fueled vaccine reluctance, breaks down myths about the vaccine, and how the experts’ messaging can address the distrust. Jemele speaks with various medical experts, policy makers, and the Reverend Al Sharpton. Jemele also interviews her mother, who like many African Americans, is not on board with taking the vaccine. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ts1wNe8P81BxgWUSyoGno</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2527</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 145: BARRY JENKINS - Happiness is a direction</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2cbUYt7Uyy0m1GkP5oH4V7?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Filmmaker Barry Jenkins joins Jemele to discuss his groundbreaking new television series, The Underground Railroad, how the success of his Oscar-winning movie Moonlight changed his life, and what it’s been like seeing the careers of actors he’s worked with — such as Regina King (If Beale Street Could Talk) and Trevante Rhodes (Moonlight) — continue to ascend. Barry and Jemele also debate if Die Hard is a Christmas movie, and Jemele offers thoughts on whether men and women can be platonic friends. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cbUYt7Uyy0m1GkP5oH4V7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4189</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 144: QUESTLOVE - Verbal Jam Session</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/30hUizLeopniyR7xzQQD4H?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Questlove joins Jemele to discuss his evolution from front man of The Roots to author, curator and podcaster. He shares the origin story behind The Roots’ legendary jam sessions, and why he decided to play the drums. He also shares his memorable first encounter with Prince, who became a close friend. Plus, Jemele gives her thoughts on the Derek Chauvin verdict. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30hUizLeopniyR7xzQQD4H</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4572</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 143: ALICIA GARZA - Tough Skin, Soft Heart</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/27VmRViH9Ej3pvh9AbXRBN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Black Lives Matter co-founder Alicia Garza joins Jemele to discuss her powerful new book, “The Purpose of Power: How We Come Together When We Fall Apart.” Alicia explains why organizing remains the most effective way to create change and amass power. Alicia shares what motivated her to leave BLM and start her own organization, Black Futures Lab. She also addresses common myths about the BLM movement, and the tricky relationship between celebrity and activism. Plus, Jemele gives her thoughts on DMX’s recent passing. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27VmRViH9Ej3pvh9AbXRBN</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4826</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 142: STEPHEN COLBERT - Truthiness</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2BkhdrJYysTvxD2HxbtZjW?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Stephen Colbert joins Jemele to discuss his career journey, the ups and downs of filming The Late Show during the pandemic, and why he’d never interview Donald Trump again. He also shares the story of how he wound up appearing on a public access show with Eminem. Plus, Jemele shares her thoughts on the Derek Chauvin trial. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2BkhdrJYysTvxD2HxbtZjW</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4718</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 141: WOOD HARRIS - I Ain’t Fighting For Trophies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/611AKLKY0uPn7BoKlTHr9O?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Wood Harris takes Jemele through his incredible career, which includes classic movies such as “Above The Rim,” “Paid In Full,” “Remember The Titans,” and of course his iconic role as Avon Barksdale on “The Wire.” Wood discusses how The Wire would be received if he came out in present day, if he’s bothered by the lack of accolades despite having such a wide-ranging, successful career, and how the documentary “The Last Dance” changed how he viewed his basketball hero, Michael Jordan. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">611AKLKY0uPn7BoKlTHr9O</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3914</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 140: ISSA RAE - Success Shit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0MsiyLgL7lK502gAzfqzP4?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The multi-talented Issa Rae joins Jemele to discuss the final season of her hit HBO comedy series, “Insecure,” what the show has meant to popular culture and how it’s led to some awkward fan encounters. Issa also gives details on the HBO Max television project she’s executive producing with rap duo, City Girls, and talks about what it’s been like transitioning from strictly a content creator to now an entrepreneur with multiple businesses. Plus, Jemele shares her thoughts on why America is unlikely to adopt any substantive gun control. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0MsiyLgL7lK502gAzfqzP4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4397</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 139: WILL PACKER - The Trois Guy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7t18FrRsTaaZru3UAaAPCN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Filmmaker Will Packer talks about his incredible journey with Jemele, including how he went from delivering newspapers to becoming one of the most successful black movie makers in history. He also discusses the challenges he still faces in Hollywood, despite his enormous success. Plus, Jemele shares her thoughts on the tragic murders of six Asian women in Atlanta. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7t18FrRsTaaZru3UAaAPCN</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4184</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 138: ANTHONY MACKIE - No. 6 on the Call Sheet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/04F2XEsJmoPR01SCTY0tbM?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Anthony Mackie joins Jemele to discuss his upcoming Disney Plus series “Falcon and the Winter Soldier,” which debuts on March 19. Anthony shares what it’s been like playing Sam Wilson, aka “The Falcon”, for nearly a decade in some of Marvel’s biggest blockbusters and if he feels any additional pressure as the most notable black character now in the comic book movie franchise. Plus, Jemele gives her thoughts on Meghan Markle and Prince Harry’s explosive interview with Oprah Winfrey. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04F2XEsJmoPR01SCTY0tbM</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4483</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 137: CHAIRMAN FRED HAMPTON JR. &amp; RYAN COOGLER - Real Rap, Real Revolution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2QzfuOwEaD9Gm0wCiPtWUz?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Director and producer Ryan Coogler and Chairman Fred Hampton Jr., the son of slain Black Panther Party leader Fred Hampton, joins Jemele to discuss the critically-acclaimed movie about Hampton’s life “Judas and the Black Messiah.” Coogler explains why he chose to get behind the film as a producer, and Jemele tries to get Coogler to reveal some details about Black Panther 2. Hampton Jr., shares why his father’s story and assassination still resonates today and what it’s been like being a target of the federal government. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2QzfuOwEaD9Gm0wCiPtWUz</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3605</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 136: CLARESSA SHIELDS - The GWOAT</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7qUWDPE2Y9GXzjtkG01vDj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>World champion boxer Claressa Shields joins Jemele to discuss her upcoming pay-per-view bout against Marie-Eve Dicaire. Shields also explains why she’s been so vocal about the lack of equality for women in boxing, and why she recently made the decision to fight in MMA. Plus, Shields shares why she abstains from sex for weeks before her fights. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7qUWDPE2Y9GXzjtkG01vDj</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3976</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 135: LEE DANIELS - Strange Fruit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2u6Qn4da1mD6uVpxQdde0H?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Renowned director and creator Lee Daniels joins Jemele to discuss his new, critically-acclaimed movie, “The United States vs. Billie Holiday.” Daniels shares what inspired him to pursue the project, and what made him choose singer Andra Day to play Holiday. Daniels also discusses his upcoming projects, his close friendship with Mariah Carey and whether Hollywood validation matters. Plus, Jemele gives her thoughts on Donald Trump’s impeachment. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2u6Qn4da1mD6uVpxQdde0H</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3779</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 134: KENAN THOMPSON - All That, 18 years and counting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2xnxqjpJT0qgEcd7kj4IoR?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Longtime Saturday Night Live veteran Kenan Thompson joins Jemele to discuss his 18-year run on the iconic comedy sketch show, his new sitcom “Kenan,” and the revival of his television partnership with close friend, Kel Mitchell. Plus, Jemele offers her thoughts on the Gorilla Glue controversy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2xnxqjpJT0qgEcd7kj4IoR</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3132</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 133: DANIEL KALUUYA - The Process of Growing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6YRgVITLesBCWX4TOir0gl?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Daniel Kaluuya joins Jemele to discuss his new, critically-acclaimed movie, “Judas and the Black Messiah,” including his intense preparation for his role as civil rights leader Fred Hampton. He also shares his experience shooting the blockbuster movie “Black Panther,” and how his breakout performance in “Get Out” changed his life. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6YRgVITLesBCWX4TOir0gl</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3051</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 132: MORRIS CHESTNUT - Surviving and Thriving</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1OyyVYcZfIDD6ifamSOnUI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Morris Chestnut joins Jemele to discuss “Spell,” a new movie starring Omari Hardwick and Loretta Devine that he is executive producing. Morris also reminisces about his breakout role as Ricky in Boyz n the Hood, shares what has been key in sustaining his nearly 30-year acting career and gives Jemele the scoop on the next Best Man project. Plus, Jemele offers emotional thoughts about a recently deceased friend and keeps it real about a NFL player who recently was accused of domestic violence. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1OyyVYcZfIDD6ifamSOnUI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5257</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 131: DAVEED DIGGS - Really Good, But ...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/58fnfuFUz14qXuk2vLBNDE?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor, rapper and producer Daveed Diggs joins Jemele to discuss the new season of his hit television show, “Snowpiercer.” He also discusses his involvement in the Disney’s animated Pixar film “Soul,” and his incredible performance in the iconic Broadway musical “Hamilton,” which netted Daveed a Tony award. An Oakland native, Daveed shares how influential all MC Hammer has been on his rap career. Plus, Jemele euologizes Donald Trump. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58fnfuFUz14qXuk2vLBNDE</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4634</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 130: DAMSON IDRIS - American By Trade</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5lGVZoBPWXDSdW9izIkmX0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Damson Idris joins Jemele to discuss Season 4 of his hit television drama “Snowfall,” and his new Netflix movie “Outside the Wire,” where he stars alongside Anthony Mackie. Damson also discusses growing up in London, what it was like being the youngest of six siblings, and how he developed his passion for acting. Plus, Jemele shares her thoughts on Donald Trump’s second impeachment. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5lGVZoBPWXDSdW9izIkmX0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3539</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 129: MICHAEL SMITH - His and Hers, The Reunion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/42caWgTKWWUnWYbsd2K6pB?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele reunites with her dear friend and former television partner Michael Smith to discuss their awkward departure from ESPN, and how their friendship made them such a strong television duo. They also discuss the transition into entrepreneurship and Michael shares what it’s been like returning to daily television. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42caWgTKWWUnWYbsd2K6pB</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6539</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 128: LATOSHA BROWN - The Pain Of Staying The Same</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0tCkVrqU8zqrELj3eSAYFq?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>LaTosha Brown, the co-founder of Black Voters Matter, joins Jemele to discuss what’s at stake in Georgia’s two Senate elections. Brown also shares how her organization has been able to reach thousands of black voters in Georgia, why so many African Americans are disillusioned by the voting and political processes, and the burgeoning political power of black people in the South. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0tCkVrqU8zqrELj3eSAYFq</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3910</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 127: METHOD MAN - A Method to the Journey</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/73TCTMzu2YkungtloUOn22?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rapper and actor Method Man joins Jemele to discuss his role as shady lawyer Davis MacLean on Starz’s “Power Book II: Ghost,” the spinoff to the hit series “Power.” Method also discusses his new podcast on the Marvel Comic Universe, how and why he fell in love with comics as a kid, and what comic book role he’d love to play. He also talks about how he felt he was portrayed in Wu-Tang Clan’s documentary and television series, and what new music you can expect from him in 2021. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73TCTMzu2YkungtloUOn22</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4166</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 126: TARAJI P. HENSON - Give Me My F**king Credit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6heIzvyxNMlGS9KwyUrldb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Taraji P. Henson joins Jemele for an introspective and personal conversation about mental health. Taraji shares why she has publicly disclosed her own mental health journey, and what she hopes to accomplish with her new Facebook Watch show that’s centered on mental wealthness. Taraji also gets candid about the fight for pay equity for Black women in Hollywood. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6heIzvyxNMlGS9KwyUrldb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4538</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 125: LESLIE JONES - I Know Who I Am</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5D0m9Yi3UV6XFQovZvRbAH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Saturday Night Live alum Leslie Jones joins Jemele to discuss her incredible career journey, which has included stand-up comedy, acting, and now hosting the iconic game show “Supermarket Sweep.” Leslie also discusses working with Eddie Murphy on the Coming to America sequel, and how her running social media commentary about popular television shows has become a hit with fans. She also shares why she’s so self-deprecating in her stand-up comedy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5D0m9Yi3UV6XFQovZvRbAH</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4220</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 124: GOVERNOR GRETCHEN WHITMER - Big Gretch</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0QlLRaUMUZTvXholONN6ML?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Michigan Governor Gretchen Whitmer joins Jemele to discuss the recent controversy involving the certification of the state’s electoral votes, disenfranchisement of black voters, and whether President-elect Joe Biden will be able to unify the country after four years of contentiousness under President Donald Trump. Whitmer also discusses how she handled the discovery that a group men planned to kidnap and possibly murder her, and how she sees her political future. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0QlLRaUMUZTvXholONN6ML</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4051</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 123: MEGAN RAPINOE - Grinding All My Life</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7lJ6wNu3f69yoa5aRGMwzB?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Soccer star and activist Megan Rapinoe joins Jemele to discuss her new memoir, “One Life.” Megan also discusses how she became passionate about social justice issues and how it inspired her to make the controversial decision to kneel during the national anthem in support of Colin Kaepernick in 2016. She also shares some details about her engagement to WNBA superstar Sue Bird. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7lJ6wNu3f69yoa5aRGMwzB</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4800</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 122: JURNEE SMOLLETT - Pessimism is a Privilege</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4lUCUomqEUORteTPC3VTTk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Jurnee Smollett joins Jemele to discuss the success of her groundbreaking series, Lovecraft Country, and why it has resonated so strongly with fans. Jurnee also shares how she maintained her optimism, despite feeling like she sometimes didn’t fit into the industry. And she explains why she’d love to be in more action movies. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4lUCUomqEUORteTPC3VTTk</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3536</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 121: MIKAILA ULMER - Bee Fearless</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7B7fUj438fEKhJGPzojZIY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>15-year-old business prodigy Mikaila Ulmer joins Jemele to discuss how she turned a lemonade business that she started at four years old into a lucrative business in which she has sold over 1 million bottles and is featured in over 1,000 stores. Mikaila also discusses how she balances school and being a CEO, how she’s involved her family and expanded her empire. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7B7fUj438fEKhJGPzojZIY</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2740</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 120: ISABEL WILKERSON - The Only Competition Is Yourself</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0L5sOBQfDJf759zNfqTorz?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Celebrated author Isabel Wilkerson joins Jemele to discuss her sensational new book, “Caste: The Origins of Our Discontents.” Isabel discusses why she believes America operates on a caste system, and why she chose to write about it following the success of her first book, “The Warmth of Other Suns.” Plus, Jemele shares her thoughts on the fixation with the white working class. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0L5sOBQfDJf759zNfqTorz</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3574</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 119: BRITTANY PACKNETT CUNNINGHAM and TIFFANY D. CROSS - Disciplined Hopefuls</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1xdJo9vK6wFaaN3UxCePhF?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Activist Brittany Packnett Cunningham and author and political analyst Tiffany D. Cross join Jemele for this special podcast on the 2020 presidential election. They discuss the anxiety over not knowing the final election result, what they learned about America during this election and whether or not it’s possible for the country to heal after such a polarizing election. They also share their thoughts on the increased support for President Donald Trump by black men, Latino and Cuban voters. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1xdJo9vK6wFaaN3UxCePhF</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4082</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 118: YAMICHE ALCINDOR &amp; APRIL RYAN - Tea for the Fever</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0rTVM2bPb3UwTtdn0OWLNT?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>White House correspondents Yamiche Alcindor and April Ryan join Jemele to discuss what it’s like covering President Donald Trump, and the impact of their verbal confrontations with the president. They also discuss how their career paths led them to the White House, and the significance of having black journalists represented in the presidential press corp. Plus, April, who has now covered four presidential administrations, compares and contrasts the different administrations. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0rTVM2bPb3UwTtdn0OWLNT</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4613</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 117: KATIE PORTER - Learning to Change the World</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5Y04JDQroOUKvxCchLaKf2?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Katie Porter, the dazzling representative for California’s 45th district, joins Jemele to discuss what motivated her to get into politics, how she’s become a political star due to her thorough questioning in congressional committee hearings, and why her relationship with Senators Kamala Harris and Elizabeth Warren was instrumental in her political career. Plus, Katie also shares what it’s like raising two, very politically engaged children, as a single parent. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5Y04JDQroOUKvxCchLaKf2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2773</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 116: CHUCK D - When the Grid Goes Down</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6ZnmH8S9Ym3tTnfWWFf6S2?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rapper and activist Chuck D joins Jemele to discuss Public Enemy’s new album, “What You Gonna Do When The Grid Goes Down?” which reunites PE with Def Jam. Chuck D provides insight into his unique relationship with Flava Flav, and why they decided to do a remake of their powerful national anthem song “Fight the Power,” featuring Nas, Rapsody, and YG, among others. Chuck D also discusses his relationship with Tupac, and breaks down the different generations in hip hop. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ZnmH8S9Ym3tTnfWWFf6S2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4418</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 115: JOHN DAVID WASHINGTON - Built for This</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6y93H4ex1cJqXl8BHn2ZyE?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor John David Washington joins Jemele to discuss his latest movie “Tenet,” which was directed by renown director Christopher Nolan. JD shares what it was like working with Nolan and how his college football background helped him do the challenging stunts associated with the film. Plus, JD talks about how he handled living with his parents during part of the COVID-19 quarantine. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6y93H4ex1cJqXl8BHn2ZyE</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3330</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 114: STEVE KERR - The Re-Education of Steve Kerr</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/17m6cHZQrhfM8clLVEJ5dP?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Golden State Warriors coach Steve Kerr joins Jemele to discuss NBA players becoming key voices in the social justice movement, and how his own awareness and understanding of black struggle has increased significantly in 2020. Steve also shares what it was like being criticized by President Donald Trump, and his thoughts on the upcoming election. Steve and Jemele also discuss what the Warriors plan to do with the second overall pick in this year’s NBA draft. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17m6cHZQrhfM8clLVEJ5dP</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3928</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 113: CHELSEA CLINTON - Optimism is a choice</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/35qlfO1ZJgZERXOCd7kIHP?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Author and activist Chelsea Clinton joins Jemele to discuss her latest book in her “She Persisted” series, which focuses on the triumphant journeys of some of the most celebrated female Olympic athletes in history. Chelsea discusses why she chose to write for young audiences, and why it’s important for them to develop an optimistic view of the world. Chelsea also shares what kind of grandparents her parents, Bill and Hilary Clinton, have been. Plus, Chelsea opens up about some harrowing personal encounters she’s had with people who oppose her parents. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35qlfO1ZJgZERXOCd7kIHP</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3509</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 112: BIG SEAN - Deep Reverence</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4Nkhw6EPiKQc0IaWC01AS0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Big Sean joins Jemele to talk extensively about his new album “Detroit 2,” which is his fifth solo album and the sequel to his 2012 mixtape. Sean explains how the track ‘Deep Reverance” — which features the late Nipsey Hussle — came together. He also shares why he chose to rap about resolving his beef with Kendrick Lamar, and coping with depression and anxiety. He also discusses how he nearly quit rapping because of his mental health struggles, and what inspired him to continue his career. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4Nkhw6EPiKQc0IaWC01AS0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3191</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 111: KERRY WASHINGTON - Professional Bad Ass​</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/09RIDSnOmgdTrgOyDi4Jkt?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Kerry Washington joins Jemele to discuss what it was like participating in the Democratic National Convention, and why it’s important for her to use her platform to encourage people to vote and speak out against injustice. Kerry also shares what it meant to receive multiple nominations in this year’s Emmys for her outstanding work on the hit limited series ‘Little Fires Everywhere’ and ‘American Son.’ Plus, Jemele gives her thoughts on the city of Louisville reaching a settlement with Breonna Taylor’s family and why it’s not cause for celebration. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09RIDSnOmgdTrgOyDi4Jkt</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3620</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 110: JANELLE MONAE - Revolutions Per Minute</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2PeF59H9GFVddK3V9WXiKF?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Singer and actress Janelle Monae joins Jemele to discuss her new single “Turntables” and her upcoming movie, Antebellum. Janelle also opens up about how she maintains her peace during such a tumultuous time, and she discusses why she’s lending her voice and platform to fighting voter suppression. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2PeF59H9GFVddK3V9WXiKF</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2509</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 109: SPENCER PAYSINGER - A New Playbook</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3wRKRrhI0xSMut6QuQibZ8?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele shares her thoughts on Chadwick Boseman’s death and has strong words for those who are trying to turn 17-year-old murderer Kyle Rittenhouse into a martyr. She’s also joined by former NFL player Spencer Paysinger, whose life story was turned into the hit television series, “All American.” Spencer also discusses why he set the goal of retiring from professional football by age 30, whether or not he regrets not kneeling in solidarity with Colin Kaepernick when he played, and how his Super Bowl ring was stolen. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3wRKRrhI0xSMut6QuQibZ8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3640</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 108: DAN RATHER - The Voice of Reason</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0ye2fSRnoJ2GkG7NZaRKlF?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Legendary journalist Dan Rather joins Jemele to discuss why the media has struggled to adequately cover Donald Trump’s presidency, and why it’s insulting to compare Trump to former president Richard Nixon. Dan also shares what it was like covering the civil rights movement and Dr. Martin Luther King Jr., and how he came to have more than 1 million Twitter followers. Plus, Jemele shares her thoughts on the sports world taking a timeout in response to what happened to 29-year-old Jacob Blake. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ye2fSRnoJ2GkG7NZaRKlF</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3950</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 107: NIKOLE HANNAH-JONES - An Inconvenient People</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/077KWNyiO2Ia3kBVKTFq0g?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele addresses the Washington football team hiring the first black president in NFL history and she also has some words for Seattle Seahawks rookie cornerback Kemah Siverand, who lost his job for sneaking a woman into his hotel. Plus, Jemele is joined by Pulitzer Prize winner Nikole Hannah-Jones, who won the prestigious award for her work on the New York Times’ 1619 Project, which traces how the legacy of slavery touches every corner of American life. Nikole shares her thoughts on the conservative critics of the project and debunks several myths about American slavery. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">077KWNyiO2Ia3kBVKTFq0g</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3487</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 106: W. KAMAU BELL - Private School Negro</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3Hy6Mc1kFrh4I2faxlow7K?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele has a word for those taking shots at vice presidential nominee Kamala Harris and for those criticizing “WAP,” the new song by Meg Thee Stallion and Cardi B. She also welcomes television host and political comedian W. Kamau Bell to the pod for a discussion on the new season of his Emmy award winning CNN show, “United Shades of America.” They discuss his infamous episode about the Klu Klux Klan, why so many white comedians wore blackface, and the political climate in Alabama. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3Hy6Mc1kFrh4I2faxlow7K</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3948</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 105: CHRISTIAN DAWKINS - The Fall Guy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/212ik8wqxtaUNY9cf6FGyy?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele applauds the pettiness of the WNBA players who endorsed the political opponent of one of their team owners. She also welcomes guest Christian Dawkins to the pod. Dawkins discusses his HBO documentary, “The Scheme,” which was based on his involvement in one of the most highly-publicized basketball scandals in college sports history. Dawkins explains why he never snitched despite facing federal prison time, and breaks down why college players should be paid.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">212ik8wqxtaUNY9cf6FGyy</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4024</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 104: ELLEN POMPEO - It’s All in The Game</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6HugX93BGIXQPryjKChxdy?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Grey’s Anatomy star Ellen Pompeo joins Jemele to discuss the gender pay equity gap in Hollywood and why she decided to publicly reveal her salary. Ellen also shares why it hasn’t been a burden for her to play the iconic character Meredith Grey for the last 15 years, and why she never left the show. She also discusses how her Boston upbringing influenced her viewpoints on race and why she has been so vocal about speaking up for women of color in Hollywood. Plus, Jemele admonishes presidential candidate Joe Biden for his revisionist history. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6HugX93BGIXQPryjKChxdy</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3404</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 103: GABRIELLE UNION - The Chip in The Cookie</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3rnDDT9kCTNwmVLvvBsDXj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor and entrepreneur Gabrielle Union opens up to Jemele about why she decided to go public with the toxicity she experienced while on America’s Got Talent. She also discusses how growing up in a predominantly white neighborhood in Nebraska shaped her attitudes about race, and she used that experience to teach her own children about racial issues. She also tells the story of offering her tuna casserole to Prince. Plus, Jemele pays tribute to civil rights icons John Lewis and C.T. Vivian. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3rnDDT9kCTNwmVLvvBsDXj</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3909</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 102: ICE CUBE - A Contract with Black America</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1UvbBVZaqSIwvTMV12z5Ax?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Ice Cube returns to the podcast for his second visit to explain why he developed “A Contract with Black America,” a detailed document he created with other experts that provides effective strategies and solutions that will combat some of the biggest issues that stand in the way of full equality for black Americans. Cube also addresses a recent column by former Laker great Kareem Abdul-Jabbar in which Abdul-Jabbar accused Cube and other Hollywood entertainers of being anti-Semitic. Also, Jemele offers her thoughts on a 15-year-old who was jailed for not completing her online schoolwork. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1UvbBVZaqSIwvTMV12z5Ax</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3862</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 101: OMAR DORSEY - Alanna</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6mHtxF2BPTTcRZAao7rhcm?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele addresses the controversy involving Philadelphia Eagles wide receiver DeSean Jackson’s anti-Semitic Instagram post. Actor Omar Dorsey joins the pod to discuss his starring role in the hit series “Queen Sugar,” and how his mother played a pivotal role in his acting career. The Atlanta native also reminisces about attending Freaknik back in the mid-1990s and what it was like growing up as a preacher’s kid. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6mHtxF2BPTTcRZAao7rhcm</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3809</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 100: JENIFER LEWIS - Walking in Joy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3kzeyPhRfc7mkCnUCvs3vc?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele has some fiery words for the critics who tried to cancel her recently on Twitter, including Barstool Sports founder Dave Portnoy. She also welcomes the multi-talented Jenifer Lewis, who currently stars on the hit television series “Black-ish.” Jenifer discusses her mental health journey, which includes coping with a bi-polar diagnosis since 1990. She also weighs in on several racial and social justice issues, and reveals how she’s dealt with racist encounters at various points in her life. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3kzeyPhRfc7mkCnUCvs3vc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4025</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 99: ROYCE da 5’9 - Book of Ryan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1ModK4i8uIye4o7t0DBA5n?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele responds to conservative criticism of her commentary on NASCAR, and shares her thoughts on America’s continual incompetent response to COVID-19. Plus, special guest and fellow Detroit native Royce da 5’9, gets candid with Jemele about his sobriety, and mental health. Royce also breaks down how the “beef” between him, Eminem and Tee Grizzley was eventually squashed. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ModK4i8uIye4o7t0DBA5n</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4298</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 98: THE-DREAM - No More Kumbaya</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1qfYV5GT8Wfg3WXPeO7riJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele offers her thoughts on Quaker’s decisions to end their usage of Aunt Jemima and Twitter’s new voice-tweet feature. She is also joined by accomplished musician and songwriter The-Dream, who discusses the mood in Atlanta in the wake up of the killing of Rayshard Brooks. He also shares how he was able to create powerful female anthems such as Beyoncé’s “Single Ladies,” and Rihanna’s “Umbrella.” Plus, The-Dream breaks down his new album, “SXTP4.” Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1qfYV5GT8Wfg3WXPeO7riJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3625</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 97: REGINA KING - Sister Night</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7n0ITtX4Z6YeqFl0AFWvMY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele breaks down what defunding the police really means, and why it’s important that it remains on the national agenda. Then, Jemele is joined by actor and director Regina King, who discusses the cultural impact of her critically-acclaimed HBO series Watchmen. Regina also discusses her versatile career arc, what inspires her to be a director, and her thoughts on today’s racially-charged climate. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7n0ITtX4Z6YeqFl0AFWvMY</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2103</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 96: YVONNE ORJI - Own Your Blessing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0juSTco6Eq1jyqEr085TXV?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele shares her thoughts on the recent controversy involving New Orleans Saints QB, Drew Brees. Then, actor and comedian Yvonne Orji discusses her first televised stand-up comedy special, “Momma I Made It!” along with the polarizing turn her character, Molly, has taken on the hit show Insecure and the backlash she’s received from fans as a result. Plus, Yvonne also explains how she’s been helped by therapy during quarantine. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0juSTco6Eq1jyqEr085TXV</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2835</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EP 95: JOHN LEGEND - Polite Raunch</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/36Ien4vFnpu2jQqyQSL9Sj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele shares her thoughts on the protests that were sparked by the unjust murders of Ahmaud Arbery, Breonna Taylor, and George Floyd, and why every celebrity shouldn’t share their opinions on social justice. Jemele is also joined by megastar John Legend, who discusses how his life has changed during the pandemic, what he’s learned about himself as a husband and a father. They also discuss his new album, including his first single “Bigger Love." Plus, Jemele asks John how he maintains his title of Sexiest Man Alive while being largely confined to the house. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36Ien4vFnpu2jQqyQSL9Sj</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5151</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Season 2 Premieres Monday, June 1st </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4USoE4WMaasa3uRoCFTZfl?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele Hill is Unbothered Season 2 Premieres Monday, June 1st with a very special guest... Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4USoE4WMaasa3uRoCFTZfl</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>54</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 94: NATASHA ROTHWELL - Prolific But Not Perfect</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6xB3aWycfyTuNqPOyqb6p5?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In a bonus episode, Jemele is joined by writer, actor and producer Natasha Rothwell, who plays the confident, no-holds-barred Kelly on HBO’s smash hit, Insecure. Natasha discusses why she calls Donald Trump “trash" every single day on Twitter, why she still hasn’t outgrown being an “awkward, black girl,” and the future of Insecure. Plus, Natasha discusses navigating Hollywood as a “body-positive feminist." Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6xB3aWycfyTuNqPOyqb6p5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4585</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 93: JAY ELLIS - Working Smarter, Not Harder</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4fCTcK9EqQwJKGsKC6W8jZ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In a bonus episode, Jemele is joined by actor Jay Ellis, who plays Lawrence on HBO’s popular comedy Insecure. Jay and Jemele break down the Netflix hit reality show, “Love is Blind.” They discuss why Insecure fans are still arguing about Lawrence and his love interest on Insecure, Issa Rae, and how it led to Jay being slapped in public one time. He also explains why he never expected #LawrenceHive to develop, and the grueling audition process to land the role. Plus, Jay talks about his role in the reboot of Top Gun, and what it was like working with Tom Cruise. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fCTcK9EqQwJKGsKC6W8jZ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4329</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 92: The JHIU's (Pronounced JOO-eys)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1JSKnXBfL22HKs10H8ckkK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele wraps up Season One of the podcast by handing out the "JHIU's," which are made-up awards that she has bestowed upon the best guests who appeared on the inaugural season of Jemele Hill is UnBothered. Relive some of the best interview moments, including who told the best story, who taught listeners the most creative curse word, and which guests left Jemele speechless. Plus, Jemele reveals which guest had the most innovative business idea, and the guest that proved to be the ultimate day drinker. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1JSKnXBfL22HKs10H8ckkK</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4353</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 91: Dat Rona</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6H8849KjZbcl9prdVC5whN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele discusses all things related to the coronavirus, including hoarders, what a trip to the grocery store is like on lockdown, and how she came close to buying ground turkey meat on the black market. She also dives into detail about the fine print on the government’s proposed stimulus package, and she’s joined by her husband, Ian, to discuss how being under quarantine can stress, or enhance relationships. Ian also gives tips for singles who are struggling to cope with lack of affection during the coronavirus shutdown. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6H8849KjZbcl9prdVC5whN</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3872</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPECIAL ANNOUNCEMENT</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4kGrYGvXZ4L5V2qJVYZXwM?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Episode 91 of Jemele Hill is UnBothered will be a special, live-streamed episode on Instagram. Jemele will discuss America’s new normal under the coronavirus, plowing through her snack supply within the first couple days of lockdown in Los Angeles, getting on her spouse’s nerves during the 24-hour lockdown, why social distancing may become a permanent way of life. Plus, Jemele will break down the best television and film to watch during virus lockdown. She also will be accepting viewer questions on the live stream. This special episode will be posted in the normal podcast feed on 3/24. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4kGrYGvXZ4L5V2qJVYZXwM</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>162</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 90: JOSHUA MORROW - 26 Years and Counting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1bPHXGElvqkE8PicsjILSA?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Joshua Morrow, who plays Nicholas Newman on the iconic soap opera Young and the Restless, joins Jemele to discuss what it’s been like playing Nick since 1994. Joshua shares crazy fan stories, talks about that time Tiger Woods hustled him on the golf course, the backstory behind Wayne Gretzky attending his wedding, and reveals the two times he seriously considered leaving Y&amp;R. Joshua also shares his thoughts on why Y&amp;R, which averages 4 million viewers a show, remains a staple, despite the fact many other soap operas have been cancelled. Plus, Joshua shares his memories of former longtime cast member Kristoff St. John, who died last year.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bPHXGElvqkE8PicsjILSA</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4196</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 89: ASHLEY NICOLE BLACK - Success In A Plus-Sized Body</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7DoghG9dWhwyXx2r01qzdL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Ashley Nicole Black, who stars in HBO’s hit series A Black Lady Sketch Show, joins Jemele to discuss overcoming stereotypes of plus-sized black women in Hollywood, and navigating negative feedback early in her career. She also discusses her relationship with former presidential candidate Elizabeth Warren, and the surprising things she learned about Donald Trump supporters when she attended the last Republican National Convention and his presidential inauguration as a correspondent for Samantha Bee’s show Full Frontal.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7DoghG9dWhwyXx2r01qzdL</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4647</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 88: ERICA ASH - The Year of No F**ks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0YqbKneDD0wphElsP7vv5o?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Erica Ash, who starred in the Showtime series “Survivors Remorse,” joins Jemele for a deeply personal conversation. Erica discusses her numerous battles with cancer, including why she didn’t tell her loved ones the first time she faced breast cancer. Erica also details a recent accident where she suffered a broken back, and the challenges she faced in recovery. Plus, she shares how she went from being pre-med in college to pursuing an entertainment career. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0YqbKneDD0wphElsP7vv5o</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4420</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 87: RASHAD ROBINSON - What’s Acceptable and What’s Possible</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3J11mKnppfejnXdSqerviT?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele sits down with Rashad Robinson, the executive director of Color of Change, the nation’s largest online racial justice organization. Rashad explains why he believes black presidential candidates Senators Kamala Harris and Cory Booker didn’t make it further in the process. He also discusses how young, black working class voters are being ignored, the critical issues that should be part of the black agenda and why we can’t depend on charity to fix inequality.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3J11mKnppfejnXdSqerviT</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4961</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 86: PHONTE - Pt 2 - Black Force Activity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1uCTeiPEQgz2S6HdK7GVcx?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Part 2 of Jemele’s interview with Phonte, who discusses how he balances a solo career, being one half of the hip hop duo Little Brother, and a member of the group Foreign Exchange. Phonte shares his future solo career plans, which might one day include some country music tracks. Phonte opens up about his relationship with his mother and how his most recent solo album “No News Is Good News,” helped repair their relationship. Plus, Jemele and Phonte debate whether Drake will be considered the greatest rapper of all time, and Phonte also explains dark-web-face-tat rap.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1uCTeiPEQgz2S6HdK7GVcx</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3737</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 85: PHONTE - Pt 1 - Smoothies and Salmon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3YXRP2g5re7trFu5qRt0UF?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Phonte, one half of the wildly popular hip hop duo Little Brother and a member of the group Foreign Exchange, joins Jemele to break down the breakup and makeup of Little Brother, and how the death of Phife Dawg from A Tribe Called Quest sparked their reunion. Phonte also discusses how different the creative process was for the Little Brother reunion album, May The Lord Watch, compared to their previous projects. Plus, Phonte talks about the challenges for artists in the streaming era, and makes the case for why Bad Boys 3 is the best movie of the trilogy and why 90-Day Fiancé is the best show on television. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3YXRP2g5re7trFu5qRt0UF</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3754</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 84: DAYMOND JOHN - For Us, By Us</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7nOr8opySq8vdM9ubWQ9Az?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Charismatic entrepreneur Daymond John joins Jemele to discuss how he went from being an interloper on music video sets to owning and creating FUBU, one of the most successful clothing companies in the world. Daymond talks about his upcoming book, “Powershift,” and shares FUBU’s origin story. He also discusses how he came to star on the hit series “Shark Tank,” and what he looks for when he determines what businesses he should invest in. Plus, Daymond reveals the mistakes up-and-coming entrepreneurs often make, why he believes Kim Kardashian will be president one day, and he explains why he isn’t leaving any of his wealth to his children. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7nOr8opySq8vdM9ubWQ9Az</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4028</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 83: BENJAMIN CRUMP - Playing With Our Emotions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5xHlFKQO9nIb73ilab2spU?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Prominent civil rights attorney Benjamin Crump, who has represented the families of Trayvon Martin, Botham Jean, and Tamir Rice, among others, joins Jemele to discuss his new book “Open Season,” and how black people are being destroyed by the criminal justice system. Crump also explains the missteps made by the prosecution in the Martin case, how the Michael Brown case in Ferguson inspired him, and what black people should do if they’re pulled over by police. Crump also breaks down why the police aren’t held accountable for the brutality they inflict on black and brown communities, and how the system uses felony convictions to disenfranchise marginalized people.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5xHlFKQO9nIb73ilab2spU</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5205</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 82: DAMON YOUNG - What Doesn’t Kill You Makes You Doper </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0cWIxRutmLe2NygicUWigp?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Author Damon Young, whose memoir “What Doesn’t Kill You Makes You Blacker” was nominated for a NAACP Image award, joins Jemele to discuss the success of his book, and the origin story behind him starting the site Very Smart Brothas. Young also gets candid about the financial pressures that black men face, including how he handled being evicted and not having a driver’s license until late in adulthood. Plus, he responds to the backlash he received for a column he wrote entitled, “Straight Black Men Are The White People of Black People.” Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0cWIxRutmLe2NygicUWigp</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4089</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 81: ED GORDON - A Conversation in Truth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5MjWIXQui5jEwupVysBN4E?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Renowned journalist Ed Gordon joins Jemele to talk about his new book, “Conversations in Black,” in which he gathered some of the most influential and high-profile black figures to discuss the critical and nuanced issues in the African-American community that often are discussed in private. Ed also discusses his celebrated career at BET, where he became the face of the entertainment network’s once prominent news coverage. He also shares stories and insights from some of his most talked about interviews, which included Tupac Shakur, O.J. Simpson, Michael Jackson, Nelson Mandela and R. Kelly, among others. Plus, Ed gives his thoughts on the controversy involving CBS anchor Gayle King.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5MjWIXQui5jEwupVysBN4E</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4489</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 80: RAPSODY - Two Black Women Did This Podcast</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5mWrWQet5ZV2f7Mo3gK92Y?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rapper Rapsody joins Jemele to discuss her critically-acclaimed album, “Eve,” which was an ode to some of the most influential and creative black women of our time. Rapsody shares why she decided to create a rap album dedicated entirely to black women, and why she named her upcoming tour, “A Black Woman Created This.” Rapsody also discusses her relationship with respected producer 9th Wonder, clamoring for respect in a male-dominated industry, and what it meant to get a huge co-sign from megastar Cardi B.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5mWrWQet5ZV2f7Mo3gK92Y</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3252</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 79: HAHA DAVIS - He’s Working-Working</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0pGUa1U6vYXBg5akztrFQe?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Comedian Haha Davis joins Jemele to discuss his incredible Internet stardom, and how he’s transitioned his social media success into an entertainment career. He also shares the difficulty of gaining respect in the stand-up comedy world as a “Internet comedian,” and how he comes up with some his famous slogans. Plus, Haha remembers his friend Juice WRLD, who passed away last December. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0pGUa1U6vYXBg5akztrFQe</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3167</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 78: MEAGAN GOOD - Pushed Off, Only To Fly</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5hx8V83t9nOmbZNNeqbJcI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actress Meagan Good joins Jemele to discuss her 30-year acting career and what helped her transition smoothly from child to adult actor. She also discusses how her Christian faith helps her stay grounded in her career and marriage. She reveals why her and husband, motivational speaker and author, Devon Franklin, decided to disclose the fact they were celibate before marriage and if their openness about their faith has placed any additional pressure on their marriage. Plus, Meagan shares why, despite her strong faith, she doesn’t attend church as much as she once did. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5hx8V83t9nOmbZNNeqbJcI</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4814</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 77: 9TH WONDER - Chance Favors the Well-Prepared</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7kfVliaYLT8Tbz8VXpTBLU?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Hip hop scholar and producer extraordinaire 9th Wonder joins Jemele to discuss hip hop as a genius art form, why today’s hip-hop fans have a different relationship with music than first generation fans, and why it was important for him to teach the history of hip-hop at Duke and North Carolina Central. He also shares the remarkable story of how he came to produce “Threat” on Jay-Z’s “The Black Album, and he makes the definitive case for why his fellow homegrown native Michael Jordan is the greatest basketball player ever. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7kfVliaYLT8Tbz8VXpTBLU</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5554</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 76: FREDDIE GIBBS - #GoodCrack</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6cSNmlwSksfESqcN54B9vN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rapper Freddie Gibbs joins Jemele to discuss his journey as an independent artist, and how it felt to have several media outlets name his album “Bandana,” as one of the best hip-hop albums of 2019. He also shares what it was like growing up in Gary, Indiana, and tells the story of how Michael Jackson and his father were once rivals — and why Freddie ultimately aided with Michael Jackson. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6cSNmlwSksfESqcN54B9vN</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4371</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 75: LUKE JAMES - To Feel Loved</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4ANCG84sdqRGLtrdMlQvq2?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele reacts to the tragic death of Kobe Bryant, and explains the unique way their relationship formed. She is later joined by R &amp; B singer Luke James, who opens up to Jemele about going through a period of not feeling appreciated by the music industry, and how that impacted his ability to create. He also shares the story of how Tyrese discovered him, what it was like going through a New Edition boot camp to prepare for his role as Johnny Gill in the BET biopic, and how he handled opening up for Beyoncé. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ANCG84sdqRGLtrdMlQvq2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5111</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 74: JACKIE CHRISTIE - Getting Down To The Nitty-Gritty</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5Kotvuir1G6C4qUBuSUzkz?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jackie Christie, who stars in the hit VH-1 reality series ‘Basketball Wives,’ joins Jemele to discuss why Basketball Wives has become a fixture in popular culture and whether the criticisms that the show fuels negative perceptions of black women are fair. Jackie also discusses some of the explosive storylines from season 8, including a cast member’s claim that show engages in colorist. She also shares her real life love story with former NBA player Doug Christie, and how they’ve maintained a marriage of nearly 25 years.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5Kotvuir1G6C4qUBuSUzkz</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4308</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 73: MICHAEL ERIC DYSON - Intelligent, Erudite Strategy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5DoZnVEsmvraXhpbOa5flu?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Renowned author, preacher and academic Michael Eric Dyson joins Jemele to discuss his latest book, “Jay-Z: Made In America,” which covers the journey of the hip-hop billionaire. He also debates Jay-Z’s controversial partnership with the NFL, and shares what he thinks ousted quarterback Colin Kaepernick should do next. Also, Dyson discusses how the world would respond to Martin Luther King, Jr., in present day.   Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5DoZnVEsmvraXhpbOa5flu</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6455</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 72: ANTHONY HAMILTON - A Little Cornbread, Fish and Collard Greens</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3e6wKxrtwxorLXM5x1ksuG?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>R&amp;B heavyweight Anthony Hamilton joins Jemele to discuss his upcoming album, his North Carolina roots, and his love of cooking. He also discusses what it’s like being the father of six boys, plus he shares some of his most memorable fan encounters and reveals where he keeps the panties that women have thrown on stage while he’s performing. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e6wKxrtwxorLXM5x1ksuG</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3820</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 71: LAKEITH STANFIELD - Permanence is Weird</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7x8D1qaoJc2XEqvjwTQ4PK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Lakeith Stanfield joins Jemele to discuss his hit movie “Uncut Gems,” his upcoming project “The Photograph,” a highly-anticipated black love story, and adjusting to sudden fame. He also discusses the unique way in which he got into acting, and why he initially thought his character Darius in the successful series “Atlanta,” was stupid. Plus, he shares why he once impersonated Donald Trump on Twitter. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7x8D1qaoJc2XEqvjwTQ4PK</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4417</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 70: ANGELA RYE - Don’t Be That Ancestor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0pFJiG7jVSw1MXkXHA8K7A?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Political pundit and strategist Angela Rye joins Jemele to discuss the apathy among black millennial voters, the importance of African Americans seizing their political power and her thoughts on why the black presidential candidates failed to gain traction among black voters. She also shares the personal story of why she decided to freeze her eggs, and what she’s learned about parenting from helping to raise her godchildren. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0pFJiG7jVSw1MXkXHA8K7A</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3354</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 69: MICHAEL EALY - Be A Star</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3TI3sIGi1qsVsjz8zR3V6Z?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Michael Ealy joins Jemele to discuss his acting career, how he’s able to tap into playing darker characters, and why he turned down a prominent role in Beyoncé’s video, “Irreplaceable.” Ealy, who also stars in ABC series “Stumptown,” also discusses teaching his children about race, and shares why honesty always is the best policy in relationships. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3TI3sIGi1qsVsjz8zR3V6Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3910</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 68: IAN WALLACE - Introducing The Wallaces</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/76WpD3TpVjaItLF1hli0It?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Ian and Jemele recap their epic wedding, spilling all the details they weren’t previously allowed to share before. They discuss what celebrities were in attendance, which guests were the drunkest, who hooked up at the wedding and one of the most discussed moments — the best man’s speech. Ian and Jemele also rank their favorite moments from the wedding, and reveal the surprise performer who sang at the ceremony and reception. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76WpD3TpVjaItLF1hli0It</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4175</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 67: TRINA - Don’t Play With Me</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2991kwaj22OhGMHyz0PGEt?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rap star Trina joins Jemele to discuss how she’s maintained her 20-plus-year career at a such high level. She explains why her and Trick Daddy have such good chemistry, and shares the story of the one lyric Trick tried to get her to say on their blockbuster hit “Nann,” but she refused. She also discusses why it’s important for her to mentor upcoming female rappers and why the industry is prejudiced against women hip-hop artists. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2991kwaj22OhGMHyz0PGEt</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4320</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 66: OMAR EPPS - Duality</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2EN1wmxv3M259CwSkVi2Rv?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Omar Epps joins Jemele to discuss his iconic film “Juice,” and his relationship with Tupac Shakur. He also discusses how he changed his acting career mid-stream, the book he wrote on black fatherhood and the one role he still regrets not landing. Plus, he shares his thoughts on his beloved Dallas Cowboys and dispels the rumors that he and Pittsburgh Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin are the same person.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2EN1wmxv3M259CwSkVi2Rv</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4266</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 65: ERIKA ALEXANDER - ”Black People Can Sell Everything”</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0Tygvk4cHbAm7YmjTeuCUY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The ‘Living Single’ and ‘The Cosby Show’ star stops by to discuss how not “fitting into a box” as a black actress led her to co-found Color Farm Media. She tells Jemele how she went from a Hilary Clinton fan to working on her campaign. Erika also shares stories about her grandmother who was a witch. She also gets emotional talking about being close to quitting acting. And Jemele gets to the bottom of if ‘Friends’ actually ripped off ‘Living Single’. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0Tygvk4cHbAm7YmjTeuCUY</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3732</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 64: LARRY WILMORE - Comedy Is Provocation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4RIiy7IZfbAYWMpmgDlABr?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The writer, producer, actor and show creator who “cornered the black show market” from ‘The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air’ to ‘Blackish’ to ‘Insecure’ details his unique journey through comedy.Larry reflects on being a part of the groundbreaking sketch comedy show ‘In Living Color’ and how he created a space for himself in Hollywood. They discuss the time Larry dropped the N word on President Obama. And Jemele gets his scorching hot sports takes including why he says there is no debate between Jordan vs LeBron. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4RIiy7IZfbAYWMpmgDlABr</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4242</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 63: LIL DUVAL - Smile</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4zty9uME9176AprH0l85l0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Comedian and artist behind the chart-topping hit “Smile” stops by to tell Jemele how he’s truly living his best life. Duval reflects on his youth before comedy when he sold drugs. The flag bearer of the “Black Men Don’t Cheat” movement explains what the phrase and song really mean. He dives into what it was like to open for Beyoncé and Jay-z. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4zty9uME9176AprH0l85l0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3762</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 62: BIG K.R.I.T. - A King Remembered In Time</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3ITUB8QFIQf02YRsHAimOt?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The man Jemele calls a “musical savant” and the artist behind K.R.I.T. IZ HERE discusses his latest album and how playing the cello in the 5th grade shaped his music career. The Meridian, MS lyricist also breaks down the difference between country and southern.K.R.I.T. tells Jemele how losing a game of Madden to his father motivated him as a rapper. He also opens up about when he hit his lowest point in his battle with anxiety and how the death of Nipsey Hussle impacted him.And in ‘This Or That’, Jemele gets K.R.I.T. to pick a side in the controversial “sugar vs salt” in grits debate. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ITUB8QFIQf02YRsHAimOt</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3600</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 61: SOPHIA CHANG - “The Baddest Bitch In The Room”</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5vPk59ySajrRKjwwsD7bRf?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Hip-Hop trailblazer and the woman Method Man calls “Wu-Tang’s” muse stops by to discuss her audio memoir. Sophia opens up to Jemele about her path into the hip-hop industry as a Korean-Canadian woman, and why she’s the self-proclaimed “baddest bitch in the room.” She explains how immersing herself into hip-hop culture and Wu-Tang sparked her own “Asian Renaissance.” Sophia also helps Jemele settle a heated debate between her and Ian about who is the leader of The Wu-Tang. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5vPk59ySajrRKjwwsD7bRf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4829</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 60: STAN VAN GUNDY - The Pepsi Swig</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2BjBC5pYa00QLHkwzdXRpk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The always candid former NBA coach and current TNT analyst opens up to Jemele about his relationships with Shaq and Dwight Howard and why he chooses Lebron over MJ. He also sets the record straight on what really happened at the end of his tenure with Pat Riley and the Miami Heat. Plus, Stan gives his opinion on the NBA-China saga and why he refuses to “stick to sports.”   Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2BjBC5pYa00QLHkwzdXRpk</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5754</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 59: NEIL BROWN JR. - Sip The Juice</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/24boQA2XIMKGB9snwYB2Gv?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The star of CBS’ ‘Seal Team’ and Lawrence’s juice sipping best friend on ‘Insecure’ drops by to share how martial arts turned into an acting career. He discusses all things ‘Insecure’, including his thoughts on #LawrenceHive. He also tells Jemele what it was like to get the co-sign from Dr. Dre and Ice Cube for his role as DJ Yella in ‘Straight Outta Compton’. And with 19 years of marriage under his belt, Neil drops some gems for a now newlywed Jemele. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24boQA2XIMKGB9snwYB2Gv</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3925</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 58: SETH MEYERS - A "Two-Fer"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3wyBVnAZwTluSGSD2c4Fag?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The SNL alum and ‘Late Night with Seth Meyers’ host joins Jemele to discuss his comedic journey, and his new Netflix special ‘Lobby Baby.’ Seth also shares his thoughts on the fondness, or lack thereof President Trump has for him, he also gives us the inside scoop on what it’s like to get drunk with Rihanna. And of course Jemele and Seth unpack the final season of ‘Game of Thrones.’ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3wyBVnAZwTluSGSD2c4Fag</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2813</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 57: IAN WALLACE - We UnBothered</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6AMRDfAdAI9FFhA4lzck3w?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele’s fiance, Ian Wallace, joins the podcast to discuss their upcoming wedding. They also discuss how they met, their first date, and why the time was right for marriage. They both also admit their biggest fears heading into marriage, and they try to find common ground over their differences — Ian’s lukewarm feelings toward the Wu Tang Clan and Jemele’s refusal to root for his favorite NFL team, the Detroit Lions. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6AMRDfAdAI9FFhA4lzck3w</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4150</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 56: THE BRIDESMAIDS - We Classy and Stuff</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2nzFGn7RiX6apxsoT18VuV?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele sits down with the six Bridesmaids in her upcoming wedding — Kelley Carter, Cari Champion, Dej Peyton, Chantre Camack, Jameka Peyton, and Amina Hussein. They discuss the roots of their friendship, and give their honest thoughts on Jemele’s fiancé. They also share some marital advice with Jemele and discuss which of the bridesmaids is most likely to hook up with someone at the wedding.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2nzFGn7RiX6apxsoT18VuV</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4000</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 55: SNOOP DOGG -  The Gangsta Professional</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7vzPoEOfX1DnzdQe0Uykbt?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Snoop Dogg joins Jemele for an all-encompassing conversation about his life and career. He discusses how he‘s maintained his authenticity despite massive commercial success, reflects on his days as a Death Row artist, and his friendships with both Biggie and Tupac. Snoop also shares why he never liked ‘Pac’s diss track, “Hit Em Up’” and if there will ever be a movie made about Death Row.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7vzPoEOfX1DnzdQe0Uykbt</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5614</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 54: VAN LATHAN - Life Between Cheat Meals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0Q9Zxc4EgPvxhWq5gCwwgY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Van Lathan joins Jemele to discuss being fired from TMZ, and what he plans to do next. He also discusses his famous confrontation with Kanye West, his weight loss journey and his upcoming book.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0Q9Zxc4EgPvxhWq5gCwwgY</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5080</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 53: OMAR GOODING - Fresh Pedicure Confidence</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/24WZ8B2kVcSiIm7Qb0ps69?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor and producer Omar Gooding joins Jemele Hill to discuss what it’s like acting, producing and writing for the Bounce TV sitcom “Family Time,” which is in its seventh season. He also discusses what it was like growing up in a family full of entertainers, and why he never resented the success of his brother, Cuba Gooding Jr. Plus, Omar shares the incredible backstory behind his starring role in the now-defunct show, “Playmakers.” The Laker superfan also explains why he considers himself a “Kobeist.” Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24WZ8B2kVcSiIm7Qb0ps69</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3815</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 52: RAJON RONDO - Call a Spade a Spade</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7aniixT3R1QNiXZt4gKmGg?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Los Angeles Lakers point guard Rajon Rondo joins Jemele to discuss whether championship expectations for the Lakers this season are fair, his desire to be a coach and general manager some day, and how much longer he sees himself playing in the NBA. He also discusses playing with LeBron James as opposed to competing against him, and how he sees LeBron and Anthony Davis meshing together as teammates.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7aniixT3R1QNiXZt4gKmGg</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4239</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 51: ROY WOOD JR. - Selling Tapes Out Of The Trunk</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5SPJaRAGYhBDRoR80WoIm4?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Comedian Roy Wood Jr. joins Jemele to discuss how ‘cancel culture’ has impacted comedians, and how the business of comedy has changed. He also discusses how he got his start, his work on Comedy Central’s ’The Daily Show,’ and he shares the story of how shoplifting at Dillard’s led to his career at comedy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5SPJaRAGYhBDRoR80WoIm4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4548</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 50: BEBE WINANS - Born For This</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4KJ1I8OIaFZuBDgqR8Rh9E?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Gospel legend BeBe Winans joins Jemele to discuss his new book, “Born For This,” how he overcame a gambling addiction, his close friendship with Whitney Houston and how he formed a successful duo with his sister, CeCe. He also discusses his new solo album, “Need You.” Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4KJ1I8OIaFZuBDgqR8Rh9E</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4108</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 49: SEN. CORY BOOKER - The Impotency of Empathy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5PahOiL7PWkxAwbhgONech?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>New Jersey Senator and presidential candidate Cory Booker joins Jemele to discuss the Donald Trump impeachment inquiry, why Americans shouldn’t feel disillusioned by the current state of American politics, and how he’s preparing for the upcoming presidential debate. He also shares his aggressive plan to combat the exploitation of college athletes, and prevent professional sports owners from colluding against players. He also confesses something that might get him in trouble with his girlfriend, actress Rosario Dawson.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5PahOiL7PWkxAwbhgONech</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4210</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 48: MAYA MOORE - Colossians 3:23</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4FcseUnGpiuYQQ8CbnM5hk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>WNBA superstar Maya Moore joins Jemele to discuss her decision to not play the 2019 WNBA season in order to focus on overturning the conviction of Johnathan Irons, who received a 50-year sentence after being convicted of a nonfatal shooting of a homeowner during a burglary, despite questionable evidence. Moore addresses whether she plans to return to basketball in 2020, what she’s learned about herself away from the game, and how she is using her criminal justice reform organization, Win With Justice, to create change. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4FcseUnGpiuYQQ8CbnM5hk</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4930</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 47: TARANA BURKE - The Valleys Will Kill You</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4chytRhcaCiWfpd4xEeEa4?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Tarana Burke, the founder of the #MeToo movement, joins Jemele to discuss the two-year anniversary of the powerful campaign that gave sexual abuse survivors a voice and created an international conversation. She discusses the progress the movement, and how media coverage has undermined the true messaging of #MeToo. She also explains the many misconceptions about sexual violence, how we need to address what consent means for both genders and how black women in particular have struggled to find intra-community support when it comes to the sexual violence they experience. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4chytRhcaCiWfpd4xEeEa4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5110</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 46: BOKEEM WOODBINE - Warning: This Person Is Different Than He Appears</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2Khx6eBXxAhs6QmmsQMRZ7?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Bokeem Woodbine joins Jemele to discuss his 20-plus years in the business, his role in the upcoming film “Queen &amp; Slim,” and how he handled being in a career slump. He also opens up about how his physical appearance made it easier to be typecast. Plus, he shares the story of how him and Tupac bonded over smoking marijuana. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2Khx6eBXxAhs6QmmsQMRZ7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4153</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 45: LARENZ TATE - Brother To The Night</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3WNJQuHkehCLHxjnohnF0A?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Larenz Tate joins Jemele to discuss the final season of his hit show ‘Power’, how he landed the role as Councilman Rashad Tate and why fans of the show are so dedicated. He also discusses some of his iconic roles in Menace II Society, Love Jones, Why Do Fools Fall in Love and Dead Presidents.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3WNJQuHkehCLHxjnohnF0A</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4375</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 44: CANDACE PARKER - Never Cheat The Game</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2OsAppGIgwqKyjEqCRJMS6?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>WNBA star and Turner Sports basketball analyst Candace Parker joins Jemele to discuss her 12th season with the Los Angeles Sparks, and her favorite memories of her former college coach, Pat Summitt. She also shares the story of dunking on a Tennessee men’s basketball player, how being a parent has changed her, her broadcasting career and how she concerned she is with whether her numerous injuries will impact her quality of life. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2OsAppGIgwqKyjEqCRJMS6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3857</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 43: NICOLE LYNN - A Different Level of Grit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1iZfXdB4SxbWpvILtUgFu5?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Sports agent Nicole Lynn joins Jemele to discuss becoming the first black woman to ever represent a top-5 pick in the 2019 NFL draft and also just the third woman ever in the draft’s 83-year history to rep a first rounder. She shares the story of how she landed New York Jets defensive tackle Quinnen Williams, the third overall pick, as a client. She also discusses how she manages the different challenges she faces as a black female sports agent, and what it’s like working for Lil Wayne’s Young Money Sports. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1iZfXdB4SxbWpvILtUgFu5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4068</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 42: TEDDY RILEY - The Music Man</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6JFqaNrhWckDy5N95lsgj2?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Historic hitmaker Teddy Riley joins Jemele for a deep dive into his origin story. He discusses what encouraged him to pursue music, how his career almost never happened because of an early drug arrest as a teenager, and how he came up with “New Jack Swing.” Having produced both Michael Jackson and Prince, Teddy also shares his insight into their rivalry and creative genius. Plus, he settles the debate about which was the better album: Thriller or Off The Wall? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6JFqaNrhWckDy5N95lsgj2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2946</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 41: JESSE WILLIAMS - It’s A Love Movement</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/426kiWEAWNw5Rad7QBFfgk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Grey’s Anatomy star Jesse Williams joins Jemele to discuss why the show has resonated with people for so long, and what he’s learned from Grey’s creator Shonda Rhimes. Jesse also discusses his deep involvement in activism, why it’s important to him and whether he worried his passion for social justice issues would cost him Hollywood opportunities.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">426kiWEAWNw5Rad7QBFfgk</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3995</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 40: JOHNNY GILL - The Game Changer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/58giMhJJZE7rAfXb6YUVbh?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>R&amp;B legend Johnny Gill joins Jemele to discuss his new album “Game Changer II,” and why he’s excelled at making classic love songs. He also discusses the latest conflict within New Edition, and why he believes the iconic group will eventually reunite.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58giMhJJZE7rAfXb6YUVbh</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3757</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 39: DEBORAH JOY WINANS - Nothing But God</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0owDvkh8bzWxJKyXJ7xFYa?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actress Deborah Joy Winans joins Jemele to discuss the new season of her hit television show, “Greenleaf.” She also discusses why she chose acting over singing, despite growing up in a famous gospel family and shares the incredible story of how Oprah Winfrey discovered her. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0owDvkh8bzWxJKyXJ7xFYa</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4184</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 38: DAVID OYELOWO - Royalty</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0kc65MDAFpd06GqwOtF27l?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor David Oyelowo joins Jemele to discuss his new movie, ‘Don’t Let Go,’ a supernatural thriller that hits theaters on August 30th. David also discusses how he’s handled playing historical figures such as Martin Luther King Jr, and Tuskegee airman Joe “Lightning” Little. He also shares the story of his royal lineage. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0kc65MDAFpd06GqwOtF27l</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3989</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 37: LUTHER CAMPBELL - Parental Advisory</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3U7xOvXgYwboqgCm93r16g?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Hip hop legend Luther Campbell joins Jemele to discuss his music, life, career and passions, which include sports and politics. Jemele and Luke dive into how 2 Live Crew’s landmark Supreme Court case impacted the conversation about free speech. Luke also discusses 2 Live Crew’s bitter breakup, offers thoughts on the Democratic presidential field and explains why there should be a black-owned sports network. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3U7xOvXgYwboqgCm93r16g</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5627</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 36: ROBIN THEDE - A Black Lady Podcast</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5dynTubiTEHgpaj80AyRE5?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Robin Thede, creator and star of the new HBO sketch series ‘A Black Lady Sketch Show,’ joins Jemele to discuss why she specifically created a comedy show for only black women, and why she believes black women in comedy often are treated as invisible. She also shares her dream list of black women she’d like to see perform in sketches on her show, and explains what life was like growing up in a trailer park in Iowa. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5dynTubiTEHgpaj80AyRE5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3499</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 35: RAPHAEL SAADIQ - Town Business</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0Zfv2dCnkGRbsjijMMCsOl?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The multi-talented Raphael Saadiq joins Jemele to discuss his new album Jimmy Lee, his first solo project in eight years. Raphael also discusses what it was like touring with Prince at 19 years old, and the breakup of his revolutionary R &amp; B band Tony! Toni! Tone! Plus, he shares the backstory behind some of his most iconic love songs. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0Zfv2dCnkGRbsjijMMCsOl</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4387</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 34: VINCE STAPLES - Straight Up, No Chaser</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3UJQUHJ8Wvk9bfSYwYIy2T?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Hip-hop artist Vince Staples joins Jemele live from Capitol Music Group's 6th annual Capitol Congress music event to discuss his upcoming project, “The Vince Staples Show.” Vince also discusses his upbringing in Long Beach, and what led him to a rap career, even though he had never listened to Jay-Z, Nas or many other rap legends before he began performing. He also shares candid opinions on why he didn’t like Kobe Bryant as a basketball player, and why he doesn’t believe Tupac’s “Dear Mama” wouldn’t be a hit in present day.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3UJQUHJ8Wvk9bfSYwYIy2T</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4071</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 33: NIECY NASH - Working Not Twerking</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5DE7Ov4kOpRlXm8XsTIxCG?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Niecy Nash joins Jemele to discuss her starring role as Desna Simms, the female boss on TNT’s ‘Claws.’ Niecy also discusses starting her acting career as a wife and mother of three children, and what it’s like being Shaq’s neighbor. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5DE7Ov4kOpRlXm8XsTIxCG</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3502</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 32: RICK ROSS - That Rozay Seasoning</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5xQkd95gC0jKfXEt9Sb2tJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rapper and boss Rick Ross joins Jemele to discuss his new album, “Port of Miami 2,” the follow-up to his classic debut in 2006. He also reveals why he has such strong chemistry with Drake, and if fans can expect a collaboration album between the two hip-hop heavyweights in the future. Plus, Rozay ranks his 10 albums. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5xQkd95gC0jKfXEt9Sb2tJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3804</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 31: KARRUECHE TRAN - Just Keep Going</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/03kgC9CchqsJ0SPpA9dQPG?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor Karrueche Tran joins Jemele to discuss her hit television show “Claws,” how she dealt with sudden fame and the difficulties of getting people to take her seriously as an actor. She also lists her favorite Atlanta strip clubs, and how studying strippers in the Atlanta clubs helped her prepare for her role on “Claws.” Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03kgC9CchqsJ0SPpA9dQPG</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3365</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 30: MARSAI MARTIN - A Little One Doing Big Things</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0rkgXDBXqzqoBKYN08OLPP?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>14-year-old actress and producer Marsai Martin joins Jemele to discuss finding her passion at a young age, becoming the youngest person in Hollywood with a production deal, and how her film, ‘Little,’ changed the game for her. Her parents, Joshua and Carol, also join the podcast to discuss what it’s like raising a child star. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0rkgXDBXqzqoBKYN08OLPP</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3824</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 29: IBTIHAJ MUHAMMAD - Faith &amp; Race</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4LogROZM2uGXk6iBKb9M2W?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Former Olympic fencer Ibtihaj Muhammad joins Jemele to discuss her experience in the 2016 Olympics, where she became the first Muslim American woman to win a medal and the first woman in a hijab to compete for Team USA at the Olympics. She also reveals why she won’t be competing in the 2020 games, and the difficulty of being an African-American Muslim woman in a climate that encourages hostility toward people with her faith. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4LogROZM2uGXk6iBKb9M2W</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4361</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 28: MUSIQ SOULCHILD - Triggers and Trauma</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1Z1OCTurdQ48iEFU2Y8jqQ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Hip-hop soul artist Musiq Soulchild joins Jemele to discuss the evolution of his music career, why he rejects being labeled as only a R &amp; B artist, and next year being the 20th anniversary of his debut smash album Aijuswanaseing. He also discusses what it’s like running his own label, co-parenting and divulges which one of his classic songs he hates to sing.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1Z1OCTurdQ48iEFU2Y8jqQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4433</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 27: BARRINGTON IRVING - Reaching New Heights</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0S8KnTCJYv37qIRbZXscQA?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Barrington Irving is the first African-American to fly around to world solo, and youngest person to ever do so. He joins Jemele to discuss his incredible feat, the many dangers he faced on his unlikely journey, and why he chose aviation over a promising football career. He also discusses his relationship with slain teenager Trayvon Martin, who was his former aviation student.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0S8KnTCJYv37qIRbZXscQA</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2597</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 26: BETO O'ROURKE - Through the Fire</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7cbZD9HC1P6bfDZXWPO0Ch?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Presidential candidate Beto O’Rourke joins Jemele to discuss why he remains optimistic despite the tumultuous political and social climate, what motivates him as a politician, and why he’s confident he can boost his sagging poll numbers. He also discusses his policy positions on student loan debt, and gun control. Plus, Jemele puts Beto on the hot seat about a controversial issue: If you’re binge-watching a TV show with your significant other, is it acceptable to watch episodes without them? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7cbZD9HC1P6bfDZXWPO0Ch</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2954</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 25: KAMALA HARRIS - Starts with a ‘M,’ ends with an ‘A</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7bjFvGXtsMZyE6JhLgl4IN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Presidential candidate Kamala Harris joins Jemele for a wide-ranging conversation on why she went after former Vice President Joe Biden during the first democratic debate, and why she feels she can beat Donald Trump. She also shares her positions on marijuana legalization, the racial wealth gap, and reparations. Plus, the California senator reveals her favorite curse word.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bjFvGXtsMZyE6JhLgl4IN</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3274</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 24: WALTER MOSELY - Writing is sex</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2kD2X4WBKiQRGIijMXu5jb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Bestselling novelist Walter Mosley joins Jemele to discuss his work as a writer and consultant for the late John Singleton’s FX drama, “Snowfall.” He also discusses the secret to his longevity, why he decided to bring back his iconic character Easy Rawlings, and why he believes drugs should be legalized. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2kD2X4WBKiQRGIijMXu5jb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3189</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 23: LALA ANTHONY - Hustlers Never Sleep</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5LVjOu2CErVN9n2ywdMmOg?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>La La Anthony joins Jemele to discuss how she stays booked and busy. La La shares how she evolved from being an MTV VJ to an actress, author, producer and activist. She also discusses her hit show, “Power” coming to an end, and explains why her husband, Carmelo Anthony, deserves to be on a NBA roster next season. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5LVjOu2CErVN9n2ywdMmOg</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3506</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 22: ROTIMI - A Duel Threat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/20VtdOPvR8Cx7lCrwdIFZi?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rotimi joins Jemele to discuss his success as both an actor and singer. He shares what it means to have both a hit album (“Walk With Me”) and hit TV show (“Power”). He also explains why music is his first love, why nobody should take 50 Cent’s trolling personally and what it meant for him to pay for his first house in cash. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20VtdOPvR8Cx7lCrwdIFZi</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2239</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 21: SPIKE LEE - The Great Shit Never Gets Old</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0zNXrj2293TpiCKLbuTZMZ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Renowned filmmaker Spike Lee joins Jemele to discuss the 30th anniversary of his iconic film, “Do The Right Thing,” and why he’ll never give up his New York Knicks fandom. Jemele and Spike also debate the best Spike Lee movies of all time. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0zNXrj2293TpiCKLbuTZMZ</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3926</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 20: LIL' REL HOWERY - America’s Best Friend</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7mco0pF22iiJkZJUZGDVzD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actor and comedian Lil’ Rel Howery joins Jemele to discuss his uniquely personal brand of comedy, what went right and wrong with his network sitcom ‘Rel,’ and how his Chicago roots shaped his comedy. He also discusses his numerous upcoming movie projects, comedy influences and close friendship with star Tiffany Haddish. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7mco0pF22iiJkZJUZGDVzD</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4604</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 19: AVA DUVERNAY - The System is the Villain</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6KsUZ5TkNJVA36Upxz0M9P?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Renowned filmmaker Ava Duvernay joins Jemele to discuss her critically-acclaimed limited series, “When They See Us,” a gripping drama about the Central Park 5’s journey to exoneration. Ava also reveals why she’s drawn to stories that address the injustice people of color face in the criminal justice system. Plus, Ava also shares what it was like directing Jay-Z and Beyonce, and how she became close friends with Oprah. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6KsUZ5TkNJVA36Upxz0M9P</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3118</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep. 18: Revenge of the Stans</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5Ubq08CSEm9oMTifiAmwb7?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Michael Arcenaux and Cole Wiley join Jemele to discuss how the Beyhive claimed another victim during the NBA Finals, and which celebrities have the worst fans. Michael and Jemele share their stories about being bullied by Ciara and Rihanna’s fanbases. Also, Michael, Jemele and Cole give their thoughts on Ava DuVernay’s new critically-acclaimed Netflix series, “When They See Us.” Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5Ubq08CSEm9oMTifiAmwb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3347</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 17: TICHINA ARNOLD - Staying The Course</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2eUNgzYrd7uvl5QrNUJrKx?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Actress Tichina Arnold joins Jemele to discuss her new critically-acclaimed movie, “Last Black Man In San Francisco,” and to reminisce about her time on the iconic television show, “Martin.” She also gives the tea on whether there will be a Martin reboot, and why she’s found a lane with network sitcoms.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2eUNgzYrd7uvl5QrNUJrKx</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3503</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 16: MARTELLUS BENNETT - Weed is my coffee</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1wNtMPZTAh7jXYtGn75HhO?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Retired NFL champion Martellus Bennett joins Jemele to discuss his new children’s book, and entertains us with crazy stories from his 9-year professional career. He also discusses why he doesn’t miss pro football, and hasn’t struggled to be fulfilled in retirement. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1wNtMPZTAh7jXYtGn75HhO</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4085</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 15: TALIB KWELI - A real-life documentarian</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2MCxzgw3dw1Ph72vM63fCf?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rapper and activist Talib Kweli joins Jemele to discuss the current state of hip hop, why we haven’t seen another Blackstar album, and why he chooses to use social media to expose racism and bigotry. He also discusses his fractured relationship with Kanye West. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2MCxzgw3dw1Ph72vM63fCf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3612</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 14:  ICE CUBE - Strength of Street Knowledge</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0zOaD80NTsa9lgG73Rkj4L?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Entertainment mogul Ice Cube joins Jemele to discuss the evolution of his sports league, the Big3, which is entering its third season. He also talks about his close relationship with the late John Singleton, how he learned to never compromise on his own worth and if we might see him and his son as co-stars in an upcoming movie. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0zOaD80NTsa9lgG73Rkj4L</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4439</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 13: METTA WORLD PEACE - Up From Queensbridge</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5Y3kR1YUZa0LLceRntfzBz?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Metta World Peace, also known as Ron Artest, joins Jemele to discuss the new Showtime documentary on his life, “Quiet Storm.” Metta discusses the infamous “Malice at The Palace” brawl, which nearly destroyed his NBA career. He also discusses his troubled upbringing, why he wants to be a NBA or college basketball head coach and how his commitment to his own mental health turned him into an outspoken mental health advocate. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5Y3kR1YUZa0LLceRntfzBz</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3828</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 12: BLACK THOUGHT - How I Got Over</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5w4qYpshS3EHAq4kX7VAcv?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Black Thought joins Jemele to discuss The Roots’ origin story and evolution, the group’s transition into being the house band for The Tonight Show and why he finally feels comfortable doing solo projects. Black Thought also opens up about his childhood, including the murders of both of his parents. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5w4qYpshS3EHAq4kX7VAcv</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4220</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 11: SOLEDAD O'BRIEN - The CEO of Me, Inc</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4Q7Ox41kGlXv2mhYSkKZuD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Award winning journalist Soledad O’Brien joins Jemele to discuss how she’s turned her company into a multi-platform force, why she‘s disappointed in today’s media, and how she coped after losing both of her parents.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4Q7Ox41kGlXv2mhYSkKZuD</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4145</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 10: KATT WILLIAMS - "Cusp of Coonery"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7EFJmZsBp8sFb4Aa0rIBnW?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Comedic legend Katt Williams joins Jemele Hill to discuss his Emmy Award winning performance in the hit series “Atlanta,” and why his upcoming Netflix special will be his best one yet. He also opens up about his troubled past, including why Jesus was the inspiration for him running away at 13 years old. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7EFJmZsBp8sFb4Aa0rIBnW</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3252</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 09: DON LEMON - Tell The Truth, Shame The Devil</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5FBFeojY7vvxwcGOrNhYBI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>CNN host Don Lemon joins Jemele to discuss his recent engagement, and how he’s changed perceptions of gay black men in America. He also discusses some of his most controversial on-air moments, his ongoing feud with President Donald Trump, and why he refuses to bite his tongue, even if that means being critical of his own community.   Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5FBFeojY7vvxwcGOrNhYBI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3281</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 08: COMMON - The Last Word</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1xvbo2QsqT4T4mlYl75ZwK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rapper and actor Common joins Jemele to discuss his why he chose to reveal he was sexually molested in his new memoir, “Let Love Have The Last Word.” Plus, he shares his approach to fatherhood, and how a high school basketball injury motivated him to get serious about rap. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1xvbo2QsqT4T4mlYl75ZwK</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4030</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 07: STACEY ABRAMS - Battle For The Throne</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/01nTfHC5QjmVCuTAbb1Bd4?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Former Georgia gubernatorial candidate Stacey Abrams joins Jemele to discuss her controversial loss in the governor’s race, and if her next step is running for president. Also, Jemele, Michael and Cole break down Avengers Endgame and the current season of Game of Thrones. Plus, TMZ’s Van Lathan adds his perspective on Avengers and if Game of Thrones’ final season has lived up to the hype. Warning: Spoiler alerts! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01nTfHC5QjmVCuTAbb1Bd4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3646</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 06: TONE BELL - Uncomfortable, But Not Offended</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/11ruVGUSapReBiCzVrftYr?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>How did actor and comedian Tone Bell go from being a first-grade teacher to starring in Issa Rae and Marsai Martin’s new film, “Little”? Tone discusses his meteoric rise with Jemele, as well as how he’s found his voice in comedy. He also discusses the complications of dating when you’re on the rise, and why he still checks his student loan balance, even though he doesn’t owe anything.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11ruVGUSapReBiCzVrftYr</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3338</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 05: CHARLAMAGNE THE GOD - For the 9-9 and the 2000</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7HrS48BvSe6SnFnlrU2vWi?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Provocative commentator Charlamagne tha God joins Jemele to discuss his rocky relationship with syndicated talk show host Wendy Williams. He also opens up about his estranged relationship with his father, and what he tells his daughters about his troubled past.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7HrS48BvSe6SnFnlrU2vWi</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3557</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 04: CHARLES BARKLEY - Still Not A Role Model</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7FYqIZFMQN1DSL9iKkBosi?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Basketball Hall of Famer and TNT analyst Charles Barkley joins Jemele to give his take on his old friend Tiger Woods winning the 2019 Masters, Magic Johnson quitting his job with the Lakers, and if Dwyane Wade will be a television star in retirement. Plus, Charles also tells Jemele about how recently visited The White House for secret meeting with Jared Kushner. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7FYqIZFMQN1DSL9iKkBosi</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4355</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 03: T.I. - Cheers and BooS</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6D4Xsf7AjPeCVOwkkmJZbZ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rapper, actor, activist and entrepreneur T.I., joins Jemele to discuss the new season of his family-inspired reality show, “T.I. &amp; Tiny: Friends &amp; Family Hustle,” as well as his new film project with Eddie Murphy. T.I., also explains why he felt it was important to call out Kodak Black, Kanye West and Floyd Mayweather. Plus, T.I., reveals why it’s important for him to mentor this current generation of hip-hop artists. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6D4Xsf7AjPeCVOwkkmJZbZ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3995</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 02: KILLER MIKE - "Up Negro Creek"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3khFc57fzFzVWduyi5n3Cs?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rapper and entrepreneur Killer Mike joins Jemele to dive deep into Nipsey Hussle’s legacy, and how he and other notable hip hop artists are trying to leave a different financial blueprint for today’s rappers. Killer Mike and Jemele also discuss why it’s important to kill more people’s dreams. Mike also makes the case for why only Bernie Sanders can beat Donald Trump in the next election. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3khFc57fzFzVWduyi5n3Cs</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3603</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep 01: Death and Taxes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2cZpn6fo0nDEBz3rRKMtgU?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On the debut episode, Jemele, Michael and Cole discuss the conflicting reactions to Tiger Woods’ Masters victory. Jemele also has some harsh words for Tiger fans who want to play the nobody-believed-in-Tiger card. Plus, Nipsey Hussle’s home-going, Tax Day drama,  how to quit like Magic, and Jemele surprisingly defends someone whose opinions she doesn’t respect. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cZpn6fo0nDEBz3rRKMtgU</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3081</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jemele Hill is Unbothered Premieres Monday April 15th</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3bIJRAHqgxT8d0T0hvPeAs?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jemele Hill is Unbothered Premieres Monday April 15th. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3bIJRAHqgxT8d0T0hvPeAs</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>100</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

