<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Living &amp; Learning with Reba McEntire</title>
    <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/7yORoNNwZKmTQWuCvz0KCc</link>
    <description>Living &amp; Learning with Reba McEntire is a new podcast inspired and informed by the way Reba approaches life: with an insatiable curiosity, dedication to expanding her knowledge, and reliance on her own lived experience. Join Reba as she invites guests into the studio for intriguing conversations every episode.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8af5aa02e2a5f89389dba1622e</url>
      <title>Living &amp; Learning with Reba McEntire</title>
      <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/7yORoNNwZKmTQWuCvz0KCc</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:48:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Well, Bless Your Heart with Leanne Morgan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0Ttr5vhlbJ39zGDQbr2D2p?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Our season finale goes out with a bang with hilarious comic Leanne Morgan joining Reba for some real talk and big laughs. Leanne’s humor is all about getting down and dirty with the funny stuff of real life. Reba chats with Leanne about surviving the mean teen daughter years to sharing Jello recipes with fans to balancing touring with being a new grandmother. Catch Leanne Morgan on her Big Panty Tour across the U.S. now! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0Ttr5vhlbJ39zGDQbr2D2p</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2624</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Change with Mickey Guyton</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4j2zGmlzLGERZO25AJjbyp?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Reba finally meets the lovely Mickey Guyton, one of the hottest and most powerful voices in country music today with her acclaimed debut album, Remember Her Name. They connect over the value of patience in their careers, building confidence and listening to your inner voice, and the importance of making country music an even more equal place. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4j2zGmlzLGERZO25AJjbyp</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2093</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Listening with Hoda Kotb</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6yXsOpicS5AnPMGvI6qtIH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>TODAY’s groundbreaking (and grounded) host Hoda Kotb sits down with Reba to talk about where they find inspiration, the art of interviewing and learning from others, and Hoda’s special love of country music! Stick around for a special preview of Hoda’s podcast, Making Space, featuring Oprah Winfrey and Maria Shriver.Listen to Making Space with Hoda Kotb on Spotify. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6yXsOpicS5AnPMGvI6qtIH</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1513</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Life of Laughter with Carol Burnett</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1cpcN4jJk8662DAtPuHWpL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Iconic actress and legendary funny lady Carol Burnett calls up Reba for a heartwarming chat about special memories in show business, the glamorous influence of Carol Burnett Show costume designer Bob Mackie, and the important ways that times have changed for women. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1cpcN4jJk8662DAtPuHWpL</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1837</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living the Dream with Keith Urban</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/39Mjw41LWfkLfysR0ITgS2?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The endlessly charming Keith Urban kicks back with Reba for a down-to-earth chat about music, marriage, family, purpose, and a touching peek into the formative childhood memories that set Keith and Reba on their creative paths as performers. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39Mjw41LWfkLfysR0ITgS2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2064</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding the Sacred in the Everyday with Becca Stevens</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2hlP9qhYF2UOGQZCKBDJNO?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Reba visits with Becca Stevens, the inspiring founder of Thistle Farms, a global organization based in Nashville which employs, houses, and supports women who’ve escaped domestic violence and sex trafficking. They talk about the incredible work of Thistle Farms, Becca’s own spiritual background as a down-to-earth Episcopal priest, and her new book, “Practically Divine,” a guide to seeing the sacred in the everyday. Content warning: this episode does discuss topics relating to domestic and sexual abuse. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2hlP9qhYF2UOGQZCKBDJNO</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2357</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Good Times with Brooks &amp; Dunn</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6LWMfx0PAKqmHdFxlqa5SA?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Just in time for the closing run of Reba and Brooks &amp; Dunn: Together in Vegas residency at Caesars Palace, Reba visits with pals Kix Brooks and Ronnie Dunn about being back out on the road, appreciating the slow-down of the pandemic, and the many memories (and mischief) of being onstage together for three decades. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6LWMfx0PAKqmHdFxlqa5SA</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1644</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting in the Spirit with Norm Lewis</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1hsSzFTPnnLn9xkBEDAhOx?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today’s guest Norm Lewis co-stars with Reba in the upcoming Lifetime movie, Christmas in Tune, out November 26! The acclaimed Broadway star and screen actor chats with Reba about theater, cherished holiday traditions, and the two take a fun spin on new Christmas song classics. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1hsSzFTPnnLn9xkBEDAhOx</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2108</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitting Your Stride with Jean Smart</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7tyw9JRQbKTrhVZihL7POn?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Reba connects with legendary actress Jean Smart on her incredible run of successful shows (including HBO’s Hacks and Mare of Easttown), staying grounded through the ups and downs of their careers, and navigating loss with grace. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7tyw9JRQbKTrhVZihL7POn</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2370</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working Together with Lady A</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6jfkDro66SAadwVoxo33Vt?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Hillary Scott, Charles Kelley and Dave Haywood of Lady A join Reba from tour, where they reflect on parenting while on the road, their new record What A Song Can Do, working together while apart, and the rewards of giving back. Check out Lady A’s new album, What A Song Can Do, on Spotify! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6jfkDro66SAadwVoxo33Vt</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2278</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Being True To Yourself with Trisha Yearwood</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0VfLqVWp7lVBWEp6NleSG4?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Reba catches up with her old friend, Trisha Yearwood, for a chat about staying true to yourself through all of life’s changes, as well as the things that matter most in life: family, food, and our furry friends. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0VfLqVWp7lVBWEp6NleSG4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2182</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Relationships with Rex Linn</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7abbsH8iD2kMBjOci5pX1u?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On our first episode of Season 2, Reba sits down to reveal a supporting character from last season who now has a leading role...Reba’s boyfriend, actor Rex Linn! They dish about the building blocks of a lasting relationship, discuss the unique work of long distance dating, and play a game to test how well they really know each other. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7abbsH8iD2kMBjOci5pX1u</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2679</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Season 2!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0rms5SkUyz7LyoQBL9rc4R?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Reba McEntire is back for season 2 of Living &amp; Learning! She invites Living &amp; Learning listeners to join her on her journey to discuss and grow with some very important people in her life. Join us on 10/25 for new episodes only on Spotify. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0rms5SkUyz7LyoQBL9rc4R</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>82</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking Back, Looking Forward</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4hU54I6OoBGnPankRl4gmw?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Reba and Melissa reflect back on all the best memories from the Living and Learning season: their favorite guest moments, biggest laughs, and all the most meaningful learnings they’ve walked away with. Plus, they discuss plans for the holidays and thoughts and hopes for the year ahead. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4hU54I6OoBGnPankRl4gmw</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3920</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rejection with Rita Moreno</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/19IJ3wiU3c3LCKqL84sZft?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Reba and Melissa take on the tough topic of rejection - how to take it gracefully, how to get past it, and when to push back. They discuss their own experiences with setbacks in their careers and personal lives and how they made it through. They are then joined by a very special guest, actress and singer Rita Moreno, who talks about her sixty plus year career in film, TV, and stage, as well as dating complicated men, trying to break into the industry as a woman of color, and the wisdom she gleaned along the way. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19IJ3wiU3c3LCKqL84sZft</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2208</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manners with Jay and Allison DeMarcus and Myka Meier</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5iRIOM5fv0NpWcOFS5226K?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Reba and Melissa discuss a topic near and dear to Reba’s heart: manners. Specifically, what manners mean in today’s fast-paced digital age, and why they’re still as important as ever. Etiquette expert Myka Meier provides insights into the new standards for minding your manners, and the ladies have a rollicking conversation with Jay and Allison DeMarcus of the new Netflix show DeMarcus Family Rules about how they approach instilling manners in their children - and in each other. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5iRIOM5fv0NpWcOFS5226K</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2851</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinventing Yourself with Darius Rucker and Heather Havrilesky</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/18SMh8m6jinFg5flYKVBCk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Reba and Melissa explore the idea of reinventing yourself, how life is a constant evolution and how to approach your own desires for change. Their expert guest, advice columnist and author Heather Havrilesky offers her top five tips on self-reinvention, big or small, and the ladies talk to singer Darius Rucker about going from lead singer of the rock band Hootie and the Blowfish to becoming an acclaimed country star, and the importance of authenticity in all phases of life. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18SMh8m6jinFg5flYKVBCk</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2435</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancel Culture with Karamo Brown and Jen Hatmaker</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1gSCVCpKUYRd79qPfBTCn1?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Reba and Melissa get into the complicated and timely topic of cancel culture - what is it, when is it necessary, and when does it go too far. They’re joined by author Jen Hatmaker and Karamo Brown from Netflix’s Queer Eye for some eye-opening conversations about what it means to forgive and how we handle making mistakes in our own lives. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1gSCVCpKUYRd79qPfBTCn1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3100</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parenting with Thomas Rhett, Lauren Akins and Glennon Doyle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5J3VsybFRyALjWgPUYqbH7?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Reba and Melissa tackle parenthood through a frank discussion about their own experiences with motherhood and raising children, what they did well and what they wish they had done differently. Author Glennon Doyle joins them to discuss her “untamed” approach to motherhood, and they also have a beautiful conversation with singer Thomas Rhett and his wife Lauren Akins about their experiences raising a blended family. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5J3VsybFRyALjWgPUYqbH7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2993</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faith with Lauren Daigle and Annie F. Downs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5KA3ZVCw29Stme8tHjOMRY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Reba and Melissa examine the importance of faith in their lives, and the different ways faith can be expressed and lived. They discuss the nuances of religion vs. faith with podcaster, speaker, and author Annie F. Downs, and have a meaningful conversation about faith as a cornerstone of art and life with singer and songwriter Lauren Daigle.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5KA3ZVCw29Stme8tHjOMRY</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2666</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wellness/Self-Care with Chrissy Metz and Tabitha Brown</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7fn7M0kOF7G070nLoU5ypo?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Reba and Melissa consider the importance of wellness and self-care and its implications on happiness and good mental health. Vegan food influencer Tabitha Brown delivers her top five wellness tips and the ladies discuss self-care strategies with actress and singer Chrissy Metz. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7fn7M0kOF7G070nLoU5ypo</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2738</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dating with Kristin Chenoweth and Mandy Len Catron</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2jVeKacbz6rFEgnISxQsph?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Reba and Melissa get into the ins and outs of dating and relationships in the modern age. They learn a ton from expert guest, Mandy Len Catron, author of the article “36 Questions That Lead To Love,” and swap dating stories with their buddy Kristin Chenoweth. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2jVeKacbz6rFEgnISxQsph</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2317</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aging with Jane Fonda</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5v9X3x2XWEoQ9CIVPxyK8N?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Reba and Melissa discuss aging and how they approach getting older with grace and joy. Special guest Jane Fonda joins for a fascinating conversation about wellness, work, activism, motherhood, what it means to thrive at any age. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5v9X3x2XWEoQ9CIVPxyK8N</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2336</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forging Your Own Path with Dolly Parton</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0UoDFAZCnO8cIhXIXtSeoD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Reba and Melissa tackle the ever important topic of how to forge your own path, both in your career and in your life, and who better to set an example and share her wisdom on the subject then the inimitable singer, songwriter, author, actress, and businesswoman Dolly Parton.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0UoDFAZCnO8cIhXIXtSeoD</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1971</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friendship with Lauren Alaina and Leslie Jordan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7Ki4aMaF1DR1O4i0vaG5ES?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Reba and Melissa take on the topic of Friendship - why it’s still important even in adulthood, how to maintain friendships in a busy world, and how to approach making new friends later in life. Guests include old pal Leslie Jordan and newer friend Lauren Alaina.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7Ki4aMaF1DR1O4i0vaG5ES</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2721</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living &amp; Learning with Reba McEntire Trailer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3iyc2SXcyONSDotsH7IUtJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>You don't know what you don't know. Reba McEntire and Melissa Peterman reunite in a brand new podcast. Follow here for new episodes every Monday, only on Spotify. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3iyc2SXcyONSDotsH7IUtJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>119</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

