<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Not Past It </title>
    <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/2IDH4p3mEBPgVHbq4HQVA2</link>
    <description>Ever wonder why the world is the way it is? Like, 1000s of years of humanity and this is the version of the world we came up with. This one? Same. Each Wednesday on Not Past It host Simone Polanen will pick a moment from that very same week in history -- and tell you how it shaped our lives today.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8ab8b5a9c419b5cd6b847a5fb5</url>
      <title>Not Past It </title>
      <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/2IDH4p3mEBPgVHbq4HQVA2</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:30:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The "Crying Indian" Ad </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6Qe37WTHCNB9FngNsJbImA?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On Earth Day, April 22nd 1971 -- 51 years ago this week -- a commercial debuted starring a crying American Indian. The image stuck in the country’s consciousness. But there were surprising forces behind the ad. In this episode, we dig into the powerful players who helped shape how we think about environmental action. Join us in talking trash and trash talking. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6Qe37WTHCNB9FngNsJbImA</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1614</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Secret Abortion Conference</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1I2MohcvBb5ldEqpG8XfNV?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In 1955, Dr. Mary Calderone assembled a group of 43 medical minds in a private location in upstate New York. This event would be one of the first abortion conferences in America - sponsored by Planned Parenthood. The discussions, and a book that came out of it, was one of the first steps on the path to Roe v. Wade. Not Past It takes you inside the conference walls. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1I2MohcvBb5ldEqpG8XfNV</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1960</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The LSD No-No </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6V8n8op2yKca0OaIq4EQ85?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The Ambies- Awards for Audio Excellence, thought the sound design on this episode was so good it was nominated for an award. So, we're bring it back so you can listen or re-listen to the story of Pittsburgh Pirates pitcher Dock Ellis. He played the best game of his career while tripping on acid. On June 12, 1970: Ellis pitched a no-hitter. Simone tells the story of his trip and what it can teach us about psychedelic drugs and performance anxiety. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6V8n8op2yKca0OaIq4EQ85</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1729</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How The Joker Came To Be</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7frFNdtYXo5qiTyeG2h6QY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Zap! Boom! Pow! This April fool’s week, comic book writer Evan Narcisse joins us for a history domino adventure. We trace how one hilarious 17th century scientific discovery shoots its way through gun history, card games and lands on the birth of an iconic and villainous comic book funnyman. And watch out! Along the way you might get kapow’d! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7frFNdtYXo5qiTyeG2h6QY</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1767</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirates of the Metric System</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2rS8j1iPvfxyXIiysAzE4S?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Looking to blame someone for America’s metric system woes? Well! Look no further than Joseph Dombey, whose sole mission was to bring the meter and the kilogram to Thomas Jefferson 228 years ago. Unfortunately, on March 21, 1794, this unlucky Frenchman was caught by pirates. The first of many ill-fated events that led to our confusing and silly Imperial system of measurements. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2rS8j1iPvfxyXIiysAzE4S</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1679</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A UFO in the Southwestern Sky</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/45rq9eCwXRuaPb4z6a4KJK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On a spring night in the late 90s, folks in Arizona looked up at the night sky and saw … something. Something they couldn’t understand. On March 13, 1997, many people witnessed one of the most famous mass UFO sightings in American history, The Phoenix Lights. Not Past It takes a look back at that night and tries to understand where the government stands on UFOs today. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45rq9eCwXRuaPb4z6a4KJK</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1706</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Notorious Life After Death </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4U7IKuHeF7RfhGH2Z9Loo1?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The Notorious B.I.G. was at the top of his game when he was murdered, 25 years ago this week. On March 9th, 1997, Christopher Wallace was gunned down in public. We’re telling the story of Biggie’s friendship with Tupac. Just not the one you may have heard.Check out our Notorious B.I.G. and Tupac playlist to hear songs from the episode and other fan favorites.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4U7IKuHeF7RfhGH2Z9Loo1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1862</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 300 Years of the American Tween</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/68819CKtMN6p9LxvipG7cV?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In our very first LIVE show, we’re exploring the wide-ranging influence of America’s coolest demographic: tween girls. Simone and our guest, BA Parker, are taking a historical domino journey that starts in Salem, MA, where, on February 29, 1692, the very first arrests were made in the Salem Witch Trials. But we’re not stopping there. We’ll examine 300+ years of history and take a good hard look at the way US history is made (and re-made) along the way. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68819CKtMN6p9LxvipG7cV</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2179</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Korea’s Olympic Dream</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0IwXV4N55HFAB0HIEWfWb4?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Before Squid Game, BTS, and Parasite, South Korea dazzled the world in a different field… figure skating. All thanks to their queen of the ice, Yuna Kim. On February 25, 2010 she set a new world record at the Winter Olympics. But Yuna’s path to the Olympics was bigger than her — and charts the history of a nation emerging into a new chapter. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0IwXV4N55HFAB0HIEWfWb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1584</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Nazi Hunter </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4L9VxAZ5U2IQ0xtYq96ysY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Simon Wiesenthal walked out of the Mauthausen concentration camp a survivor determined to hold war criminals accountable. When it was discovered that one of the Holocaust’s primary architects was in hiding, Simon was on the case. His 15 year globe-spanning hunt ended in 1960 with some secret spy photography that would make Simon a legend. His story would inspire those seeking justice to this day. Even if Simon’s hunt wasn’t entirely truthful.*A warning for our listeners: this story contains graphic descriptions of violence. please take care while you listen. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4L9VxAZ5U2IQ0xtYq96ysY</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1842</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Found Love In A Historical Place</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6vR8wb04xufrg6oTwMDW65?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Roses are red, violets are blue…love stories from throughout history, our gift to you. February 14th, Valentine’s Day, marks a moment that we set aside to share our appreciation for one another. This week we’ve got stories about a young poet, bromance, and love that is out of this world. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6vR8wb04xufrg6oTwMDW65</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1628</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balto Wasn’t The (Only) Hero</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5X8fK4IeTWPiOit2Co3HIi?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In the winter of 1925, the terrible suspicions of the only doctor in Nome -- a small, isolated town in northwest Alaska -- came true. A highly contagious and deadly disease called diphtheria was spreading, and he sent word asking for a delivery of the medicine to cure it. On February 2, 1925, Nome received its first delivery of antitoxin, transported by some heroic couriers: dogs! Sled dogs, braving the treacherous elements of a freezing Alaskan winter. But just one of those dogs would become legend. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5X8fK4IeTWPiOit2Co3HIi</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1667</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Queen of Hawaii </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0TrF79HO2KtLX4R4zrK0lj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Before Hawaii became the 50th state of the United States of America, it was ruled by a monarchy. On January 29, 1891, Lili’uokalani was crowned Queen of Hawaii. She would be faced with the greed and violence of White sugar plantation owners that had been building under her brother, King Kalakaua. She was the first queen of the island nation and would be the last. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0TrF79HO2KtLX4R4zrK0lj</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1727</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Sheriff in Town</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6cuDquBQi7dR9Y6doClMY5?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In the 1960s Alabama was at the forefront of the Civil Rights Movement. It’s the home of the years-long Montgomery Bus Boycotts and demonstrations in Selma for Black people to gain equal voting rights. But in Tuskegee, on January 16th, 1967 – history was made when Lucius Amerson was sworn in as Sheriff of Macon County, Alabama. He was the first Black documented sheriff in the South since Reconstruction. Amerson gained unprecedented power for a Black man in the South...and many people wanted to take that power away from him. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6cuDquBQi7dR9Y6doClMY5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1868</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sweet, but Deadly, Disaster</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/14wTf23h0I9AxP561YSiPY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On January 15, 1919, a tank exploded in Boston’s North End releasing a tsunami wave of molasses that plowed down the city’s streets at 35 miles per hour. It destroyed businesses and homes. Lives were lost. And in the wake of this sticky disaster, people were suspicious… What caused the tank to blow? Who was to blame? There were rumors of foul play. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14wTf23h0I9AxP561YSiPY</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1304</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Kings of Drag</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6cIeBXO1bdnwbpdReydRG8?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Drag Kings. Gender Bending. Punk Rock. In the 1990s, that’s what Club Casanova was all about. Back then, New York City nightlife was poppin’. But so was crime. Both of which then Mayor Rudy Giuliani was hellbent on cleaning up. Luckily for him, a racist Prohibition-era law helped eradicate crime...and fun. And a few days before New Years 1998, Club Casanova was Rudy’s latest victim. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6cIeBXO1bdnwbpdReydRG8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1720</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zsa Zsa Gabor, Guilty As Charged </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4c5ZQsRwS3D7KKfp9lWttu?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week we are bringing a you dazzling NPI episode from earlier this year. Zsa Zsa Gabor was the epitome of Hollywood glam, starring in dozens of films and tv shows in the 1940s and 50s. But by the 1980s, her shine began to dim. On September 14 1989, Gabor made a celebrity comeback when she was prosecuted for slapping a Beverly Hills cop. In court Gabor played the role she was born to play… herself. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c5ZQsRwS3D7KKfp9lWttu</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1651</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Beanie Baby Craze</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2bZNH9oA8aKiKncaSEWpGd?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week we’re hitting repeat on one of our favorite episodes: In the 90s, everybody had to have a Beanie Baby. Not just kids. They were one of the biggest get-rich-quick schemes of the decade. On August 31, 1999, the company, Ty Inc., released a cryptic message that they would retire the wildly popular toys. Instead of fueling a massive frenzy — it revealed the beanie baby bubble was destined to burst. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2bZNH9oA8aKiKncaSEWpGd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1632</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World’s Most Famous Virgins</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1Uav5Hfq6Fz02msK8Xo2Cs?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Christmas is upon us. And, that means one thing at Not Past It: diving into the dark, twisted history of S E X. This week, Simone is taking our guest Eric Mennel on a domino history ride that starts with a bishop’s declaration of original sin and ends with the outward sexual displays of America’s beloved celebrities. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1Uav5Hfq6Fz02msK8Xo2Cs</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2062</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Are My Background Singers?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6oOUVWzQtnMpwGxr1b5gtx?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On December 5, 1996, Patti LaBelle performed at the National Tree Lighting Ceremony, and so much went wrong: her cue cards were out of order, the backup singers were missing, and it was on national TV. The moment has since become an annual Christmas-time viral sensation. But 25 years later, the question remains: how did everything go so far off the rails? Now, finally, we have the answer. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6oOUVWzQtnMpwGxr1b5gtx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2301</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Invent A Holiday</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0GrFC9lXMG7e6z9B6RVxPN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>To usher in the holiday season, we’re offering up four historical events that we think should be celebrated on the first day of the last month of every year. These history holidays require no religion, gift-giving, or even cooking...just an appreciation for how the past shapes our lives. Come create a new tradition with us. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0GrFC9lXMG7e6z9B6RVxPN</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1409</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sabotaging Thanksgiving</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2wap9x96thbG0qi217oQzC?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Wamsutta Frank James, a member of the Wampanoag Tribe, led his fellow activists in protest of a Thanksgiving Celebration in Plymouth, MA. On November 26, 1970, he set the record straight as to the true and violent history of this holiday. The Pilgrim celebration went to shit and the first National Day of Mourning was born. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2wap9x96thbG0qi217oQzC</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1552</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Not Past It</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6XNbwZrr4i2BL36m9yIJI8?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>History reveals something about the present. Every Wednesday, host Simone Polanen picks a moment from that week in history to explore how it shapes our world today. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6XNbwZrr4i2BL36m9yIJI8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>119</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder in Ogoniland</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6JYntiaBHlyxfAwn0oRc9G?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>After four decades of devastating oil pollution in the Niger Delta, Ken Saro-Wiwa decided he couldn’t stand the injustices any longer. The Nigerian writer-turned-activist started campaigning to defend the rights of his people, the Ogoni, from the oil drilling that was destroying their land and way of life. But Ken paid a price. In this episode, actor Gbenga Akinnagbe (The Deuce, The Wire), brings Saro-Wiwa’s work to life. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6JYntiaBHlyxfAwn0oRc9G</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1893</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ma Barker’s True Crime</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/59NC5W9LdjfBmSPtr3CUTA?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, we brush off an NPI true crime favorite. Ever heard of lady crime boss, Ma Barker? On July 26, 1932, her alleged gang of thieves stole over $200,000 from a Kansas bank without firing a single shot. The Barker-Karpis gang stole millions before Ma was killed in a shootout with the FBI. But was she a criminal mastermind or just a scapegoat? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59NC5W9LdjfBmSPtr3CUTA</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1628</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King Tut Died for Tourism</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6gXAht20E5UrOFoTYu6JHM?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>King Tutankhamen, Egypt’s boy prince was laid to rest in a fantastical chamber of secrets. On November 4, 1922, the entrance to King Tut’s tomb was discovered 33 centuries after he was buried. But when the king’s tomb was disturbed strange things began to happen. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6gXAht20E5UrOFoTYu6JHM</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1715</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houdini: The OG Ghostbuster</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4tPWj2aGyn5jkKnBfEdd4d?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Harry Houdini escaped from handcuffs, sea monsters and torture cells, but his last great illusion defied even the spirits. On October 31, 1936, the famous escape artist was set to come back from the dead. But, as spooky as that sounds, the backstory to uncover America’s most notorious frauds of the day, is even more devilish. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4tPWj2aGyn5jkKnBfEdd4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2281</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s Haunting The Lake ?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1SUhu5B3KNjixFNUnaXQGt?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Roughly 40 miles northeast of Atlanta, in Forsyth County, lies Lake Lanier. It’s a place where people go to relax, fish or party - and legend has it, it's haunted. But not in the way it’s been talked about. We’re revealing the true haunting of Lake Lanier, where a horrific story of racial violence and terror is hidden under a veneer of suburban bliss. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1SUhu5B3KNjixFNUnaXQGt</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2235</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hooked on Black Horror</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3Um3POnl8U9xGVmNuTlyok?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Candyman, Candyman, Candyman… Do you dare say it five times? On October 16, 1992, Candyman was released in theaters introducing the world to the ghost-like ghoul with a hook for a hand. But this horror cult classic is different--it features a Black man as the haunting character with a backstory of racial trauma. We explore the legacy of the film and why it has such staying power, despite its flaws. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3Um3POnl8U9xGVmNuTlyok</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2006</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> The Witch of Delray</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0xi7lbcz32zSYxQk521SLA?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Depression-era Detroit is known for many things: baseball, bootlegging, and the booming auto industry. But what about a witch? On October 5, 1931, a Wayne County jury reached a verdict in the trial of an immigrant woman accused of murder and of being...The Witch of Delray. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0xi7lbcz32zSYxQk521SLA</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2016</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How The Green M&amp;M Got Sexy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/07DStmh2JlD8DqcPkdbSC9?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The backstory of the M&amp;M can be traced to the Spanish American War. On October 1, 1898, a coalition of diplomats met in Paris to negotiate a peace treaty between the U.S. and Spain, leading to a sugar rush across America’s new colonial territories. And eventually… domino-ing us into the modern day sex icon that is the green M&amp;M. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07DStmh2JlD8DqcPkdbSC9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2124</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>💩🌠The Birth of Emojis 😂🤰🏾</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3qEZoI2O6G5TKXabRxjsav?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Smiling poop. Zombie lady. High-fiving squid. Emojis cover a huge spectrum of human expression. But did you ever wonder where they came from? On September 19, 1982, a computer scientist, concerned his jokes weren’t landing in a university chatroom, used the first emoticon; colon, minus sign, parenthesis. The simple smiley face set the stage for a revolution in online communication. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3qEZoI2O6G5TKXabRxjsav</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1654</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zsa Zsa Slaps a Cop</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5BCcifTPNz1f4MI01HABGs?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Zsa Zsa Gabor was the epitome of Hollywood glam, starring in dozens of films and tv shows in the 1940s and 50s. But by the 1980s, her shine began to dim. On September 14 1989, Gabor made a celebrity comeback when she was prosecuted for slapping a Beverly Hills cop. In court Gabor played the role she was born to play… herself. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5BCcifTPNz1f4MI01HABGs</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1584</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9/11 Makes Me Uncomfortable</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3piWwuPTE4ruOdWJi6TzGI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>American flags, camouflage ribbons and “Never Forget” statements, prevailed as symbols of patriotism in the early 2000s. On September 11, 2001, four coordinated terrorist attacks took place in the U.S. and had catastrophic ripple effects across the globe. Simone explores her personal feelings about 9/11 and the “Never Forget” narrative. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3piWwuPTE4ruOdWJi6TzGI</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1729</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Beanie Babies Are Worthless</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7a8leoyNqgf0BAUxdECDLf?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In the 90s, everybody had to have a Beanie Baby. Not just kids. They were one of the biggest get-rich-quick schemes of the decade. On August 31, 1999, the company, Ty Inc., released a cryptic message that they would retire the wildly popular toys. Instead of fueling a massive frenzy — it revealed the beanie baby bubble was destined to burst. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a8leoyNqgf0BAUxdECDLf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1585</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Enron Whistleblower</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1FYTocWIODDPXA37rhj5gS?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Enron, the Houston-based energy giant, was one of the biggest, most well-respected companies in the 90s. But in 2001, it went from top of the heap to bottom of the barrel, real quick. On August 22, 2001, Sherron Watkins met with the company’s CEO to warn him about the accounting scandal pushing the company to the brink of collapse. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1FYTocWIODDPXA37rhj5gS</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1921</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woodstock 69: A Peaceful Disaster</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7KuB5NieOh40fUh2tOuFOC?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Woodstock is the most iconic music festival in American history, remembered for peace and love. On August 18, 1969 it earned that reputation after being declared an official disaster zone without all the deadly side effects. It even converted its host, dairy farmer Max Yasgur, into an unlikely apostle on the way. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7KuB5NieOh40fUh2tOuFOC</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1684</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Billboard Chart Topper from Crime Show</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1o7G5gsZg8SOVEL5AcznfJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Martha Wash was flipping through TV channels when, to her complete surprise, she happened upon a familiar voice: her own – coming out of the mouth of someone else. Problem was: stealing her voice wasn’t a crime. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1o7G5gsZg8SOVEL5AcznfJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2197</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Olympic GOAT Gets Snubbed </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3LFMnUjaoQ4FmR8zuIQSlb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jesse Owens swept the track and field events at the Olympics in Berlin. On August 3, 1936, Owens won his first of four gold medals in the 100 meter dash cementing his name in history. The Black track star was celebrated as a hero -- but the celebration was short lived. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3LFMnUjaoQ4FmR8zuIQSlb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1880</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Notorious Ma Barker</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3lARVIo0zdyjFhmTuvK3ez?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Ever heard of lady crime boss, Ma Barker? On July 26, 1932, her alleged gang of thieves stole over $200,000 from a Kansas bank without firing a single shot. The Barker-Karpis gang stole millions before Ma was killed in a shootout with the FBI. But was she a criminal mastermind or just a scapegoat? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3lARVIo0zdyjFhmTuvK3ez</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1592</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitch, I’m an Astrophysicist </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2m9Mul0Jeuhwx9Ax251J4t?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Sally Ride was the first woman to rocket off into space for NASA. On July 23, 2012, she died and left behind a legacy for women and girls in STEM. We dig into the limits of being labeled “first” and learn about the woman inside the space suit. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2m9Mul0Jeuhwx9Ax251J4t</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2144</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Town Secession</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2fez4pP7BoPbtvDaEsbj82?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Fed up with not receiving funding to fix their crumbling water infrastructure, the residents of a small town in Minnesota took matters into their own hands. On July 13th, 1977, the town of Kinney voted to secede from the U.S. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2fez4pP7BoPbtvDaEsbj82</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1683</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United States of Illuminati</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4dvB50Pdq1R9p8J632kGYY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Think you know the Illuminati? Well, it's more than a rumored celebrity cult. And on July 4, 1798, the speech "The Duty of Americans at the Present Crisis," was delivered to warn of the group's threat to American democracy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4dvB50Pdq1R9p8J632kGYY</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1487</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rated PG-13 for Sex and Violence </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2jm4Ob5mJm5iLvUD6Dxdhg?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Did you know that backlash from Indiana Jones and Gremlins led to the PG-13 rating? On July 1, 1984, the MPAA announced the rating that changed film forever. This week Simone reviews the rating system and it's hidden Puritan agenda. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2jm4Ob5mJm5iLvUD6Dxdhg</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1580</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nazi Battle to Pop Musical?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5UjS3weO4BR5wcIpitlh9H?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>How a Nazi Battle on June 22, 1941, led to the one of the biggest movie musicals of all time. Can you guess how we get there? This week Simone connects the dots.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5UjS3weO4BR5wcIpitlh9H</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1730</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Paris Hilton Sex Tape</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/32iPDgapksonc6GNuigeWY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Paris Hilton’s sex tape ushered in a new era of celebrity obsession. On June 15, 2004: it went on sale after her ex made a deal with a pornographic distributor. Simone reflects on the scandal, fallout and impact it had on a generation of young women. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32iPDgapksonc6GNuigeWY</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1316</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The LSD No-Hitter </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1E5Y9HUnjgUDs7ubJCfUlm?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Pittsburgh Pirates pitcher Dock Ellis, played the best game of his career while tripping on acid. On June 12, 1970:Ellis pitched a no-hitter. Simone tells the story of his trip and what it can teach us about psychedelic drugs and performance anxiety. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1E5Y9HUnjgUDs7ubJCfUlm</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1664</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Vax That Got Axed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3CTUQt5mXzgM4qm7PsOjbc?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Did you know there was almost an AIDS vaccine? On June 3, 1998: AIDSVAX VAX004 reached the final stage of trials before widespread approval. Simone gets the facts on the vax and why it never made it to the masses. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3CTUQt5mXzgM4qm7PsOjbc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1747</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Race for a Better Breakfast</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4FpICVDtX77ASx3RdHR4ah?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>How are cornflakes and eugenics connected? On May 31, 1895: the Kellogg brothers filed the patent for what would eventually become Corn Flakes. Simone digs in to the cereal’s bizarre, dark origins and examines its lasting impact on the wellness industry today. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4FpICVDtX77ASx3RdHR4ah</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1553</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

