<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Off the Record with DJ Akademiks</title>
    <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/0u8NBMvWajLvc66r9NsJJs</link>
    <description>Off the Record with DJ Akademiks is a show about music, entertainment, and culture. After spending years reporting on the latest trends in music, Akademiks has cemented his voice in the conversation. Now with Spotify he plans to take his coverage of hip hop to the next level. Beginning September 20th, Off the Record will release three episodes each week featuring roundtable discussions and a special interview with music’s hottest artists and personalities.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8a78acdd6523bc3123ee1acff1</url>
      <title>Off the Record with DJ Akademiks</title>
      <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/0u8NBMvWajLvc66r9NsJJs</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:15:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 082: Free Agent (feat. Antonio Brown)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1ZmNUBgQdj5tADTaMxRm03?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On the day Antonio Brown drops his project, 'Paradigm', he sat with DJ Akademiks to talk about everything life and music. Akademiks got a chance to pull up to his crib where Antonio did some meditation with him gave him a house tour, played basketball with him  and oh of-course played him some music. AB discusses him walking off the field as a member of the Tampa Bay Bucaneers and answers if he regrets doing that. He then talks about the next step for him in his life and also the media portayal of him. He talks about meeting some dope people including Kanye West and Young Thug and how they helped him in music. He also talks about being the president of Donda Sports and what that entails. We then get into his project and his motivation behind it and why he thinks there is a paradigm shift happening right now. At last, AB seems to be at peace with himself going into this project and also where his life is, we do a happiness check on him to see how he/s feeling and he lets us know he's never been better.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ZmNUBgQdj5tADTaMxRm03</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4238</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 081: 6ix9ine Returns (featuring 6ix9ine, Wack 100 &amp; Hassan Campbell)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/74KGq9Hofh9ShLTqJiP8VP?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>6ix9ine returns to Off The Record with a familiar face, Wack 100. This time we add one more to the table, Hassan Campbell. 6ix9ine explains his hiatus and also showcases his new crew and new label. He's still touting the 'I'm Outside and Untouched' slogan that we've heard before but with new confidence as he pulls up with a new song called 'GINÉ'. This is promised to be one of the most chaotic podcasts you've ever watched.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74KGq9Hofh9ShLTqJiP8VP</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>8772</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 080: YNW Melly is COMING HOME! (feat. DrewFilmedit)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6hhTxMThRg5u2WqdCTBSSV?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We got one of the most popular videographer in hip hop as our guest today. Drewfilmedit, most notorious for filming the majority of YNW Melly videos. He has a ton of stories involving hip hop after being in the most interesting predicaments while filming music videos for artists. He talks about meeting Melly, blowing up while in high school and also explains how his father was supportive of his entire journey.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6hhTxMThRg5u2WqdCTBSSV</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4474</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 079: Waka Flocka Flame (Spotify Live)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5M5U7ZXUH1T6WjFGVnAEaY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Waka Flocka is our guest today on Spotify Live. He also pulled up to our studio so we have a video component of today's conversation. Waka Flocka gets into his growth and evolution as a person and recaps his career as a rapper.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5M5U7ZXUH1T6WjFGVnAEaY</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7173</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 078: Poker Face: Double Down or Fold? (feat. Myron Gaines &amp; Lil Boom)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0vLPWmn6dsY02ikLiu7PO7?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We begin by talking about our favorite topic yet again, mainstream acceptance of certain opinions and also how those that express those opinions that are unfavorable get treated. We then delve into the Taxstone and Troy Ave incident that has yet to reach a jury trial and where Troy Ave's bodyguard died in the incident. We then talk about YNW Melly case updates.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0vLPWmn6dsY02ikLiu7PO7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>11392</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 077: Censorship</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1SUP3z3TYR9u3VN3v4NbHM?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Akademiks is here recording a podcast right before catching a flight to Miami! He talks about the censorship machine is coming for him lately and also updates us on whats going on with his Instagram. He then talks about the Grammys, Meg thee Stallion and Tory Lanez and also a ridiculous event that went down in DC with a corpse being brought in the club for a homegoing concert.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1SUP3z3TYR9u3VN3v4NbHM</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2955</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 076: 'I Knew 6ix9ine Would Rat. GS9 would Never!' (feat. Rowdy Rebel)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3TTioIkqFRYKRktqNZdh5k?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rowdy Rebel is our guest for today. After serving 7 years in a state prison along with his GS9 codefendants including Bobby Shmurda, Rowdy is back free and dropping music. He's slated to drop a new project and is back on the scene recapping his time prior to being locked up and detailing how he survived being locked up for 7 years. Akademiks and Rowdy go back and forth about stories of how Rowdy survived jail and also how he learned a few helpful traits while being locked up like humbleness and patience. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3TTioIkqFRYKRktqNZdh5k</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5829</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 075: Money Can't buy Happiness (feat. Celina Powell)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7MLQ3zoFGNM2rYsYCNBxGb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Celina Powell is our guest for today's episode. She's been a notorious figure in hip hop over the years with her initial claim to fame being linked with many of the hottest rappers of our time. She has experienced and seen many hip hop moments from behind the scenes and has been sort of a notorious figure in hip hop as her name rising in popularity became the new replacement for Video Vixens / Hip Hop Groupies . Today she sits with Akademiks after their interesting connection over the years and talk about how this podcast happened from the get go to recapping her past actions and ponder over the questions of what the ramifications to her action were. She also talks about trying to find happiness after becoming a millionaire through OnlyFans. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7MLQ3zoFGNM2rYsYCNBxGb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5235</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 074: [Rubi Rose] Live</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6CDBj2G8jA8ji7DMtWnHAj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rubi Rose talks with Akademiks, Previously Recorded LIVE, about her rise to fame in the rap game. From being a rappers girlfriend to detailing her very first time making a song. She talks about making the XXL Freshman list, being on songs with PartyNextDoor and Future and even how her first big single 'Big Mouth' blew up and got her signed. She talks about how she keeps it diverse and defends having a Onlyfans which she posts more provocative content. She talks about what she learned from her ex boyfriend, DDG and also her future plans of working with Lil Tjay and also dropping a project this year. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6CDBj2G8jA8ji7DMtWnHAj</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2984</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 073: The Real Reason Will Smith SLAPPED Chris Rock</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1IKnc8x2ifSIf52TE6rpPS?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today we're talking about the Slap heard around the world. Chris Rock was assaulted by Will Smith at the Oscars after he dropped a joke about Jada Pinkett Smith. Will Smith has since apologized but admitted he was triggered by the joke that mentioned Jada's hair and she's had her bouts with a condition called alopecia. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1IKnc8x2ifSIf52TE6rpPS</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3286</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 072: Conversational Therapy (feat. Pink Sweats)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3Rqn9BmnlzmKSvRRXB3DQj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Pink Sweats is our guest today. He hails from Philly with a unique style in every way from clothing to music. Known for his writing and vocal talents he joins us to showcase a different side of himself that many wouldn't know about. In this 3 hour 30 min convo, topics range from his time in the church, to growing up with his father as his hero to thoughts on marriage, Mt Rushmore of R&amp;B and even politics.  Comment under our last instagram picture (@offtherecordclips) if you made it to the end. you should know the key word!</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3Rqn9BmnlzmKSvRRXB3DQj</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>12707</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 071: 'I'd Do A Song with NBA Youngboy' (feat. Fredo Bang)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2t04ll8YwYPxBsGdjsg6Jh?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Fredo Bang is our guest for todays episode. He's from Louisiana and discussed in detail how he got into rap music and how his career got constantly derailed by being sent back and forth to jail. He speaks on Gee Money and his impact on his career and how his death affected him. We then discuss whether or not he was dissing his cousin Boosie on his latest track. We also talk about his relationship with NBA Youngboy and if he would do a song with him. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2t04ll8YwYPxBsGdjsg6Jh</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6277</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 070: My Dawg 6ix9ine Down Bad... He BROKE??</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7LUMut3yt86Z0W3okUggfc?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On todays episode, Akademiks recaps his time going to watch Batman at a dine in theater and also speaks on Tyler the Creator selling out MSG. He talks about news these days is contextualized to support the  narrative that is being pushed or presented. He talks about 6ix9ine allegedly being down bad and broke asf and gives the full details behind it. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7LUMut3yt86Z0W3okUggfc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3795</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 069: Call Me Big Latto? (feat. Latto)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7khQuWfJ1ir43oBmxB0ZZr?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Latto is our guest today. Latto speaks on changing to her from Mulatto to Latto. We talk about her come up in the streets of Atlanta growing up around her father who was in the streets and also developing a passion for rap. She talks about getting on 'The Rap Game' and winning then getting her big break and recognition with freestyles. She talks about being on the XXL Freshman list. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7khQuWfJ1ir43oBmxB0ZZr</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4690</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 068: How I Dropped Out of College and Became The Biggest Twitch Streamer (feat. Kaicenat)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1APaOso1WSTYjGeGDO2M8L?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Kaicenat is our guest today. He's one of the most popular Twitch streamers today who grew up in Bronx, New York. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1APaOso1WSTYjGeGDO2M8L</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>8207</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 067: Lil Durk and YB Beef Have Sucked The Air out the Music Industry!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6KAZVuky7Bi56fUBA7r6l7?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today we talk about how Lil Durk and NBA Youngboy issues have completely turned the industry into being the Durk/YB show. We analyze how Beefing has its effects of isolating the attention of fans to be on only a select few artists. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6KAZVuky7Bi56fUBA7r6l7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3867</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 066: [Flo Milli] Live</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/78l3Hg6uT51SeSbzgYxUod?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In case you missed it, this episode was previously recorded LIVE. Our featured guest was Flo Milli, an artist from Mobile, Alabama. After being nominated in 2020 for Best New artist and also making the XXL Freshman list in the same year, Flo Milli has been on the fast track to being one of the biggest female rappers in the game. She joins us to talk about her come up and where her career is right now. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78l3Hg6uT51SeSbzgYxUod</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4006</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 065: Why We Told Kanye West "NO" after he asked to Get on A YNW Melly Song (King Von Manager aka 100k Track)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6Lr7q5zZ324vIwnjrOntGx?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today guest is 100k Track, who is most notable for being the manager of King Von at the time of his passing and also YNW Melly. He speaks on his come up and linking with Kodak Black and Sniper gang. He speaks about his experience being a rapper to then transitioning to manager. He talks about meeting with YNW Melly while he was in Jail and then having a crazy run with him once he got out of jail 8 months later. He talks about how he met King Von and how he got Lil Durk approval to manage him. He gives a story of how they told Kanye West 'NO' to him askin to getting on a song. He describes the process of working with Kanye and even the early stages of being in the studio with Kanye while he was cooking up Donda in Calabasas. He talks about how he saved Jackboy in a situation where cops would have arrested him.  </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6Lr7q5zZ324vIwnjrOntGx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6121</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 064: Crypto, NFTs and Rappers (feat. Coffeezilla)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4VUIpWlayFxfjDzpDO4Z8l?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Our guest today is none other than a very popular youtuber that goes by the name Coffeezilla. He joins us to talk about Cryptocurrency, NFTs and Influencers (rappers especially) involvement with what has been highly controversial 'pump and dumps. Coffeezilla starts out by telling us how he got into the space where he exposed people doin scummy thing in the Crypto / NFT space. He also breaks down what a NFT is and also speaks on how money is siphoned from fans to influencers and who really owns the majority of NFTs. He issues a warning to rappers who take advantage of their fan loyalty by promoting these rug pulls and explains the difference between a legit NFT project and a rug pull.  </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4VUIpWlayFxfjDzpDO4Z8l</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4022</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 063: "Kay Flock is the Face Of Bronx Drill, but I'm #1" (feat. B-Lovee)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2c80JGEODRCybolpaxqC6v?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>B-Lovee is our guest for this episode. He talks about his rise to fame and navigating the streets of the Bronx. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c80JGEODRCybolpaxqC6v</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5655</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 062 - 'I Had Kanye West Doing Drill Music' (feat. Fivio Foreign)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3OO3hZU6Oc8fXLGcboCPii?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today's guest is NYC very own Fivio Foreign. Recently he's been in the media for not only music as he's being seen recently collaborating  with Kanye West on his latest single 'City of Gods' which also features Alicia Keys. Kanye has taken a likening to Fivio Foreign and even agreed to executive produce his album tentatively titled 'Bible'. Fivio speaks about his relationship with Kanye West and even touches on some issues domestically in NYC as the mayor of New York, Eric Adams, recently took aim at drill music and even threatened to ban it from social media. Fivio Foreign recaps the meeting with the mayor and also talks about the influence of Pop Smoke and answers the question if he still considers himself a Drill Rapper current or not. He gives his list of the current faces of New York in terms of artists and speaks on Kay Flock situation. Fivio also recaps the experience recording 'Donda' and exposes Kanye West recording process / workflow.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3OO3hZU6Oc8fXLGcboCPii</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3170</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 061: The Real Information behind Misinformation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7oc2bGXkeSQ0p19SIxxXDK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today's Episode, Akademiks breaks down the real behind social media and programming. We get into how social media platforms control what you get to see and when and Akademiks uses a personal example. Akademiks also talks about how Kanye West right now is changing the game with putting his music on a STEM player which is unheard of and how he turned down a $100 million contract for a Apple Music streaming deal.  Song of the Week: Kay Flock - PSA</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7oc2bGXkeSQ0p19SIxxXDK</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3243</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 060: Kodak Black is WYLING!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/54hAFCyyQT0XlEIUTszPOq?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today's episode we're back in our home studio and we get to recap whats been going on in the last week. We talk about recent Roddy Ricch episode and recap the Superbowl. We talk Jay Z's involvement and if anyone can have a lineage verzuz that can compete with Dr Dre. We talk about Colin Kaepernick and the NFL having the best ratings in years. We then talk about the antics of Kodak Black. We talk about Nicki Minaj's new single with Lil Baby ' We Got a Problem' and talk if there is a NBA comparison for her of Lebron James or Russel Westbrook. We talk about Future's new music and if he's leaning into the social media perception of him of being toxic.  Record of the Week: Future - Worst Day</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54hAFCyyQT0XlEIUTszPOq</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3071</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 059: 'Think Outside The Box' (feat. Roddy Ricch)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5zSgultJwntHQn67Gj3xUm?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Roddy Ricch is our guest today on Off the Record. Roddy summoned Akademiks to the hills of Belair to have this important conversation about his mental state, his career, his recent album and actions on social media. Roddy talks about how he first met Akademiks and how quickly his career took off once a few of his singles took off. He talks having a diamond single 'The Box' and how that changes things and also addresses the theory if he could have dropped music when he wanted or did the label hold him up. He talks about criticism of his release schedule and addresses head on whether he has an inflated ego now or not. He talks about doing features and how the pandemic slowed up his progress after having a huge album and the toll it took on his craft and mental state. Roddy Ricch addresses tweets by Meek Mill that put him in the center of Meek's beef with Atlantic where Meek Mill claimed Roddy Ricch was stolen from him by Atlantic Records and that he didn't benefit off helping to find Roddy Ricch in the initial stages. Roddy explains what his reaction to that statement was and how his relationship has been from the get go with Meek Mill and also the late Nipsey Hussle. Roddy Ricch also addresses going on Clubhouse to confront someone from his hood who had an issue with him. We talk about his future plans of releasing music and how he plans to combat dealing with the internet following false narratives about him and his music. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5zSgultJwntHQn67Gj3xUm</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7365</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 058: Life's' a Finesse (Feat. Bandman Kevo)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1kCNQiQ7QIDR9JY8Txvkvy?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today our guest is Bandman Kevo. He's most known from his days in Chicago where he was busted after running a elaborate 'Card Cracking' ring in 2014. He got out of Prison 3 years later and turned his finessing ways into teaching people how to build credit and teach legal business hacks to people who needed lines of credit etc. He talks about his time in Chicago cracking cards and also the minimum security prison he went to. He also details his new plans now on how not to go back to jail while making millions legally helping out other people become financially literate. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1kCNQiQ7QIDR9JY8Txvkvy</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>8108</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 057: A Redemption Story. (Feat. Hassan Campbell)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/58msnywBfDJYrdKPLImZkI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In one of our most explosive and most likely controversial episodes ever, Hassan Campbell is our guest. Hassan Campbell is a social media personality who has been outspoken in the last few years speaking about the hypocrisy of hip hop culture and those who benefit off it yet push a message that is detrimental to the community which it effects. He talks about growing up in Bronx River and being around the Zulu Nation and Afrika Bambaataa. He talks about growing up in his house and watching his mom in situations and seeing that his father was absent and how it lead him to looking for a father figure in the streets. He later apologizes to the two men he killed and sent his condolences to their mothers and reflected on how Bronx and Brooklyn Drill makes fun of the dead. TRIGGER WARNING!! This episode discusses adult subject matter, including descriptions of sexual abuse of a child, and is intended for adult consumption only. Listener discretion is advised. If you have been affected by sexual violence, free, confidential support is available 24/7 through RAINN's National Sexual Assault Hotline at 800.656-4673 and online.rainn.org</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58msnywBfDJYrdKPLImZkI</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>9640</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 056: Behind the Flagrance (feat. Andrew Schulz)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1LxIbrzZ3ZsY60mvhmVNsH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Andrew Schulz is our guest today. We told you guys we would get him on and he's finally here. He's a accomplished comedian who has a successful podcast, Flagrant 2, and has done TV shows w/ Viacom and also recently Schulz Saves America. We begin by talking about Fresh and Fit appearance on his podcast and Akademiks asks if he intentionally Good Cop/ Bad Cop the duo. We talk about how he prepares to do a standup special and how he separates the material from what he does on the podcast or via other types of content. We also revisit a previous conversation about Lil Baby being hot within the culture of hip hop as opposed how he's viewed by those who aren't in the culture. We talk about how Andrew Schulz increases his audience by widening his demographics and knowing a little about many various groups. We talk about how turning his focus from Brilliant Idiots to having multiple podcasts per week to now building the brand of Flagrant 2. He talks about the impact of Charlamagne Tha god on his career. We talked about Chrissy Teigen and the backlash Akademiks faced while working at Complex. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1LxIbrzZ3ZsY60mvhmVNsH</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>12177</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 055: '' feat. [2 Chainz] Live</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2Tb2VWAgG42k5tfxFi2NOj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This is a archive recording of our live episode of Off the Record podcast w/ 2 Chainz. 2 Chainz talks about his come up and also his iconic mixtape 'TRU Realigion' then subsequently his debut solo album 'Based on a TRU Story'. We recap his career of changing his name from Titty Boi to 2 Chainz. We talk about his collab project with Lil Wayne and also try to establish a Mt. Rushmore for Atlanta in the 2010s. We talk about his new project and why he's only putting out one more Trap Album. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2Tb2VWAgG42k5tfxFi2NOj</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3631</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 054: Who Is Nardo Wick? (feat. Nardo Wick)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5PqPVQP2i2Z9ysuMSuGGYD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Nardo Wick is a rapper from Jacksonville, Florida and is our guest today. He comes in on the heels of  a  controversial clip that went viral from another podcast where he stated his mentality while younger was 'Why Get a Job When I can just rob someone'. He clarifies what he meant in this episode with Akademiks. He talks about watching his mom go to jail, people cook crack around him and also him sleeping on the ground trying to make ends meet. He talks about being in the streets lead him to rapping and then figuring out when he was getting some traction to the moves he made afterwards. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5PqPVQP2i2Z9ysuMSuGGYD</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5134</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 053: 'My Soul Wasn't At Peace Until I Found Meditation' (feat. NLE Choppa)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3yF9wz4zqfUxi02NQpUpZ0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>NLE Choppa is our guest today. He's a rapper from Memphis who gained notoriety after blowing up from his song 'Shotta Flow'. We talk about his new health regimen and also his plant based diet and how he went cold turkey giving up all the vices that distracted him. He talks about attaining the riches, fame and money yet feeling soulless and also about transfer of energy from food. We talk about the run in at the airport with a fan and also issues with NBA Youngboy, his relationship with King Von and Lil Durk.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3yF9wz4zqfUxi02NQpUpZ0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4151</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 052: When I See U (feat. Foolio)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/715Y6YmmbEroSFX9oxDCbh?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Our guest today is a Jacksonville rapper named Foolio. Over the last few years, he's been notorious for his many beefs and feuds within his hometown but within the last year, his viral diss song remixing Fantasia's 'When I See You' has given him additional notoriety and also cemented him as one of the most disrespectful rappers today in hip hop. We talk about some of the trauma in his life coming up while trying to rap. He talks about how he was shot while getting off the bus because he was beefing with someone else who was killed the same day. He talks about his mothers house being shot up and also his reaction when he heard the song 'Who I Smoke' by Yungeen Ace and crew. He details how he began to put together his response song which ultimately was called 'When I See U'.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">715Y6YmmbEroSFX9oxDCbh</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6121</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 051: Brittany Renner meets Fresh and Fit!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4hZlYBCefTcEX0ZT4B3yQI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Todays episode is with Brittany Renner and Fresh and Fit joining us for a group conversation about relationships and dating in the modern world. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4hZlYBCefTcEX0ZT4B3yQI</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6876</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 050: Fresh And Fit Are Officially CANCELLED!!!!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0zsIyOTeNpGa6Mp8aDcZyI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Our Guests today are the hosts from the Fresh and Fit podcast. Fresh and Fit recently has been the most controversial podcast in the space after a explosive interview with Asian Doll followed up by a slew of videos being uncovered where the hosts made comments about their dating preferences not being black women. We have them on to talk about both topics plus much more within the dating / relationship world. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0zsIyOTeNpGa6Mp8aDcZyI</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7430</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 049: Do I Have to Really Pick a Side with Lil Durk and NBA Youngboy?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7KCJdneXQiZFWQXKQEUqoi?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This is our last episode of our mini quarantine, we'll be back in studio next week with guests as well. We begin this episode discussing if Akademiks or fans should be picking a side between Lil Durk and NBA Youngboy. We talk about their issues escalating since the death of King Von and how other rappers have been picking sides. We then talk about The Weeknd new album 'Dawn FM' being underwhelming in quality and sales and compare it to the throwback album that Tory Lanez dropped. We also discuss Casanova possibly asking for help from Jay Z and find out the real answer to 500k or dinner with Jay Z. We introduce a new segment called 'BURNT OUT' and give it to Kanye West for his recent antics surrounding Pete Davidson.  We then end by talking about the rumored story of Drake putting hot sauce in a used condom and the IG Model suing him over it. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7KCJdneXQiZFWQXKQEUqoi</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3268</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 048: Wire-Tapped </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7B2asfYCtzEx8fTVr9UELi?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We begin our Covid Protocol episode with discussing the new variants Delta, Omicron and Deltacron. We talk about Clubhouse and Street/Gang Activity. Also react to a clip of Roddy Ricch going on Clubhouse to check someone from his neighborhood who accused him of false flagging. We then talk about controversial comments made by G Herbo baby mama 'Ari Fletcher' that resulted in her being dropped from SavagexFenty. We also talk about the new albums that dropped Friday, The Weeknd 'Dawn FM' and Gunna 'DS4ever'. We talk about the sales projections for The Weeknd. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7B2asfYCtzEx8fTVr9UELi</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3798</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 047: The Real Story that Fetty Wap Didn't Tell You (feat. Nitt Da Gritt)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6SnVp6qcyvKCNhB6cPbTW2?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Nitt Da Gritt is our guest for this episode for this episode. He is the owner and founder of RGF Productions which is most commonly known for introducing the world to Fetty Wap. After our interview with Fetty, Nitt Da Gritt, wanted to let the world know his side of what happened to the career of Fetty Wap and the role he played in it. He talks about helping Fetty Wap come up, financing his music career until Trap Queen is recorded. He talks about what changes between him and Fetty Wap after the money comes in and details how things become a bit sticky with all the people involved in putting out music for Fetty Wap. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6SnVp6qcyvKCNhB6cPbTW2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7845</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 046: Everyone Ghosted Me After Snitching Paperwork Came Out! (feat. Popp Hunna)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3rqlazW9mN52jMdlhsASAq?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today's Episode features Popp Hunna, the creator of "Corvette Corvette" the most viral song thus far since Tik Tok incarnation. He talks about his come up, growing up in Philly and how he got into music. He talks about how his music popped off which seemingly happened in a span of months in 2021 then also landing a Lil Uzi Vert feature in the same time period as well. He also talks about the decision to stay independent and not sign to a major label. He then talks about the infamous 'Paperwork' that came out that had the streets and everyone in his home town talking about him which then lead to everyone in the music business avoiding him. He finally gives the real story, raw and uncut. He talks about the difference between what he did and 6ix9ine.  Disclaimer: He has a speech problem where he stutters from time to time and its important to note that when listening to this podcast that he isn't lying rather he has a speech problem which has been documented before in other interviews.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3rqlazW9mN52jMdlhsASAq</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7676</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 045: 2021 Wrap Up.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2yja7J6Pdc7Hq8ElIE0uVR?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Akademiks gives us a rundown of what went down in 2021.  He discusses some of the rappers we lost and rappers we saw got incarcerated. (Young Dolph, DMX, Drakeo the Ruler, Slim 400, Biz Markie, Edai, WizdaWizard, Lil Loaded). Also rappers we saw got incarcerated. (YFN Lucci, Pooh Shiesty, Glokknine, Sheff G, Foogiano, Kay Flock, NBA Youngboy, Casanova). We talk about the pardoning of Lil Wayne and Kodak Black by Donald Trump. We discuss Federick Gibbs catching a case of DA BEATS by Jim Jones. Also talk about people going back outside and concerts opening up then Astroworld happening. We discuss Nicki Minaj viral tweets about her cousin and the vaccine. We give flowers to YSL, Generation Now, 1017, QC and CMG. We talk about the comeback of Migos, Saweetie Drama and also Justin La Boy. We talk also about Drake vs Kanye West and the CLB vs DONDA competition that later lead to them squashing it and being on the same stage for Larry hoover. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2yja7J6Pdc7Hq8ElIE0uVR</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4030</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 044: So Yall Want a Relationship like Durk and India?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0jwhK6WT9zq0UE9DrbUoD8?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today we had a roundtable episode with a few women as we talk about pop culture and dating. We talk aging, surgeries, dating in a current market place. Also we discuss the idolization of celebrity relationships and ask if Lil Durk proposing to India has set a new standard for women to aspire to. We then talk Onlyfans vs Stripping and figure out what type of men women want. We talk Brittany Renner and the infamous episode we did on Off The Record. We're still in Holiday Mode lol.. Give us a break. We'll get to our Music Rap ups in the next few Episodes!</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0jwhK6WT9zq0UE9DrbUoD8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6548</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 043: Jay Z Beats Lil Wayne, Drake and Kanye in a Verzuz?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1OInWx3ZcHiJWv94LIXZ18?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Merry Christmas!!!! We discuss how Christmas this year and how people spend them with their families. We then talk about Lil Durk getting engaged to India and then Akademiks gives a story of his brother getting engaged for the second time. We Talk about Youngboy and his face-paint and no one saying anything despite the fact that they would if it was another artist. We talk about Jay Z saying no one could stand on a verzuz stage with him. We discuss if Lil Wayne, Drake, Kanye or Future could actually legitimately compete with him if a verzuz went down and if the criteria changes depends on where it goes down and who is judging it.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1OInWx3ZcHiJWv94LIXZ18</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3973</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 042 - 'I Left A Drake Feature off my Album Because...' feat. Fetty Wap</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0fhO0tZq0VvLMMvX2c1iY0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Fetty Wap is rapper from Paterson, NJ who blew up in 2014 after dropping a slew of hits on SoundCloud. After noticing he had a unique voice and a talent for finding melody, he recorded 'Trap Queen' as his third song ever. Fetty Wap talks abotu his come up with Akademiks and how dropping songs on SoundCloud that quickly blew up in his hometown then later across the internet changed his life quickly. He talks about going to SxSW for the first time and then getting signed to 300 ENT through RGF Productions. He Talks about being arrogant for the first few years of his career and the obligations he turned down because he didn't feel like doing. Fetty Wap says in 2015 he was the hottest artist in the world and recaps how the situation went when Drake hopped on one of his tracks that ended up not being on his album or even on DSPs. He talks the lifestyle that comes with blowing up rather fast and admits to owning 30 cars at one time. Fetty Wap talks about turning down being on tour with Beyonce, Justin Bieber and even Future one year just to go on a solo tour to put his homies on. Fetty Wap says he use to bring 30+ people with him on tours with several DJ's multiple tour buses until Taylor Swift put him on to how she runs her business. Fetty Wap then discusses his issues with his longtime partner, Nitt Da Gritt, and describes how it affects his passion for recording music and continuing in the music business. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0fhO0tZq0VvLMMvX2c1iY0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>8921</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 041 - How I Fumbled a $1 Million Record Deal. (feat. Skinny From the 9)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7MKn7Cgjj81Bv7BWt5ErqJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Skinny from the 9 is our guest today. We talk about his comeup and legal issues that prevented him from achieving his potential in the music industry. He Talks about being caught with a Kidnapping charge, signing to a record label for a million dollars instead of going with his gut and signing to a situation where he felt his career would be pushed. He also talks about how he was finessed into signing that deal and how everyone changed up on him afte rhe signed. He talks about being jumped, sucker-punched and even shot while not realizing how famous he was and also addresses allegations that he was snitching. He talks about meeting 6ix9ine and Shotti and what happened in the aftermath of that.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7MKn7Cgjj81Bv7BWt5ErqJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>8994</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 040: Did Roddy Ricch Deliver or Did he Wait Too Long??</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3pVMN34Ciwb7QdznXp4Hlr?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today is the release of Roddy Ricch's album 'Live Life Fast'. We introduce our new Friday segment which is 'Record of the Week'. We talk about reaction to Roddy's album and talk about why artists take so long to create and drop music. Also speak about the run that Kodak Black has had this year and why he hasn't dropped an album but has dropped many loose singles and a EP. We then talk about expectations of fans when artist take so long to drop.  We then talk about Pooh Shiesty situation and the legal trouble he's in and the message he sent out to fans on social media assuring them he's a Real one. We then end on discussing Rowdy Rebel label situation with Epic Records where he seems fed up with not getting paid despite putting out music and being in a contract with Epic Records since 2014. Music Education 101 is the theme of todays episode. Enjoy!</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3pVMN34Ciwb7QdznXp4Hlr</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3664</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 039: 'Kanye Felt A Way About me Working with Beyonce' feat. [Hitboy] Live</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4seGyFA3VqnXi78Z9CrO7S?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Hitboy joins us today for our live episode of Off the Record. He's a multi grammy winning producer that has worked with the likes of Kanye West, Beyonce, Jay Z, Nas, Big Sean and others. In the last few years his notoriety has increased exponentially and he's now even recognized as more than just a producer, he's seen as a artist as well. Akademiks asks him about his come up and what song that he produced did the most to change his life. We talk about him producing 'Sicko Mode' and 'N*ggas in Paris'. We also talk about Kanye West feeling a type of way that he produced for Beyonce and where the status of their relationship is now. Also, Hit boy reacts to Kanye West comments about Big Sean on Drink Champs. We figure out what Hit Boy favorite produced songs are and also ask him about working with Nipsey Hussle and Roddy Ricch for the grammy winning song 'Racks in the Middle'. We talk about him working with Nas on 'King Disease' and its sequel which are both grammy nominated. We talk about what his future plans are in cementing himself as an artist and also ask about who he would rather do a complete project with Drake or Kendrick Lamar. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4seGyFA3VqnXi78Z9CrO7S</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3557</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 038 'I'm Not a Industry Plant' feat. [Iann Dior] Live</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7G8QATdSApGz64Q2Ff2U9v?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This is our first episode recorded live w/ special guest Iann Dior. We talk about his 2021 and rise to fame in the music industry. He talks about embracing the term 'industry plant' to remove the power from the word and to allow people to focus on his music. He talks about how he was down to his last before having a breakthrough in the music industry and also reflect on him making the XXL freshman list and his feelings on that. We play a game of 'This or That' where he picks between some of his favorite artists and gives an explanation of why he picked each choice. He names artists he would like to collaborate with and even says he wants to venture into TV &amp; film.  Also PS. this episode was recorded live the day after the death of Young Dolph so we open up by talking about Dolph and then safety and security as an artist.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7G8QATdSApGz64Q2Ff2U9v</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5837</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 037: 'God is Great &amp; My Paper's Straight' (feat. Troy Ave)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3XujHeuMV5tVXK7gSamsvk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Troy Ave joins us today for what might be our longest episode of Off The Record yet! If you don't know, Troy Ave is a rapper from NYC who has been embroiled in beef and controversy ever since he came on the scene. One notable incident landed him in jail for a few months after it was seen on camera him chasing someone in a packed club with a gun. He claims that incident was self defense and also his bodyguard was murdered in the very same incident as well. Since then, he's tried to resume a music career but with legal issues hanging over his head and also other people distancing themselves from him, he has tried establishing his own platforms indepently and continue to provide music for his supporters. He's here to talk about everything, from getting his lil bro laid to how he makes his money through music independently and also investments outside of it. He also addresses many of the issues he previously had since most of the dust has since settled.  DISCLAIMER!!!!!! The Following Content Contains Adult Subject Matter, Including Sensitive Material, And Is Intended for Adult Consumption Only. It May Not Be Suitable For All Audiences, Therefore, Discretion is Advised!</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3XujHeuMV5tVXK7gSamsvk</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>13826</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 036: 'I Signed to a 360 Deal for $7500' (feat. Lil Boom)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5hPNuk14N6vRSqR6OVdW8e?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Our guest for today is Lil Boom, a rapper from Florida who struck up a relationship with DJ Akademiks by just being a loyal supporter in his YouTube comment section but was savy enough and musically talented enough to go viral many times by being a head of the curve, manipulating internet algorithms and also being one of the pioneers of 'Meme Rap'. Over 5  years later, he is now releasing his debut album and he sits with Akademiks to explain the full story of how he got to this point. From homelessness, self doubt, street activity to persistence and self belief, this is a story about someone using the internet to achieve their dreams and trying to change the realities and situations of everyone around them. No story is complete without the highs and lows and in a very honest and humble interview, Lil Boom talks about signing for $7500 and getting screwed and then trying to force his way out of a really crappy record deal. His new album 'The End of the World' is already out, do him a solid and check it out if you enjoyed the conversation!</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5hPNuk14N6vRSqR6OVdW8e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4270</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 035: Why The Feds Targeted NBA Youngboy, 6ix9ine, Pooh Shiesty an YNW Melly! (feat. Myron)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4sqEJYpNpKgIGOU94ve6K9?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today our guest is Myron Gaines, a former Homeland Security agent that has worked tons of cases and filed indictments on domestic gangs all the way up to The Cartel. Today we will talk about his background, how feds look at cases overall and why it seems like in 2021 Federal charges against rapper have increased. We talk about the NBA Youngboy recent arrest, federal indictment and also him getting out on bail. We also talk about Casanova's federal RICO indictment and forecast what's the most likely scenario of what will happen to him. We then talk about Pooh Shiesty case and do a deep dive on why the federal authorities seem to be so keen on keeping him off the streets. We then finally touch on the YNW Melly case and Myron gives a very bold prediction of how he believes this will end.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4sqEJYpNpKgIGOU94ve6K9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>8452</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 034: This Might Get Us Cancelled! ( ft. Andrew Tate)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1x2LNvZ2QUk7sUxgm6xddq?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Andrew Tate is our Guest today. He’s a 4x kickboxing world champion. We talk about dating, relationships, gender roles and tradition. Also Andrew gives us a incredible story about his come up and the values his father instilled in him. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1x2LNvZ2QUk7sUxgm6xddq</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7881</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 033: I Found out my Ex Girlfriend was a Sugar Baby (feat. Fresh and Fit)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6Cx7mVWyunP0aAWjNe7Mgj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Once again, We're back in Miami. On this episode of Off the Record, Akademiks along with Myron and Fresh come to resolution about the recent saga with Fresh and his recently exposed girlfriend, Miranda. We discuss and recap what went down and how Fresh felt about his girl being on a sugar daddy site.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6Cx7mVWyunP0aAWjNe7Mgj</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7450</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Youngboy Speaks out from House Arrest! (Live)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3iAloFa1ne1zBSzyCy2XHr?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On this special episode of Off The Record, recently incarcerated rapper (NBA Youngboy) speaks out from house arrest for the first time to Akademiks. This is the first time we've heard his voice since he's been set free from Federal jail on a bond. They begin to talk about his current mental state and how he survived being incarcerated. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3iAloFa1ne1zBSzyCy2XHr</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>10990</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 031: RIP Virgil Abloh</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/162inXbkYM5NysxJ3chMf2?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Akademiks starts out this podcast with acknowledging the passing of Virgil Abloh. He talks about how influential Virgil was but also how people ridiculed him months before his passing. Akademiks talks YK Osiris and mental health. He then gets into talking about Saweetie and Lil Baby and how Quavo and Jayda have been reacting to the the news that Baby and Saweetie might be dating. He then touches on Wack 100 and Blueface dealing with their artist Chris Sean Rock and how that mirrors what happened with Da Baby and Danileigh. Akademiks touches on how some artists are very sensitive to criticism even when there is no intended disresepect. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">162inXbkYM5NysxJ3chMf2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3274</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 030 - Thank You!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1sYpiOefFWtcsVrvLYAAU1?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>After two full months of our launch, Akademiks takes time on this Thanksgiving holiday to thank everyone who made this possible. Thank you to the audience, Spotify, our team behind the scenes and other business people. Akademiks gives the story of first going to Complex and also Cancel Culture. He talks about Dave Chapelle and Netflix being unwilling to part ways with Dave despite the outrage. Akademiks talks why he went to Spotify to do this podcast. We also discuss Will Smith, Kanye West x Kim Kardashian x Pete Davidson. Conversation also get to Saweetie, Lil Baby and Quavo and also Summer Walker and her boo. We talk about Fetty Wap current situation with his label and his legal situation and Akademiks gives a warning to other artists on the come up about why certain other artists disappeared off the scene. Akademiks talks Lebron James and how he handles himself in the media and ends with discussing the highly publicized trials of the killers of Ahmaud Arbery and also Kyle Rittenhouse.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1sYpiOefFWtcsVrvLYAAU1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4590</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 029: "Don't Put me in a Box' (feat. Fatboy)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/63eK6A3JEF2QAdOVKNEkY3?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Fatboy SSE is a online entertainer, known for his comedy, rapping and acting. He Joins todays Off the Record today to talk about his come up among other things. Fatboy Talks about how he blew up on Instagram and detailing when the money caught up to his fame. He also talks moving out the hood and to California. He talks about his decision to do music instead of being a comedian. He talks about J Cole reaching out to do music with him and other artists. Fatboy talks being safe while moving around, how to hustle.  Akademiks and Fatboy also reflects on both of them coming up in New jersey.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63eK6A3JEF2QAdOVKNEkY3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7606</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 028: 6ix9ine Is My Business Partner (feat. Wack 100)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0wMxA5u018HpzpXsZT4RZj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Wack 100 RETURNS! Wack clarifies that him and 6ix9ine despite meeting under interesting terms a few months ago are now BUSINESS PARTNERS! Wack also exposes Suge Knight for shady business and also possibly pillow talking behind Snoop Dogg back. Wack hears the story of how Akademiks and Meek Mill called a truce and he gets asked if there is a possibility for Wack 100 and Meek Mill to end their issues as well. Wack 100 speaks on Blueface home robbery and also his assault charge with a LA bouncer. Wack also breaks down what went wrong when 6ix9ine went to get a feature from Lul Tim in Savannah, Georgia.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0wMxA5u018HpzpXsZT4RZj</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>11559</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 027: RIP YOUNG DOLPH (feat. Meezy)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2aRw84cQufyoPZRku56ZHg?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Meezy is our guest for today. He's been on previously and most notable recognized as being 21 savage manager but also a very influential figure in the rise of the talk app Clubhouse. We begin by talking about Clubhouse and creators who made the app pop off. We discuss equity and also compare his time with Clubhouse as opposed to Joe Budden. We then get to talk about the very unfortunate of the passing of Young Dolph. We talk about how artists can move around safely and if its smart to return to your hometown neighborhood. We also talk about Kanye and Drake squashing beef and try to unravel the myth of J Prince and the pull he has in the industry. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2aRw84cQufyoPZRku56ZHg</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>8437</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 026: They Tried Controlling Me!!!! (featuring Bobby Shmurda)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3EMN0xPZctZi5aZ4bIVtLh?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today's episode guest is Bobby Shmurda. Bobby Shmurda is a hip hop artist from New York City who after exploding onto the scene with his hit song 'Hot Boy', him and his GS9 crew were taken down by the cops on a conspiracy charge in December 2014. He sat in jail for 7 years and got freed earlier this year. He has never done a interview since his release until now. He talks with Akademiks about his rise to fame, the moment he got locked up and the aftermath. Bobby explains his current label situation and says that before now there was an attempt to control him on social media and other public places. He breaks down the relationship with Roc Nation and other artists who have shown him love in the past. He also answers the question if he felt he is owed anything by the artists who have been using his name for extra attention recently. Bobby Shmurda details whats next and how he wants to be more vocal and be able to do him without a label or management censoring him. Also, he gives a breakdown of what is to come in terms of music -- EP on the way then album!</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3EMN0xPZctZi5aZ4bIVtLh</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>8186</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 025: NURSE!!!! He's Out Again!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5OIFdQSJt4ZXXzU8fHScZm?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Akademiks is finally back from Miami. He recaps his time in Miami and tells the story of going to the gun range with a bunch of Dior Demons. He also vents on rappers who he flew out to do episodes with cancelling on him. Conversation then goes back to Astroworld in light of the 9th person dying as a result of their injuries at the concert. Akademiks changes his tune and assess how much blame should be given to Travis Scott for in light of his actions promoting chaos at his concerts over the years. Akademiks also talks about Casanova catching another case adding on to his mounting legal issues. Akademiks talks about the feds sitting. Akademiks breaks down the definition of being really independent and if Soulja Boy has a point about Young Dolph not being independent compared to him. Akademiks also puts ILoveMakonnen in his place after ILoveMakonnen got on twitter and claimed he is the reason why Akademiks has a career.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5OIFdQSJt4ZXXzU8fHScZm</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3684</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 024: Its Travis Scott Fault for the Astroworld Tragedy!!??</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3AqjlcJNmJ0iK0ylyy98DF?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Akademiks is back in Miami again yall and we got one of our past guests, Annoying TV aka Mario back on as Akademiks' cohost. Also joining us is Fresh from Fresh and Fit podcast. We start out by talking about Akademiks lack of understanding in the jewelry game, the breakdown in the mindset behind buying jewelry, wearing it and also whether its a good investment as an asset or not. We later discuss Travis Scott's Astroworld and the disaster of the festival where 8 people were killed after alleged trampling and overdosing occured. We talk the Kanye West Interview and his comments about Big Sean, Just Blaze and others. Also discuss the Kanye West vs Drake thing. We talk about Drake devious ways in beef and discuss if Kanye West is lying or telling his version of the truth. We Also talk about Lil Durk and why his music is effective and then even discuss if what he's doing now is considered Drill by the sound or just by the content.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3AqjlcJNmJ0iK0ylyy98DF</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6912</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 023: High Level (Featuring Cordae)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/76o0mJxL3i7WF1hdN65ggy?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Cordae is our guest for today. He joins us today to talk about his new state of mind, album, and what he's been up to since the last time he sat down and talked to Akademiks. He talks about his new clothing line and mindset, High Level. Cordae talks about how made life changes during the pandemic which meant cutting out some vices that resulted in self improvement. Cordae talks about being in Africa for 5 months during the pandemic and trying to live life to create music that means something. Cordae addresses dropping the YBN off his name and also his relationship with Nahmir and Almighty Jay and also his take on their issues between them.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76o0mJxL3i7WF1hdN65ggy</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6177</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 022: The Story of the Fraudulent Gibbs aka Frederick Gibbs.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2j4lUqa9PaV1GjYwFZosd2?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today, we are in beef yall. A gangsta rapper out of Gary, Indiana 'Freddie Gibbs' has launched a computer attack on famous internet blogger/nerd 'DJ Akademiks'. Today, we expose Freddie Gibbs for being someone who is faking and portraying a lifestyle he hasn't lived. Akademiks also exposed him to be the son of a police officer and that Frederick's whole career was funded through funds from Law Enforcement. (The Irony of him being a gangsta rapper right?). Anyway the exposal and the current update of Frederick continues until Akademiks recaps the Brittany Renner episode. He recaps some of the viral clips and speaks on how Brittany was off camera and what he sees for her future. Akademiks then touches on Fetty Wap getting caught by the feds in a drug sting at Rolling Loud. He also touches on Kim Kardashian / Kanye West</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2j4lUqa9PaV1GjYwFZosd2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3084</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 021: The Trap Queen? (featuring Brittany Renner)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6MWaNgeEAmblol8SL5eveL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Brittany Renner is our guest today. She's a controversial social media personality who recently has been getting a lot of backlash for her public relationship fallout with NBA player, PJ Washington. That has spurred memes, narratives and fans being divided about how they feel about her. She's never addressed any of the narratives or cleared anything up.... until today! She speaks openly about her past, her thoughts on sexuality and also speaks on the perceptions about her that the internet has created. She also is keen on letting everyone know that because she's a mother doesn't mean she isn't a individual who can still express herself. She clears up..kinda.. the rumors about her getting 6 figures in child support from her child's father and also answers the question if she trapped him. She gets confronted with questions about why she is attracted to young dudes and if she actually is scouting out new NFL prospects after recent pictures of her on a college campus and at college football games. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6MWaNgeEAmblol8SL5eveL</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7418</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 020: 6ix9ine Triggered me By Snitching! (Featuring DJ Vlad)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5lvgGemyjL8K9DVxchcQgY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>DJ Vlad joins us for our last episode in our Los Angeles Run. DJ Vlad is the owner of one of the longest and successful independent hip hop media platform currently, Vlad TV.  Rarely seen ever on camera, it is a honor to have him along with Akademiks talking about the media game, his come up and how independent media outlets like Akademiks and Vlad TV are now outperforming and essentially running the game when it comes to music and content creation in hip hop. Vlad speaks on how he focused on growing a interview catalog that he knew would be valuable someday. Vlad talks about Hip Hop's victim mentality where there is a inherent need to blame someone else for your own actions. He also talks about how as things have changed and outlets have become obsolete, he's thought about purchasing XXL Magazine. DJ Vlad addresses people trying to say he's the police, breaks down the Casanova interview and the allegations that he was mentioned in his case. He recaps his come up and talks about the infamous Ransom / Joe Budden beef that the hip hop world was shocked to see documented on his platform. He goes into discussing Lil B, growing and figuring out a business model and also breaking down some of 'life story' style interviews he has of many people who either never had many interviews or who never told their story on other platforms. We talk accountability and also artists being upset with the media rather than their own actions at times. Vlad also speaks about his issue with Soulja Boy and in the infamous interview with the guys who were in a shootout with Soulja Boy. Also he discusses the interview with No Plug, He also talks about 6ix9ine and how he's had a change of tune in terms of offering his platform to him. He admits that 6ix9ine triggered him with certain actions that caused him to have a particular reaction. DJ Vlad goes on to expose the jeweler who also finessed Lil Baby after shady business dealings with that individual in the past. Vlad also gives a epic story of how Drake had his homeboys try to press Vlad about him allowing others a platform to criticize him. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5lvgGemyjL8K9DVxchcQgY</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>10513</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 019: 'Make Comedy Great Again' (Featuring Druski)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1rUvkWYnVcZFMzXCmceKKP?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Druski is our guest for today's episode. He's a internet comedian who in the last few years has risen to stardom to the point he's the opening act on J Cole's "Off Season" Tour. Druskii details his come up and talks about when he first realized he was funny. He talks about being telling jokes to his family then later to school and then translating it to online. He also talks about how making income with a large following was difficult because he was balancing losing a audience and selling promo. He talks about Drake giving him a opportunity to be in his music video. He then decides either Kanye West or Drake if he had to make a choice.  He talks about wanting to develop his skills to be able to do a standup tour and talks the importance of standup for him. He talks about the state of comedy and why its interesting with things you can or cannot talk about. He talks about his future and upcoming moves and gives the Mount Rushmore of new comedians.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1rUvkWYnVcZFMzXCmceKKP</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5243</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 018: 'How I Became the #1 Streamer on Twitch!' (Featuring Adin Ross)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4AiNtzptt38f19IBh4Mmyx?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Adin Ross is our guest today. He's the most popular streamer currently on the Twitch platform and one of the fastest rising on YouTube and Tik Tok. Adin addresses how he manifested his success from a young kid in high school and the sacrifices he and his father had to make to get to the point where he's at. He also speaks about his clout and fame getting to the point speaks on how he initially accidentally stepped into beef by mentioning a song by Yungeen Ace where Foolio got offended. He addresses rumors of him being involved with sketchy gambling scheme that his fans were upset about. Akademiks tries to solve the issues with Adin and 6ix9ine and even get into the behind the scenes of how it may have developed. 6ix9ine vs Adin Ross boxing? Adin talks issues with Polo G and also him trolling being taken way out of context and way more serious than he ever imagined.  </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4AiNtzptt38f19IBh4Mmyx</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7930</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 017: I Could Have Signed NBA YOUNGBOY (Feat. Soulja Boy)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1UoKhcld6uizDEINhtz3TX?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Yung DRACO aka Soulja Boy is our guest this episode.  Its been 3 years since Akademiks and Soulja Boy had a sit down and last time it was all shouting, name calling and pure hilarity. The tone of this entire sit down is notably different with both Soulja Boy and Akademiks complimenting each other on each respective's path to success. Soulja Boy recaps how life has changed for him in the last two years and what he learned from getting locked up after finding a new resurgence of his career in 2017-2019. He details the life changes he's made since and also how his probation officer authorized a raid on his residence on his last day of probation which then landed him into jail at arguably the worst time in his career. He details his time in jail and then coming back and refocusing on creating new moments, new music and new products. He talks about how Kanye West lied to him by pretending he was going to be on Kanye's 2021 LP, Donda. Soulja had the text messages to back his accusations up. He talks issues with Tyga and Akademiks tries to get him to apologize to Tyga and others he's wronged. He reveals he was the first to give Tyga a Cameo in the music industry and shows Akademiks proof of Tyga hopping out of a convertible in the 'She Got a Donk' video. He briefly recounts his issues with Migos and details the mindset he was in while going back and forth with rappers online. He also admits that the attention that was brought from those beefs got him more scrutiny from law enforcement. Soulja Boy talks trolling NBA Youngboy fans back after they started trolling him and reveals he's been in contact with Youngboy's brother OG3Three. He also reveals that Youngboy reached out to him when he was 15/16 and Youngboy could have been signed to SODMG. He talks about his label and focusing on signing artists in light of acknowledging that many artists he collabed with early in their careers became successful later. Soulja Boy gives Akademiks a business breakdown of why he chose the independent path instead of staying signed to a major label. He also shows off his extensive product line which includes Soulja Exotics, Soulja Lemonade, Soulja Pineapple Soda, Soulja Game, Soulja Headphones among others. He explains what really happened with Atari as fans saw their CEO deny Soulja Boy claim that he owned the company. Soulja Boy talks about his movie that he ended up scrapping and talks about the events that led up to him changing the type of music he made. The infamous shootout which involved Soulja Boy using a weapon to defend himself against home invaders put him in a state where making kid friendly music was no longer a viable option for him as he felt it encouraged people to try him. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1UoKhcld6uizDEINhtz3TX</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>8090</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 016: For The Love of The Game (Feat. Van Lathan)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1h4aT4XAZOE7EC9NU7M7ui?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Van Lathan is our guest today. He's a academy award winning film creator and renowned media personality. Many know him from his time at TMZ in which he most famously 'checked' Kanye West, others know him for being a host on 'Higher Learning' and winning an academy award for Best Short Film. The episode kicks off with Akademiks and Van talking about women in Miami, jewelry and respecting women. Conversation then goes back into the history of Van and Akademiks back in high school/college and brings up the age old question of if Nerds are winning. Van explains how its possible to navigate and escape out the friend zone and how that was a effective strategy in college. Things get a bit more serious when Van attempts to hold Akademiks accountable for the effects of his 'War in Chiraq' series on the city of Chicago. Akademiks offers pushback in questioning where the energy is at for others who are more influential in that city for example rappers. Akademiks and Van discuss what Akademiks considers 'The League' and Van questions if some of Akademiks motivation is because of hurt he's suppressed from the past. Akademiks discusses 'beef' with other podcasters which Van also has a relationship with and also questions if there is hypocrisy when others are mentioned compared to him. Conversation gets even more heated with Akademiks accusing Van Lathan of spinning and avoiding giving honest criticism about others he might consider his peers. As you may expect, there isn't much of a resolution in most things discussed but nonetheless it makes for a entertaining episode. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1h4aT4XAZOE7EC9NU7M7ui</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>9144</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 015: The Blame Game (featuring Adam 22)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/70iVZ1XuHZFNyVCrTPsfci?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Adam 22 is our guest this episode of Off The Record. Adam 22 is a entrepreneur, media personality and the owner of the 'No Jumper' media platform. Adam 22 and Akademiks discuss accountability of their platforms and reporting in the hip hop world. Conversation also gets into discussing acknowledgement of newer platforms and how both felt about the BET  Hip Hop Award nomination snub. Adam makes a bold proclamation about the current state of Tekashi 6ix9ine career and also gives a breakdown of how hard it is for media personalities as they grow to still give their real opinion about artists and events happening in the hip hop sphere.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70iVZ1XuHZFNyVCrTPsfci</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>9149</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 014: Meek Mill and Akademiks called a TRUCE!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2Lnp6Kf30RJbmjDnA2NL10?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Yes, you seen the title ... IT IS TRUE.  Akademiks describes the latest update in the saga between him and Meek Mill.  Akademiks gives a recap of his week also breaks down his theory why its the hardest when you're the youngest child. He then talks about the recent arrest of the killers of FBG Duck and how rappers who do Drill music seem to not learn lessons despite police and the authorities basically telling them they are snitching on themselves. Of course, an episode wouldn't be complete without the latest update on Akademiks journey to join the vaccinated crowd. He questions if taking the vaccine is even considered a personal choice these days when you consider that you may lose your job or be unable to work and continue your livelihood without it. He discusses if Kyrie Irving is doing the right thing by giving up almost $16 million to stand on his choice of not being vaccinated. Akademiks explains why he's excited to watch the Boosie movie after hearing people criticizing it and calling it bad. Lastly, the Clubhouse A&amp;R and new wave of highly attractive music A&amp;R gets discussed. Are labels hiring attractive women to recruit artists or are the new A&amp;R's out of pure coincidence seem to be highly attractive?</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2Lnp6Kf30RJbmjDnA2NL10</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5637</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 013: 'Views from the 6ix' (featuring Pressa)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5fd9ZjEicgkD4hR4M1NM2d?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On our episode today, Pressa joins Akademiks to talk about his music career and the music scene in Toronto. Pressa breaks down the politics in the city of Toronto and making it out to now having influence on the US Hip hop scene. He also reflects on recent arrest of rapper Top 5. Akademiks tries to get an understanding of how artists like Drake, Tory Lanez or Nav still have influence on the city though they have crossed over and asks if they owe the underground scene opportunities. We talk about his girlfriend 'Coi Leray' and the criticism she receives online and how he helps her cope. He talks about his plans going forward in putting his brothers on and becoming a legend in his city and hip hop.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5fd9ZjEicgkD4hR4M1NM2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6163</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 012: Selective Morals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3TFZBExResHc1srwqUCRLl?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We finally after 11 episodes get a solo DJ Akademiks Episode. He holds court about our last two episodes with Kodak Black and Omi in a Hellcat. He also addresses the backlash that has been caused by Dave Chapelle's Netflix special and where he stands on the entire issue. He talks about Pooh Shiesty facing life in prison after declining a potential plea deal and opting to go to trial on October 25th. Akademiks recaps his first yacht experience with his homies in Miami and how one particular homie Russell Westbrook'ed the entire situation.  He also gets into learning about Superman's son being bisexual. He gets into squid games and questions the hype about it and wonders if its as good as the hype or Netflix is just able to create hype because they own the platform and the content they choose to put in front of you. He finally ends on some numbers for this weeks albums and talks if numbers is still the standard if most labels can finesse them.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3TFZBExResHc1srwqUCRLl</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3954</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 011: 'The Feds Saved My Life' (Featuring Omi in a Hellcat)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6qv6DUTOk2rdviOZv0i9hs?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Omi in a Hellcat is a popular YouTuber and influencer who was recently caught up in the news for his arrest by the FBI in a federal piracy case. He's known in the hip hop community for his flashy lifestyle, many cars and jewelry. We begin the conversation talking about feds, paranoia and informants (I know lol sorry). We discuss 6ix9ine's driver being a cooperator then open up the show with Omi in a Hellcat letting us know how his life changed from being married a decade until he started making money. He gives a breakdown of how he got started with Gears TV. He then describes how he was operating in a gray area with his business since it wasn't technically illegal. He describes when he realized the feds was on to him and when they seized everything he had a few years ago. Omi explains why he feels someone has it out for him since others who have done similar things or even worse haven't garnered the same treatment by the feds. He also talks about how much money he made in just three years of being successful at what he was doing. Also, he explains how his accountant and others switched up on him and even makes a proclamation that he was happier before the money than he was with it. Akademiks asks what the most expensive one time purchase Omi made. Pocket Watching ensues with Akademiks discussing if Lil Baby really made $50 Million over the last few years since he's been on. Omi clears up his issues with G Herbo and DJ Vlad and gives his thoughts on people who call him a scammer. Omi ends with naming his favorite rappers currently.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6qv6DUTOk2rdviOZv0i9hs</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6884</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 010: 'Pay the Piper or the Sniper' (Featuring Kodak Black)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6oswodfM4k3mATmu113i3G?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Kodak Black joins us for todays episode. In a rare conversation, Kodak Black recaps his time spent in federal prison where he was being mistreated by CO's but eventually got pardoned by the former present of The United States, Donald Trump. He talked about realizing a lot about people around him and figuring out what those feelings of distrust or seeing people move weird was about. He talks about Almost signing NBA Youngboy, squashing the issues and even tells stories of how Youngboy use to hang at his house before Youngboy got to the position he's now in. Kodak Black speaks on being accused of a being cloned and speaks to how people wanted him to turn his back on Donald Trump after his pardon. Kodak black then reveals he was hanging with the bloods while being locked up in prison and even clears the air about Nipsey Hussle &amp; Lauren London. He gets into talking about Florida rappers and also denounces rappers 'smoking on packs' or disrespecting the dead. Kodak also talks demanding his respect for his influence and sauce that many people have ran off with. Kodak gets serious with addressing his drug issues that recently came up in the news and also talks prior interviews with Hot 97 and even discussed his resolved sexual assault case.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6oswodfM4k3mATmu113i3G</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5913</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 009: Stuck in Miami (Featuring Fresh and Fit)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5eMBKlucmkd3K7wXlaP6Gq?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>DJ Akademiks pulls up to Miami in anticipation of finally meeting Kodak Black and links with favorite people in the city, Fresh and Fit. They are a podcast about relationships and lifestyle, a self help podcast for men who need a guide through life and relationships. Akademiks gives the history between him and Fresh and also how he found out about the podcast, recaps his weekend with the guys. Also switches gears a bit and delves into some relationship topics with Fresh and Fit. Conversation eventually leads to the controversial perspective the guys have about dating and relationships and how to survive in a Clout / fast paced economy like Miami. I know most people are used to straight conversations about hip hop, but the lifestyle that comes with it is definitely a bi product of what this podcast becomes. A convo about onlyfans, loyalty, trust issues and beef.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5eMBKlucmkd3K7wXlaP6Gq</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>9780</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 008: Expensive Pain or Overpriced?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4Ft6lz6HHMdgTB7AjcjDnb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>For this episode, Akademiks had to bring two of his friends on this episode to discuss Meek Mill's 'Expensive Pain' album. Continuing with the issues with Meek and AK, Akademiks didn't listen to Meek's album but he had two people who did. AJ, one of Meek Mill's most loyal supporters confronts Akademiks about Meek Mill's new album and also his status in the game. We're also joined by Claudia, who also have enjoyed the club environment in Atlanta and can provide some insight on how current music and also artists have effected the game and where Meek Mill fits in it. Claudia also gives us the finesse how women in the strip club pretend to fake drink with their customers.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4Ft6lz6HHMdgTB7AjcjDnb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4647</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 007: "Pick a Side" (Feat. 21 Savage and Meezy)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0NKWIOfNdOecvHe9r9x84J?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>21 Savage rolled into New York this weekend and hit up Akademiks, and a last minute request from Ak had him pop into the podcast before his set at Governors Ball. As usual, he was brutally honest about everything. He was accompanied by his manager and Clubhouse superstar Meezy. 21 Savage started out describing the differences between people  who 10 years ago prioritized mixtape sites to get access music over legitimate ways. Akademiks was shocked to hear that his favorite Drake might not be seen by some in Atlanta as the biggest rapper in the game because of perspective. We then talk about the first time 21 Savage ever heard a full Drake album and also speak on Verzuz from a perspective of Atlanta vs Everybody. 21 Savage states that there are more Atlanta rappers in the top 30 right now than any other region or city. Meezy and 21 Savage tries to stage a intervention and squash the issues between Meek Mill and Akademiks even resulting in 21 Savage attempting to call Meek Mill on the podcast. This brings up another interesting situation in music about picking sides. NBA Youngboy is used as a example of why he didn't get the full support of the industry when his album dropped. 21 Savage and Meezy both admit that at times even in music, you can't play the middle and after a situation has gone too far you have to pick a side. He even says he wouldn't want to be on Donda after knowing Drake would put him on Certified Lover Boy. Finally Meezy and 21 Savage give their side of the story to the 6ix9ine situation where they were in the same club and 6ix9ine brought it up on our very first podcast with Wack 100. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0NKWIOfNdOecvHe9r9x84J</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4899</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 006: J Cole Needs a EGO</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0QOTHd59A37BUCQtUNctpS?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On Today's episode, Akademiks reveals he's one step closer to taking the vaccine. He recaps his weekend and talks about starting a family and his thoughts on kids. He then recaps the NBA Youngboy album, where YB is at in his career and talks about promo strategy differences between Lil Nas X and Youngboy. He also asks the question if Rappers promoting NFTs is a way to scam their fans. Then we have Cordae's manager 'Ace' join him on set where they discuss The top 3 of the last 10 years and a potential top 3 of the next 10 years. Conversation then gets into whether or not Kendrick Lamar is 'battle tested' and if J Cole needs more of a ego to be considered the best. Cordae is also discussed in the conversation and Akademiks draws a comparison to Chance the Rapper. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0QOTHd59A37BUCQtUNctpS</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4594</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 005: "YB BETTER" </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0d5w0MOCAq8xzrwrObxBRD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On today's episode, Akademiks is joined by some friends, Annoying TV, Silky Durag and others. First, Akademiks recaps the episode with Rich The Kid which he walked off during questioning. The crew then gets into heated discussion while about testing your homie's significant other loyalty and going through her phone. Also, giving your significant other a hall pass with your favorite musician. We talk About Onlyfans, Wack 100 vs Kanye West and Kim Kardashian. Conversation then goes into Lil Baby being finessed for $400K by his jeweler. Silky tries to then call out Akademiks for being late to the Pop Smoke bandwagon and also analyze Lil Tecca's career. Annoying TV gets confronted on giving harsh opinions on YBN Nahmir's latest music and the issues between them thereafter. Finally, the crew attempts to explain why NBA Youngboy has the entire generation of the youth in the palm of his hands. We also explains where Meek Mill fits in the current wave of newer street rappers of the likes of NBA Youngboy, Lil Durk, Lil Baby.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d5w0MOCAq8xzrwrObxBRD</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>8159</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 004: "I'm The Goat" (Feat. Rich The Kid)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/744Yk2X9PqUIxPbwYmKTz8?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rich the Kid, though while being born in New York, found his entry into the music industry after linking with Atlanta's own 'Migos' and Quality Conrol Music. He eventually branched off and started his own label 'Rich Forever Records' where he signed artists like Famous Dex and Jay Critch. He also dropped hit songs like 'New Freezer', 'Plug Walk' that helped exponentially catapult his own solo career as a artist. He joins Off the Record with DJ Akademiks today to talk about his come up, his label and new music on the way. He explains getting his music to Kendrick Lamar, his new collab album with Lil Wayne and his relationship with NBA Youngboy. He gives a update on Famous Dex as well and things get a a lil tense once questions are asked about many of the numerous rumors that have floated around about him over the years.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">744Yk2X9PqUIxPbwYmKTz8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3608</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 003: Who Tried To Kill Jay Z?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6KzysRFNq71YpPX7yY1SxT?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On our launch episode of 'Off the Record', we kick things off by discussing a wide variety of topics including, Kanye 'Donda' vs Drake 'Certified Lover Boy'. Kanye legacy vs Drake Legacy. We try to figure out the riddle of who is trying to kill Jay Z and who he was talking about on 'Love All'. Also, we mention the Karen Civil saga and allegations. Also, we touch on the case of Gabby Petito and speculate what might have happened to her and also what her boyfriend did in the immediate aftermath of her disappearance.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6KzysRFNq71YpPX7yY1SxT</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6079</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Episode: Shotti Responds to 6ix9ine Interview</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3UiAIo6PXTU6FwN3zOjIpJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Tune in for an exclusive, audio-only interview with Shotti. Previously 6ix9ine's right-hand man, he speaks for the first time since 2018 to share his side of the story.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3UiAIo6PXTU6FwN3zOjIpJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2306</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off the Record with DJ Akademiks: 6ix9ine vs Wack 100</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/16Nxc050PeLakH9BxVdIgw?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Our guest today is one of the biggest and most polarizing artists in the world, Tekashi 6ix9ine. His chart topping music shook the industry to its core, but a few years ago things took a turn. In 2018 he pleaded guilty to firearms and racketeering charges and agreed to cooperate with the government. After being released, Tekashi’s involvement in hip hop has been a point of discussion, and many question where his voice should be tolerated.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16Nxc050PeLakH9BxVdIgw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>10681</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Off the Record with DJ Akademiks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2HrsRcVy9ObpjOFFEPPF5B?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>My new show, Off The Record with DJ Akademiks, is coming exclusively to Spotify starting on September 20th. Follow and stay tuned for more roundtable discussions and interviews with music’s hottest artists and personalities.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2HrsRcVy9ObpjOFFEPPF5B</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>67</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

