<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Psych2Go Mental Health Podcast</title>
    <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/0bAOWnt6FZC7WzNzxrB5by</link>
    <description>Saving lives by building a community around mental health and psychology animated content. Our mission is to give you the hard topics and make it relatable and understandable; we hope to decrease the stigma associated with mental health and bring light to the darkness.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8a1c5a5ccf731706b45c687fe5</url>
      <title>Psych2Go Mental Health Podcast</title>
      <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/0bAOWnt6FZC7WzNzxrB5by</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:19:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>6 Signs You Might Have a Toxic Parent - Part 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3HGyVWIdP4wSbmJ6BcdJbW?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>It’s common sense to distance yourself from toxic people, but what if those toxic people are your parents? When you have a toxic family, and you see them every day, that can be extremely difficult. What sort of toxic family members have you experienced? A toxic mother? A toxic father? A toxic sibling? Here are some more toxic parenting behaviors to watch out for: blaming, cursing, manipulating, blocking you from happiness and so much more.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3HGyVWIdP4wSbmJ6BcdJbW</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>347</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schizophrenia... What is it?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0hrSrK6sngkdc5r8bXNwB3?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Schizophrenia is a chronic and severe mental disorder that affects how a person thinks, feels, and behaves. People with schizophrenia may seem like they have lost touch with reality. Although schizophrenia is not as common as other mental disorders, the symptoms can be very disabling. In this video, we cover what is schizophrenia, the signs of schizophrenia, as well as the symptoms.   Schizophrenia is a term that literally translates to “split mind.” There is a common misconception that people diagnosed with schizophrenia have split personalities. Experiencing fragments of one’s personality occurs in people with dissociative identity disorder, or DID, not Schizophrenia.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0hrSrK6sngkdc5r8bXNwB3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>312</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Side Of INFJ - The World's Rarest Personality Type</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4sIEBITCr1mdMpw0AJmDT9?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Are you an INFJ? Did you know that the rarest category is the INFJ, which stands for Introverted, iNtuitive, Feeling, and Judging? INFJs are known to be gentle, thoughtful, and kind-hearted. However, with all the attention that the positive traits of INFJ receive, it is also necessary to focus on the dark side of this personality type. Curious to learn more about the dark side of INFJ? This video is for you!    Disclaimer: This video is based on the Myers-Briggs Type Inventory, which is just a theory and has personality types that are just rough tendencies rather than strict classifications.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4sIEBITCr1mdMpw0AJmDT9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>312</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Signs of a Dark Empath - The Most Dangerous Personality Type</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0fBDk5xRjbB00PORI1F8hG?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Have you heard of the dark empath? When you hear that someone is an empath, you may think it a good thing. But, what if someone possessed cognitive empathy and displayed traits of a dark personality type? Would they use your feelings against you? Know exactly how to behave and act to appear ‘kind’ and ‘normal’ while hiding their true intentions? In this video, we'll be discussing what a dark empath is and the warning signs.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0fBDk5xRjbB00PORI1F8hG</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>288</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex vs Gender vs Orientation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1zHejniYHnEZH6qp9aMRGw?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Learn the difference between sex, gender and orientation. Gender is a social construct while sex is your genetics and what lies between your legs. There can be more than one gender or sex. Orientation is about the sex-gender combination – or lack thereof – that turns us on the most. While are all very capable of selecting potential partners, the pool of people we get to choose from is subject to our autonomic arousal responses (and our intrusive romantic daydreaming).</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1zHejniYHnEZH6qp9aMRGw</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>302</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 Problems Only Highly Sensitive People Will Understand</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6bifQlFlgCRtZmTpDkl2lH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Do you consider yourself a deep thinker and feel things much more intensely than others? If you answered yes, then chances are you’re part of the small percentage of people who are highly sensitive. Being a Highly Sensitive Person – or HSP - means that you are naturally predisposed to process and perceive information on a much deeper level than most. You’re also likely perceptive, empathetic, intuitive, and self-aware. HSPs are also emotionally intelligent and incredibly creative, passionate, people.    As you can imagine, though, feeling and processing more intensely has some downsides. So without further ado, here are 13 struggles only Highly Sensitive People will probably relate to.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6bifQlFlgCRtZmTpDkl2lH</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>466</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Signs You're a Highly Sensitive Person with a Strong Personality</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0n3jws1Yek7ntcP6ZnPZRV?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Highly Sensitive People (HSP) make up 15-20% of everyone all over the world, and even rarer are those who are both HSPs and have a strong personality. Do you consider yourself as a highly sensitive person (HSP) or an empath? Are you among those who consider sensitivity a weakness? If so, that might not be entirely true. A person can be both sensitive and strong at the same time, especially an empath. Watch this video to see if you identify with some of these signs.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0n3jws1Yek7ntcP6ZnPZRV</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>346</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Signs You're Emotionally Abusive To Others</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4VBv0IvDuP8Anz4DfTlnAN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Emotional abuse is more common than physical or verbal abuse but may be reported less because it is harder to prove, this includes narcissistic abuse, gaslighting, emotional blackmail, and so on. Emotional abuse is behavioral and emotional tactics that are used to attack the target’s sense of control or sense of self. Are you wondering if emotional abuse played a role in any friendships or relationships that have been hurtful?  Maybe you are looking to change a few patterns in your life.  Or maybe you are wondering if you are the abuser. This video is for you.    Trigger warning &amp; Disclaimer: If you recognize yourself in any of these examples, please know this was not posted to shame, hurt, or trigger you. Seeing yourself in these behaviors does not automatically make you a bad person or evil.  Rather, seeing yourself in these behaviors means you are able to look at yourself and figure out whether you want to change how you deal with the people in your lives.  If the material in this video is too triggering or painful for you, please honor yourself, even if it means not watching further.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4VBv0IvDuP8Anz4DfTlnAN</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>342</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Signs You Might Have Impostor Syndrome</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3VxCc8f6rDI6KNWMcDwLXN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Impostor syndrome, or “impostor phenomenon,” is a term that was first used in 1978 by psychologists Pauline Clance and Suzanne Imes to describe why many high-achieving people felt like impostors in their respective fields. Do you often feel like a fraud or an imposter? Learning about impostor syndrome can help put a name to feelings of phoniness and give people struggling with it reassurance that they are not the only ones experiencing these feelings. So, here are a few signs you might be experiencing imposter syndrome.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3VxCc8f6rDI6KNWMcDwLXN</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>263</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Facts on the INFJ Personality Type!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2yXLUZnfkcftOYHRmEZG37?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Have you ever taken the myers-briggs personality test, and found out you were an INFJ, aka the Advocate? Do you wonder about the characteristics about the INFJ personality type? INFJs are the rarest personality type, as only 1-2% of the world's population are INFJ. They put the "book" in bookworm, and know how to climb the social ladder. INFJs see things and understand them, and love a good puzzle. They are also very classy, and have a knack for making routine less boring.  Do you identify as an INFJ personality type? What are some characteristics of an INFJ that you relate to? Let us know in the comments down below!</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2yXLUZnfkcftOYHRmEZG37</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>197</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Struggles of Being a Highly Intelligent Person</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2vWuJtfJunNCxFeIXfvN7b?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Intelligent people are gifted at analyzing concepts and building upon them to form a better understanding of the world and those around them, how everything is connected, and why things are the way they are. A Highly Intelligent Person often has remarkably high IQs, academic achievements, and go on to become successful leaders and trailblazers in their fields. However, they are faced with certain problems and challenges that only they can relate to. Having said that, here are 8 struggles only highly intelligent people will understand.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2vWuJtfJunNCxFeIXfvN7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>433</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Sure-fire Ways to Get Your Crush to Notice You</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/50xGTeLpiAGUlZ9IT21k0I?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>So you have a crush, and you’re pretty sure they don’t know you exist. *gulp* Or at least that you “like-like” them. Or… well, yeah, they probably don’t know who you are. For now.  Here are six sure-fire ways to get your crush to notice you.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50xGTeLpiAGUlZ9IT21k0I</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>325</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Signs You're An Old Soul and Think Differently</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2GIDfOjLVk604fHnPj2Qn6?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Have you ever been told you’re an old soul?  Being an old soul means you think and behave more maturely than people your age typically do. You have more knowledge and wisdom than expected and act accordingly. Watch this if you’re curious to find out whether you’re an old soul.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2GIDfOjLVk604fHnPj2Qn6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>351</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Signs You’re an Introvert, and NOT BORING</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3oeIJvLMzJrNovhJhX3qfb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Introverts are individuals who get their energy from spending time alone. Do you identify yourself as an introvert? If so, you might think yourself as someone boring to other people. But is that really true? Introverts are known to have very rich internal life.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3oeIJvLMzJrNovhJhX3qfb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>198</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Signs Someone Is Hiding Their Anxiety</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1D64hr9vkwRU6wyPdGFmGC?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Are you concerned that someone close to you may be hiding deep feelings of anxiety? This video can help you out.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1D64hr9vkwRU6wyPdGFmGC</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>413</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Things Toxic Mothers Say To Their Children</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5265HpxRdtMiVF6XxEuxJL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Usually, the person who is abused in these toxic relationships does not know that they are in one, they fear what would happen if they reached out for help, they have been brought to a very low state of mind, or because sometimes toxicity is very subtle. So, today, we are going to talk about these toxic parental relationships, specifically how a toxic mother relates or talks to their child in order to manipulate them. Disclaimer: This video is for informational purposes only, to help guide you to ask professionals if needed. It is no way a substitute for qualified professional diagnoses or treatment We've also made another video on the signs of a Narcissistic mother: https://youtu.be/pCUecQCODk8</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5265HpxRdtMiVF6XxEuxJL</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>482</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Toxic Things Parents Do To Their Child</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7af9e4aOTExsQ3Cv3d5BDS?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Do you often wonder if your parents truly love you, or are they just being toxic? Toxic parents can be a toxic mother who helicopters you, or a toxic father who expects too much achievement from you. Even if parents do not want to be toxic, sometimes, they unintentionally are toxic. Does your parents downplay your achievements, set expectations too high, control too much, treat you like a child, close off communication?</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7af9e4aOTExsQ3Cv3d5BDS</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>297</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Traits of a Psychopath</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/65TP1vIQ8VzKSdPCWY7Lug?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Superficial charm, a grandiose notion of self-worth, the need for stimulation and impulsiveness, pathological lying, the ability to manipulate others and a lack of remorse and empathy.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65TP1vIQ8VzKSdPCWY7Lug</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>298</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Struggles of Being a Highly Intelligent Person</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1tbbaEelkLnMPXESqX1nKk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Intelligent people are gifted at analyzing concepts and building upon them to form a better understanding of the world and those around them, how everything is connected, and why things are the way they are. A Highly Intelligent Person often has remarkably high IQs, academic achievements, and go on to become successful leaders and trailblazers in their fields. However, they are faced with certain problems and challenges that only they can relate to. Having said that, here are 8 struggles only highly intelligent people will understand.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1tbbaEelkLnMPXESqX1nKk</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>433</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Signs Someone's Pretending Not To Like You 💖👀</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5pyqW6zYUzFm4BieFW9iq6?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Is someone pretending not to like you? Are you getting a tugging feeling that someone likes you, but they have been giving you mixed signals and you have no idea what is going on? Sometimes, their behaviors can get super confusing and mysterious. There are a number of reasons why someone pretends not to like you even though they are interested and attracted to you. They could be nervous, unsure of what you are feeling towards them, trying to suppress their feelings, not looking for a relationship, or emotionally not ready. To help you to get more clarity and affirmation, here is a list of clear indications that someone likes you, but is trying not to show it by pretending.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5pyqW6zYUzFm4BieFW9iq6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>278</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Signs You Have Toxic Parents - Part 1</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0w9mg8D05Tlj3ozK1Kho44?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Toxic parents can be damaging to your mental health. Are you stuck with your parents during the lockdown, and wondering if they are toxic? Have they been putting even more stress onto you and you can't getaway? Being in the same roof with toxic parents can be as detrimental as being in a toxic relationship. So, here are a few toxic parents signs you may relate to. Watch our video, 7 Signs You Might Have Toxic Parents - Part 1, to find out more.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0w9mg8D05Tlj3ozK1Kho44</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>227</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Things Asexual People Want You To Know</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1KRjnyZxSnU7KPzZjdZtRK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Asexuality is an extremely misunderstood sexual identity. Sexual intimacy is important for many of us. Because most of society deems sexual attraction important, asexuals are often ostracized – even pitied – for their sexual orientation. In this video, we cover some of the common misconceptions that asexual people want you to know. If you want to help promote awareness of this topic, help us share this video.   The asexual visibility and education network at https://asexuality.org</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1KRjnyZxSnU7KPzZjdZtRK</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>226</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Your Childhood Affects Your Love Styles</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1aL3Pf985gAkOgmWujNYuL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Our childhood, how we were brought up, our relationships with our caregivers play a big impact on our love styles. Whether you are the pleaser, the victim or the controller, your upbringing is largely responsible for that. Watch this video to see how your childhood might have affected who you are.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1aL3Pf985gAkOgmWujNYuL</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>355</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Signs You're Falling in Love</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1Qh0bRJkHG0tO3mGz1OALX?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>So, you’ve been together with your romantic partner for a while now, but how do you know whether or not you’re falling in love? In the initial stage of dating, it might be hard to pinpoint what your heart is telling you when you have a surge of mixed intense feelings all at once. You’re unsure of whether or not it’s merely physical attraction, infatuation, or the real deal. Moreover, you’re wondering what your partner thinks of you and if they’ve given any thought towards developing your relationship even further. How do you fully decipher your emotions?</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1Qh0bRJkHG0tO3mGz1OALX</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>356</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Signs You’re An INFJ – The World Rarest Personality Type</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/38Mw832OQ1StinW1Fs6xvi?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>One of the rarest personality types in this system is the INFJ, which is characterized by Introversion, Intuition, Feeling, and Judgement. This type of personality makes up less than 2% of the world’s population and people with this kind of personality are known for their warm empathy, keen insights, and deep insights into human potential. Do you think you might be an INFJ? Watch this video to find out.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38Mw832OQ1StinW1Fs6xvi</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>372</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Signs You May Have High Functioning Depression</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7nIUVYjncR6iMujOFZwlwh?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Many psychologists associate high functioning depression with persistent depressive disorder. Which is a prolonged state of depression. Those with high functioning depression may not feel as helpless as those with clinical depression, but their depression does affect tremendously their quality of life. It minimizes their interest in everything, including social events with friends and family. High functioning depressives will socialize when necessary, and will go to work and school. But once they are done with their responsibilities they will withdraw themselves. Here are 7 signs you may have high functioning depression.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7nIUVYjncR6iMujOFZwlwh</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>200</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Signs Someone is Secretly In Love With You</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3yNdjaksVmawp1nZOe5y6i?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Have you ever fallen head over heels for someone but couldn’t tell if they felt the same way? Or maybe wanted to know if the person who’s been flirting with you a lot felt a deeper connection towards you? Are you looking for some love advice to know whether some is secretly in love with you? So many of us let our love go unspoken because we’re afraid of getting rejected or feel uncomfortable with emotional vulnerability. If you're wondering if you should confess to someone because you're unsure about how they feel, this video is for you.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3yNdjaksVmawp1nZOe5y6i</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>330</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Signs You Were Never in Love</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0U1hf0Ke9vKy3qPJPLEkLv?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Do you wonder if you're still in love with him or her? Unfortunately, love is something that fades. And sometimes, it might be helpful to recognize the signs early than late. If you are no longer in love with someone, you have to let them know.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0U1hf0Ke9vKy3qPJPLEkLv</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>298</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Toxic Things Parents Say To their Children</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/43NjQlnMq3smeyLwRdkovD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Do you wonder about the toxic people in your life? What if your mother is toxic? What if your father is toxic? Or what if both of your parents are toxic. Regardless, of whether your family members are really toxic or not, Psych2Go made this video to highlight the 8 things that toxic things that parents or anyone could say to you.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43NjQlnMq3smeyLwRdkovD</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>364</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Common Dream Meanings You Should NEVER Ignore!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5Q7QIk95mz56jh7nK3N9PK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Do you frequently have common dreams about certain themes, and wonder if the dream symbols mean something? Here are 7 common dream meanings you must know about. Have you ever dreamed about being lost or trapped? How about missed opportunities, or car troubles? Some other common dreams include failing a test, being chased, teeth decay, and falling or sinking. Although there is no scientific evidence to prove that dreams hold special meaning, dreams have been studied to promote better self-awareness and to help us understand what's bothering us in our everyday lives.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5Q7QIk95mz56jh7nK3N9PK</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>310</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

