<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Real Pirates</title>
    <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/1kccYfBJh374gfkNDVHiYr</link>
    <description>Pirates. For centuries the world has been fascinated by them. Their legends have swollen to fantastic proportions. But who were they really? Join us each week as we set sail alongside legendary outlaws such as Blackbeard, Samuel Bellamy, Henry Morgan and Ann Bonny. We’ll separate fact from fiction and discover what life was really like under the black flag. Real Pirates is a Spotify Original from Parcast produced in partnership with Noiser.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8ac5f4a04302c0f365075069b1</url>
      <title>Real Pirates</title>
      <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/1kccYfBJh374gfkNDVHiYr</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:40:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bonny &amp; Read Part 3: End Game</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4BxB1n8LslO8QxMjUrlJdX?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rackham, Bonny, and Read are just getting started, wreaking havoc on local shipping. But they're not too busy to settle old scores — or seek revenge on those who have wronged them. Little do they know, it's they who are being hunted. We ask what life was really like for these two female pirates. Stripping back centuries of myth and legend, can we unearth who were the REAL Bonny and Read? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4BxB1n8LslO8QxMjUrlJdX</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2564</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bonny &amp; Read Part 2: Shattered Dreams</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4CaprVqRFwNKdp67uqyiEo?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Bonny and Rackham are back on the account and ready to blaze a trail through the Caribbean. But hardly a week at sea and harmony aboard the Revenge is shattered... At the heart of it is a striking young sailor – Mark Read – and a closely guarded secret. A secret he has successfully kept hidden for years. That is, until he meets Anne Bonny. The truth will set him free and launch this unusual crew into the history books. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4CaprVqRFwNKdp67uqyiEo</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2232</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bonny &amp; Read Part 1: Dangerous Love</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7GRS4umSn00JXM8e3Bfr0B?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>After the fall of Nassau, only the most desperate, or the most foolhardy, would go on pirating against mounting odds. Time will tell which camp Captain 'Calico Jack' Rackham belongs to… But out of this chaos will emerge an unconventional crew, as legendary as any who came before. It all comes down to a chance meeting in a tavern between 'Calico Jack' and Anne Bonny. A woman, and a pirate, like no other. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7GRS4umSn00JXM8e3Bfr0B</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2241</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of the Republic Part 4: Violent Delights</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0B9dtCqQS4Mw72BLC2WJpR?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Piracy is now a game of diminishing returns. Even a fearsome figure like Charles Vane knows he only serves at the pleasure of his crew. Should he slip up, one man in particular is waiting in the wings... 'Calico Jack' Rackham. On Nassau, Woodes Rogers lurches from crisis to crisis, straining to control a divided populace. However a new threat is on the rise that might yet unite them... War with Spain looms large once again. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0B9dtCqQS4Mw72BLC2WJpR</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2842</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of the Republic Part 3: Hearts &amp; Minds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5RpYrEtHmjLsx7O16jgLZx?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>With the threat of Charles Vane lurking in the shadows, Woodes Rogers struggles to assert his authority in Nassau. Little did he know taking control of the Bahamas would be the easy part; maintaining it may prove far harder. Pro-pardon pirates are now faced with the hardships of making an honest living... for many it's too much, quietly slipping back into their old ways. Vane too must now adjust to the changing landscape. With fewer friendly ports and easy scores, he must be bold to keep the loyalty of his crew. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5RpYrEtHmjLsx7O16jgLZx</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2564</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of the Republic Part 2: Charles Vane</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/70a49g6dgEPAHLvaEx716z?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Woodes Rogers stands on the precipice, his fate hanging in the balance. As he enters the harbor at Nassau, he can hardly imagine the trials and tribulations that will soon be upon him. But then, no one said bringing civilization back to the Bahamas was going to be easy. First and foremost he will have to deal with one of the most hardened criminals ever to emerge from the Americas: a diehard and unrepentant pirate… Captain Charles Vane.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70a49g6dgEPAHLvaEx716z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2752</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of the Republic Part 1: Woodes Rogers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3fgiLHnx4zSh9Gzd3ZLHdb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The final showdown is coming... A Royal Navy task force is on its way to finally take on the pirate base on Nassau in the Bahamas — the symbolic home of piracy in the Caribbean. It's not a mission for the faint-hearted. No wonder then, that the man in charge is as hard as they come. Captain Woodes Rogers: mariner, slaver, explorer, military hero. He's battle hardened and has the scars to prove it. We explore the backstory of the man who is tasked with bringing an end to the Republic of Pirates. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3fgiLHnx4zSh9Gzd3ZLHdb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2703</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pirate Hunter</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/04OxWWRE4xCUaiTd0M5vS5?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Piracy in the Caribbean is at its height, but the tables are slowly turning. The colonies and the crown now work together to try and end the Golden Age of Piracy for good. Pirates are being tried and executed in greater numbers. But many remain at large. The truth is catching pirates isn't easy. Even for the Royal Navy. By 1718, only one man has truly earned the reputation as a pirate hunter. Aboard the HMS Scarborough, Captain Francis Hume is determined to succeed where so many have failed. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04OxWWRE4xCUaiTd0M5vS5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2736</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlikely Allies Part 5: Bonnet’s Revenge</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6dkazEO4MKtVDTtfoVBy1p?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We return to pick up the story of Gentleman Pirate, Major Stede Bonnet – Blackbeard's partner in crime. In the months after Blackbeard's betrayal, Bonnet and his crew of loyalists will have a big decision to make – to take the pardon and return to polite society or to go on pirating, and, perhaps, pay the price. For most pirates, a comfortable retirement is not an option... but for Stede Bonnet, a return to his life of luxury on Barbados is now within his grasp. First, he has a score to settle. Come hell or high water, Bonnet will have his revenge! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6dkazEO4MKtVDTtfoVBy1p</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2894</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlikely Allies Part 4: Blackbeard’s Head</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4GFpLoKd6SselLEkoTiVHu?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In early 1718, the extent of Blackbeard's cold-hearted ruthlessness shocks many — including his closest allies. Always one step ahead, it seems Blackbeard will keep outsmarting his opponents and living on his own terms. But his outsized reputation is becoming a heavy burden. Before Blackbeard can disappear off the map, he catches the attention of the one man who will stop at nothing to bring him to justice: Governor Alexander Spottswood, the scourge of pirates. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4GFpLoKd6SselLEkoTiVHu</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2650</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlikely Allies Part 3: Blackbeard’s Terror</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7rRlNA1cGqFE8bYdutsURd?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Now at the height of their powers, Blackbeard and Stede Bonnet have the colonies at their mercy. But they receive news from Great Britain that will affect every pirate in the Americas. It's time to take stock and make a decision on the future. Some will rage against their new reality, whilst others will surrender to it. Blackbeard won't be easily cowed, he has a plan... but first he needs to make that one big score that will secure their futures. With the clock ticking, the hunt is on. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7rRlNA1cGqFE8bYdutsURd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2854</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlikely Allies Part 2: Blackbeard</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/22GgslIRiLcfkmOhxLNWvj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The unlikely pairing of gentleman landlubber Stede Bonnet and the battle-hardened Blackbeard proves to be a great success… at least for one of them. It may not turn out to be the equal partnership Bonnet had envisaged. For Blackbeard though, it's everything he could dream of and more. His name is soon scorched across the Americas. A legend in his own lifetime. But is he really as fearsome as his reputation suggests? What's the real story behind his sudden rise? And what part did the colonies play in creating the monster that now stalks them? Meet the man behind that notorious beard. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22GgslIRiLcfkmOhxLNWvj</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2845</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlikely Allies Part 1: The Gentleman Pirate</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6tcibvpd9ZpdRwsoOpqqNK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Piracy in the Americas is reaching a climax. The British Empire has decided that enough is enough. The war on Pirates is beginning. But in this increasingly hostile landscape, some of history’s greatest seafaring villains will emerge. Chief amongst them is Blackbeard. In 1717 Captain Edward Thatch is still a relative unknown... a minor brigand operating out of the Bahamas. But all that is about to change. Little does Thatch know, his legend will be launched thanks to a chance meeting with an unlikely figure — Major Stede Bonnet. The upstanding colonial nobleman turned outlaw. This is the story of The Gentleman Pirate. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6tcibvpd9ZpdRwsoOpqqNK</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2676</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Black' Sam Bellamy Part 4: Trials &amp; Executions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3lKu8Lz4fgZMnwdjiLKiOK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In the autumn of 1717 the storm that sank the Whydah may have abated, but the winds of change still pummel the survivors. In fact, all across the Atlantic the British Empire and her colonies now start to turn the screw on pirates everywhere. The remaining Bellamy pirates face an uncertain future. Some will try and forge new careers against mounting resistance, but others must stand trial for their crimes against society, the crown and God. Boston hosts a landmark legal case. Some are guiltier than others – will any be spared? Or will they all end up at the end of a short drop and dancing the hangman's jig? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3lKu8Lz4fgZMnwdjiLKiOK</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2883</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Black' Sam Bellamy Part 3: The Fall</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7jbFEJtuQPouYXYIIiQNHC?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In the concluding part of 'Black' Sam Bellamy we discover what, if anything, can check his astonishing rise to power. By the spring of 1717 he has gone from impoverished peasant to peerless pirate captain. And now his golden touch brings him closer to greatness as he targets a vessel that will elevate him even further. We finally get to the root of his fantastic legend, stripping back the mythology that has sprung up around him. But dark clouds are gathering... and he must make a perilous journey back to New England... to where it all began. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7jbFEJtuQPouYXYIIiQNHC</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2432</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Black' Sam Bellamy Part 2: Prince of Pirates</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5CKdBIXzCBJo3rmpAwYtTb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In a matter of months, Bellamy pushes to expand his crew and his pirate fleet at breakneck pace. As he continues to lay waste to colonial shipping, he must navigate the first real test of his strength and overcome the doubts that plague him... as well as those of his followers. Bellamy knows better than most — a captain only serves at the pleasure of his crew. And pirates can be a fickle bunch...  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5CKdBIXzCBJo3rmpAwYtTb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2394</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Black' Sam Bellamy Part 1: The Rise</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2VJ93GxyUdL7GFXJb7zGRj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We return to the Golden Age of Piracy in the Caribbean with the story of one of the most feared and notorious mariners of the 18th century: ‘Black’ Sam Bellamy. Seemingly from nowhere, a common seaman rises up to become the scourge of the Atlantic — a rags-to-riches story like no other. But it is a tale that has grown to fantastic proportions… Is it possible to peel back the centuries of myth to reveal the man beneath? Social revolutionary? Rogue agent of change? Or a jilted lover with a point to prove? Who is the REAL ‘Black’ Sam Bellamy? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2VJ93GxyUdL7GFXJb7zGRj</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2341</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"The Christmas Rapture” from Cults</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6GE3YDlWOxD1rWdHpzrVCE?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On Christmas Eve nearly seventy years ago, Dorothy Martin and the Seekers stood outside in Chicago and sang carols. They were waiting for a spacecraft that would shepherd them away from Earth — and the impending apocalypse. This is a Christmas special from Cults, another Spotify Original from Parcast. If you like it, follow Cults for more chilling insights every week. Real Pirates will be back with a new episode next Monday. Thanks for listening! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6GE3YDlWOxD1rWdHpzrVCE</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2313</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ho Ho Ho and a Bottle of Rum!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/77AIc6ESml20lnO8ZI8NYH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>It's a well-known fact that pirates like to party. It's all part of the job - commonly called the 'Merry Life.’ Rum, music and dancing were part of the allure of going 'upon the account' in the 18th century. But what did the Pirates of the Caribbean do at Christmas? There are mutinies, beach parties, and a big night out in the pirate port of Tortuga. Find out how pirates spend the festive season in this REAL PIRATES Holiday Special! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77AIc6ESml20lnO8ZI8NYH</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2259</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pirate Republic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7CVe31K0dt7W3kl39vAavQ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Welcome to the Pirate port of Nassau. The year is 1716, and all manner of criminals and ne'er-do-wells flock to the growing pirate haven in the Bahamas. We delve into their ramshackle life in the ruined remains of a British colony. Supported by black market traders, tavern keepers and sex workers, an illegal maritime economy sprang up and, for a time, flourished in the Caribbean. We meet the pirates and traumatised locals who coexisted there under the leadership of Captain Benjamin Hornigold. Find out what life was really like in the Pirate Republic. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7CVe31K0dt7W3kl39vAavQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2493</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning Pirate Part 3: The Rivalry</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6IC7i1zK062Z61oSoNN5cu?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The Hurricane that scuppered the Spanish Treasure Fleet of 1715 was a seismic event — and a catalyst for piracy in the Caribbean. Now two rising powers face off: the self-styled pirate king Benjamin Hornigold and his nemesis, the self-righteous privateer Henry Jennings. In the shadows of these early skirmishes, names emerge that will become legends in their own right. Edward Thatch (alias Blackbeard), Charles Vane and ‘Black’ Sam Bellamy burst onto the scene.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6IC7i1zK062Z61oSoNN5cu</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2401</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning Pirate Part 2: Henry Jennings</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0A2fq8cpPCyPLH6hOG7UAk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In the early 1700s the changing tides of geopolitics play havoc with trade and economics in the Americas. Tensions rise between the Royal houses of Europe and their overseas colonies in the Caribbean. The line between right and wrong is becoming blurred as many look to exploit the grey areas of international maritime law. Captain Henry Jennings is about to find out that the path into piracy is paved with Spanish Gold. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0A2fq8cpPCyPLH6hOG7UAk</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2371</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning Pirate Part 1: Benjamin Hornigold</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/44thmVmCr5U34TrZN8K61G?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The year is 1713 — it’s the eve of the Golden Age of Atlantic piracy. A period that would give birth to some of the most notorious outlaws in history. In the fallout of a ruinous global conflict, from the ashes of peace, one man would rise up and inspire thousands to follow his steps into piracy. Benjamin Hornigold and a desperate crew of sailors decide to go ‘upon the account’ — as Pirates.     Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44thmVmCr5U34TrZN8K61G</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2602</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real Pirates Official Trailer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0J6F4lAXCs9qvXH08n5NF0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Take to the high seas for an epic adventure into the lives of legendary pirates. Who were these men and women who roamed the oceans? What was life really like under the black flag? Find out every Monday on Real Pirates, a Spotify Original from Parcast produced in partnership with Noiser. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0J6F4lAXCs9qvXH08n5NF0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>60</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

