<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Shugga Service with Ian Isiah</title>
    <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/2vAt0wZG37Q4b1NvqQY2Gt</link>
    <description>Shugga Service is a weekly freeform talkshow with the multi-hyphenate that is Ian Isiah. The Brooklyn native that has already staked his claim in music and fashion is now hosting his very own Spotify exclusive podcast. Ian will be coming at you every Friday with the news, his views, and conversations with vibrant guests like Justine Skye and Dev Hynes (Blood Orange).Listen to Ian Isiah on Spotify.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8ad0ac0087ef856646ab9c7f6e</url>
      <title>Shugga Service with Ian Isiah</title>
      <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/2vAt0wZG37Q4b1NvqQY2Gt</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:51:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Moving On Up with Josh Johnson</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6jW9lufzkEGIu83UIy4cmD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Back after a brief but too long break we are here to deliver. The Shugga Service is going on all cylinders this week as we welcome movement director and internationally renowned dancer Josh Johnson to the show to discuss a myriad of issues pertaining to his life. He is a trail blazer, and you're going to want to hear what he has to say. As always we have the news and views since we're the ones who seem to have some sort of clue. Tune in and chill out, it's the Shugga Service. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6jW9lufzkEGIu83UIy4cmD</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1103</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community with GirlKell</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0sWHZ0xi1AvJz6sAHhe7iU?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Hello how are you and welcome back to the Shugga Service, this week we are speaking to and about the community with our dear friend the amazing Girl Kell. Tune in and inspire yourself to get involved! Another episode of light and love, courtesy of Big Shugga. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0sWHZ0xi1AvJz6sAHhe7iU</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1343</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giggles with Kerwin Frost</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3ovWkSY25uwa9koaNFC4UR?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week on Shugga Service we touch base with the creative force Kerwin Frost, and talk about how you can make your dreams possible, and get a little insight into how he follows his. Strap on your boots and put on a furry hat, it's time for the Shugga Service. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ovWkSY25uwa9koaNFC4UR</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1503</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paging Dr. Berry with Mr. Vacation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/38OIyCU43GMYfSFq26Hk1S?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Paging Dr. Vacation! Paging Dr. Vacation! Please come to the Shugga Booth! This week on the Shugga Service we welcome the wonderful DJ Mister Vacation aka Dr. Alaina Berry onto the program to talk about this, that, and the third. As always we have our share of flowers, news, views, and the like so tune in and get into it! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38OIyCU43GMYfSFq26Hk1S</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1374</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Real Saint Patty</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5IuhnUBSm6bj2f54cvcLy6?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week on the Shugga Service we are joined by an old friend and much needed voice, editor and writer Patrik Sandberg. The two discuss all manner of things, and you’ll just have to tune in to get the details. As always we salute a local hero, give out roses and shake our heads at the news. All this and more, on the Shugga Service. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5IuhnUBSm6bj2f54cvcLy6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1139</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic Finger Micka</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1JwvN3fl2eGdUg9LfwufJe?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>If you think you see a shimmer in the air or a sparkle in the sky, your eyes don’t deceive you, because you’ve tuned into the Shugga Service, and this week we have Magic for you. The magic of Mika! Tune in to hear sage advice and good conversation from an industry mainstay and all around delightful person, stay for the news views and as always a beautiful Word of the Week to keep away from the blues. All that and more, on the Shugga Service. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1JwvN3fl2eGdUg9LfwufJe</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1252</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J6 with James Garland</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3QCZbKZb3FMFjUsI2UOa9a?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week on the Shugga Service with Ian Isiah: longtime friend and forever legend James Garland stops drops a line all the way from Italy to talk about his new line for SSENSE, old history, and everything in between. Tune in for your weekly dose of the Shugga Service. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3QCZbKZb3FMFjUsI2UOa9a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1505</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RREEPPLLIICCAA with RREEPPLLIICCAA</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/480RVyLP4ouTQGafQmr91W?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We go behind the scenes this week on Shugga Service! Ian talks with the duo behind the production agency RREEPPLLIICCAA about what it takes to strike out on your own in the fashion industry, and what it’s like to help Telfar TV come to life. Come for the chat, stay for the views and news, get a clue it’s the Shugga Service with Ian Isiah. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">480RVyLP4ouTQGafQmr91W</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1214</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smooth Art Purr Radio with DonChristian</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/77s7xeMsybWxgFFrB6NgE7?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week we are surviving fashion week. In fact, we may even be thriving. We have updates from the life and the world, and naturally, a guest that lights up our works. Don Christian Jones joins us this week, and he has some exciting news. All that and more, on this week’s Shugga Service. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77s7xeMsybWxgFFrB6NgE7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1320</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Headless with Anonymous</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6EQsQgWRA7neIgoombkBKl?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On today’s Shugga Service we are getting down to the root of a mystery you’ve all been pondering…who and what is ANONYMOUS? Recorded during rehearsals for this weekend’s three day presentation at the Shed, Pablo sheds just enough light on the collective, with a hello from a very special guest. This is not the episode to miss. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6EQsQgWRA7neIgoombkBKl</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1413</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Spoken Word with Kai Isaiah Jamal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1bvwWCi0LVOClXmUknb4Ek?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week on Shugga Service - Kai Isiah Jamal joins us to grace us all with their poetry beauty and power. Tune in to gain enlightenment. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bvwWCi0LVOClXmUknb4Ek</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1451</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So Radio with Nick Harwood</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1qUDpPjJtZHHjL9bVKyZe9?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Welcome back to the Shugga Service! This week we’re going to the movies…or are we listening to the radio? This week we host one of our favorite up and coming (damn near arrived) directors, Mr. Nick Harwood. He speaks on his career, his beginnings, and his dream of being a radio personality. All that plus the News, Views, and Chit Chat Chew you have come to expect, only on the Shugga Service. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1qUDpPjJtZHHjL9bVKyZe9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1747</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will The Real Archive Please Stand Up with Eric Johnson</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5hr9BhNQcI19JzdmJBgeWM?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Hello and welcome back to another episode of the Shugga Service, as we continue on with the third episode of 2022, we continue bringing you legends. This week’s guest, photographer Eric Johnson, has been contributing to the culture for decades. Whether you know it or not, you’ve seen the images he’s made, and if you feel anything you’ve felt them. As always we have some views and the news before we chit chat chew. Just another packed episode of the Shugga Service. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5hr9BhNQcI19JzdmJBgeWM</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1999</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Icon Fridays with Mike Q</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0gdcKF3fkbP6QwwHKvugq2?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Hello, and welcome back to the Shugga Service with Ian Isiah, your only location for the station talking this talk. This week our guest is none other than the legendary MikeQ. Either that’s all that needs to be said, or you don’t know and must find out. Either way, it’s time to press play. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0gdcKF3fkbP6QwwHKvugq2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1418</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>True Beauty with Raisa Flowers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6gosq2hpBfrcKEdDVGx1oF?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Happy New Years to you and yours! You made it to 2022, and thank God for that. Our first guest of the year is none other than Raisa Flowers. Tune in to hear about her journey to becoming one of those most sought after nail artists in the Industry. As always we will take time to reflect on a word of the week and give someone their roses, so stop pausing and press play, it’s time for the Shugga Service. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6gosq2hpBfrcKEdDVGx1oF</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1630</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lemon Squeeze with Quil Lemons</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/03Qd5609mxAPTtMjZnn0s8?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Season's Greetings, from the Shugga Service! We're leaving you with one last episode for the year. We hope you've made it safe and sound, because this one's special as always. The young legend photographer Quil Lemons comes by to speak on his work and especially on his vision. You'll just have to tune in to find out. It's all here, on the Shugga Service.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03Qd5609mxAPTtMjZnn0s8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1904</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talk Of The Telly with Telfar and Babak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7LAb0qAEWPVMQOlqGML2fW?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We have a very special treat to follow up last week's very special treat, because Thee Telfar Clemons came by the Shugga Service alongside his collaborator Babak Radboy to chit chat chew with Ian. The results are glorious, and you'll just have to listen. As always, we have the news views and everything else you need ready and waiting for you on here, on the Shugga Service. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7LAb0qAEWPVMQOlqGML2fW</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2385</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birthdays On Stage Is The Only Way To Rage</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5u81LNwf00nbpvhmgrdK7u?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week is a Shugga Service like no other. Join Ian, his friends, family, and his band for a special live Birthday episode! Hear from guests past and future along with a very special live set from Shugga himself. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5u81LNwf00nbpvhmgrdK7u</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1822</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Big Plate Of Love with ONLUNCHBREAK</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4mJBoe9a44np2zHPKNpzbi?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Hello and welcome once again to the show with the most. This week Ian breaks bread with the community oriented ball of light that is On Lunch Breaks founder Thuan Tran. They discuss building a community and how to know yourself and what you want. As always we hit you with the news, and we have an especially important Word of the Week that you will not want to miss. All that and more, on the Shugga Service. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4mJBoe9a44np2zHPKNpzbi</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1549</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real Tips with Dawn Sterling</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/43Us2tuF8SLQn70xBWgzWk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We know it’s a long wait until Friday for your life and for the Shugga Service, but we hope you haven’t been biting your nails because the cuticle queen, the nail goddess Dawn Sterling, joins Ian Isiah this week to discuss her rise to the top of the first chairs. The news is crazier than usual and the word of the week is more powerful than ever. Sit down and spark up because you are you and you deserve it. It’s time for the Shugga Service. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43Us2tuF8SLQn70xBWgzWk</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1501</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Process with Aya Brown</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2LoIYHwg4bhzoS1qYkiTbs?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week on the Shugga Service, our beloved host sits down with his granddaughter, the young artist on the rise Aya Brown to discuss her practice and how to create what you need to see in the world. The news is chaos as always and the word of the week is better than ever. Sit down and strap in, we’re glad you dressed up you look great. It’s time for the Shugga Service.Find Aya Brown's work here. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2LoIYHwg4bhzoS1qYkiTbs</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1568</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Does It All Even Meme with Patia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0xnjNPu9SB1pfJNZWkqlIT?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Are your selfies memes? Are your memes selfies? What does it all meme anymore? Strap in for a very special Shugga Service with the memestress herself Ms. Patia Borja. Ian and Patia catch up on her wild last year and a half and talk about what else: the internet. Tune in for that convo plus all your usual favorites, right here, on the Shugga Service. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0xnjNPu9SB1pfJNZWkqlIT</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1643</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nights Over Egypt with Jawara</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5viCsVv5zNpDbkB8ZiiOfx?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week on the Shugga Service we go more than scalp deep. Hair legend JAWARA stops by and he and Ian get into it on all manner of topics, but you’ll have to listen to find out more. As always we deliver the news, views, and ways to fight the blues, with another life affirming word of the week. More crazy call ins and much much more, all for you every Friday on the Shugga Service.Find Jawara on Art Partner Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5viCsVv5zNpDbkB8ZiiOfx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1695</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girls Only, You Heard</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/76DuG2VcReLKwPGeTvj7Ng?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week on the Shugga Service, we talk to the power couple behind Girls Only, an organization that is truly “hugging the block.” We talk about community fridges and much much more, so tune in for some inspiration on how to get involved with the people around you. Of course we always have to give you some news, roses, a carry of the week, and so much more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76DuG2VcReLKwPGeTvj7Ng</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1618</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filmed Up with Leilah Weinraub</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6qe6uddEQ0iedp1ki8FdOk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week on Shugga Service, esteemed director, former HBA CEO, and good friend Leilah Weinraub joins the Shugga Service to speak on her experience as an artist as well as her landmark documentary Shake Down. What's next for our favorite director? You'll have to tune in and hear all about it. As always we're joined by crazy callers, we check out the news, and give out some roses, only on the Shugga Service. Watch Shakedown here. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6qe6uddEQ0iedp1ki8FdOk</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2301</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Force with Christina Jo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1hVuZCv7UcRAoyYC5HnyxU?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On this week's Shugga Service we talk about the ins and outs of Motherhood with Ian's good friend Christina Jo. On top of that entree the appetizers are still there as well; we dive into the news, hand out roses and give out the word of the week (hint: DO NOT dim your light for others) Enjoy! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1hVuZCv7UcRAoyYC5HnyxU</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1709</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testimony Time with Latisha Chong</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6XOMGCtiZg0hqjoNM2OsZ1?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today’s Shugga Service we learn about real strength and purpose. Ian gets into real life with this week’s esteemed Guest, renowned hair stylist Latisha Chong. In addition to that sterling conversation that you cannot and should not miss, we have some more wild call-ins to the hotline, news, views, roses for a living legend, and everything else you didn’t know you needed, right here on the Shugga Service. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6XOMGCtiZg0hqjoNM2OsZ1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2096</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locks with Gitoo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0gBvOY9PmfpFcQa8KnhJ2A?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>On this blessed Friday we greet those atoned and those waiting to atone with our weekly dose of the host that's known for the most delivering the Shugga Service. This Week Ian is joined by casting director and global party host Jorge "Gitoo" Wright, who’s here to speak the truth, the whole truth, and maybe some other things too. With news on Lil Uzi Vert’s shiny forehead and many other important worldly matters, this is another episode you do not want to miss. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0gBvOY9PmfpFcQa8KnhJ2A</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1858</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocking Chairs with Paul Cupo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1ExhLnpK5e4epPWVoIRWnk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week on Shugga Service, we have something new for you, we let a few folks call in and things got interesting fast. If you're in need of some encouragement, do not miss the word of the week as Ian speaks on your better tomorrow. This week’s guest is the undeniably talented Paul Cupo. A designer, a podcaster, and much more, Paul visits and touches base with Ian. Strap in for an education you didn’t know you needed. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ExhLnpK5e4epPWVoIRWnk</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1510</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snacks with Raul Lopez</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/794loetqIkUOywQF1wsdyz?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Welcome back to another episode of Shugga Service. On the agenda today... Are we tweakin'? We also give you the word of the week, hand out roses as always, and most importantly check in with legend and icon Raul Lopez of Luar Zepol. We talk Fashion passion and food. Not an episode to be missed! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">794loetqIkUOywQF1wsdyz</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1984</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Good Time with Dev Hynes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2NOvv5icS7eybHHe3sIbOJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Ian is back once again with more truth, love, and light. All the news, views and a little blues are on the docket before being joined by a very special guest, the *world renowned* Mr. Dev Hynes. And of course we’ll be giving out roses to a living legend as always.Dev Hynes on Spotify Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2NOvv5icS7eybHHe3sIbOJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2506</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carrying with Justine Skye</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/21ugu56s62lvA0WvoixKvR?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>For the first time ever Ian Isiah speaks in a new tone for your soul, giving vocabulary lessons such as today’s, which is carrying and giving views on the news while our world is still upside down. He also sits down with his wonderful friend the talented Ms Justine Skye, before finally giving the benediction.Justine Skye on:Spotify Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21ugu56s62lvA0WvoixKvR</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1831</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Shugga Service with Ian Isiah</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5BDlI23sCtvg6mZwFpPl8G?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Join us this Friday for the premiere of Shugga Service, a weekly freeform talkshow with the hyphenate that is Ian Isiah. The Brooklyn native that has already staked his claim in music and fashion is now hosting his very own Spotify exclusive podcast. Ian will be coming at you every Friday with the news, his views, and conversations with vibrant guests like Justine Skye and Dev Hynes (Blood Orange).Ian Isiah on Instagram. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5BDlI23sCtvg6mZwFpPl8G</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>46</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

