<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>The Bridge: 50 Years of Hip Hop</title>
    <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/1pVq808ida291Q3XfssgaV</link>
    <description>Join Nas and Minya "Miss Info" Oh, for The Bridge - candid conversations with legendary figures who developed the culture and the new generation of voices carrying hip-hop forward. We celebrate hip-hop now, and through its 50th anniversary in 2023. It was written, now it's heard. </description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8ac97d3b1bf3fc52f47a8fbe9c</url>
      <title>The Bridge: 50 Years of Hip Hop</title>
      <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/1pVq808ida291Q3XfssgaV</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:48:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 25: DJ Khaled</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5XKJsU382dBNelh1Mzc7re?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Everybody knows DJ Khaled is inspirational. But what we have here is something bordering on a motivational speech. In this high energy interview, Khaled speaks about his early roots in both New Orleans and Florida, how he has unreleased records with big name artists stashed in the vault, and why it meant so much to him to orchestrate a Nas and Jay-Z collabo. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5XKJsU382dBNelh1Mzc7re</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2315</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 24: Ice-T</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0CfOiWLvwCwX5cpqGba0O7?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>When Ice-T speaks, smart people listen. The streetwise veteran has wisdom to pass on, whether it be in his music or interviews. As you are about to hear, Ice proved to be the master storyteller as he ran down various critical moments in his long career, like why he was scared to do New Jack City or the deeper meaning behind the iconic POWER album cover. He even revealed the rapper who influenced him when writing the theme song to the L.A. gang-banger film, Colors. All that, plus how he survived being canceled over the “Cop Killer” controversy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0CfOiWLvwCwX5cpqGba0O7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2704</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 23: Common</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2S1PMOJgcLKqNeOzdpVALB?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Call it a homecoming. Minya shares her fond memories of traveling back home to Chicago from NYC (where she worked at The Source) and playing an advanced copy of Illmatic for her longtime friend Common, who in turn, used it as inspiration for his career-altering second album, Resurrection. Common also breaks down the unique aspect of Chicago street life, in which gangsters and scholars commonly cross paths. There’s also several fascinating exchanges between Nas and Common in this episode, where they reveal their respective creative process. It’s a rare glimpse into the way artists' minds work. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2S1PMOJgcLKqNeOzdpVALB</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2125</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 22: Lil Jon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3E3FiHQJJ9wJD0ie9kXMyD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The undisputed King of Crunk knows what it’s like to party like there’s no tomorrow. Lil Jon also knows a thing or two about making monster hit records. Go back with the mega producer / world class hype man as he explains why the original beat for Usher’s “Yeah!” ended up on Petey Pablo’s “Freek-A-Leek” and what he liked most about attending Freaknik at its peak. He also discusses what he truly thought about those Dave Chappelle skits and why he picks Las Vegas over Ibiza as the premier destination for getting your groove on. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3E3FiHQJJ9wJD0ie9kXMyD</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2367</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 21: Lee Quiñones</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7JrdDQgX4GgEIXodTKayqY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Graffiti legend LEE stops by to reminisce about the making of Wild Style and the special connection that film has with Nas’ debut, Illmatic. He also paints a vivid picture of the outlaw days of old school New York when hip-hop was just forming and he was considered public enemy #1 by the MTA vandal squad. All this, plus his time spent with Basquiat, being a DJ assistant as a teen in the Lower East Side, and the immeasurable value graffiti art has today. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7JrdDQgX4GgEIXodTKayqY</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2304</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 20: Cypress Hill</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/49fgzz1IScYOCt1lXb5T72?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Cypress Hill broke all the rules. From the beginning, they were staunch advocates for the legalization of marijuana and they bumrushed the scene with the shocking, chaotic sounds of “How I Could Just Kill a Man.” B-Real and Sen Dog had a blast going back down their stoned path to success, detailing step-by-step what happened that infamous night that led to them being banned from SNL, and how they refused to let the industry exploit their Latin heritage. Sen also talked about the physical and mental strain of touring the world while B-Real broke down his high-pitch vocal style and the influence Rammellzee had on him. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49fgzz1IScYOCt1lXb5T72</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2648</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 19: Yo-Yo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5aOZAY0oskXGeqjbLTLlOi?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In the early ‘90s, Yo-Yo emerged on the West Coast as a strong female voice, a tough and witty counterpart to her mentor Ice Cube. In this episode, Yo-Yo is straight up honest about her career ups-and-downs. She tells Nas and Minya how she had to make sure her money was right, her relationship with other women MCs, and her reasoning for doing Reality TV. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5aOZAY0oskXGeqjbLTLlOi</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2228</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 18: Roxanne Shante</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6X0BCUBD59zERSmMmbN4GB?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Nas pays respect to his “big sister” Roxanne Shanté, who encouraged him at an early age to strive for greatness. In this often moving conversation, Shanté shares her incredible story of setting the rap world on fire at only 14 years old by battling anyone and everyone, all day every day. She also breaks down her troubled relationship with her father, getting cheated at the New Music Seminar, and gives an emotional tribute to her dearly departed friend and Juice Crew partner Biz Markie. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6X0BCUBD59zERSmMmbN4GB</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2861</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 17: Teddy Riley</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4PyIJAaEwIJg8qiKX9EESB?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>You can’t fit Teddy Riley into just one category. The producer extraordinaire is not only synonymous with an entire genre of music (New Jack Swing), he’s made countless R&amp;B classics. For those not up on his extensive resume, this episode will be a revelation. The producer extraordinaire (who has deep, deep ties to Harlem) talked with Nas and Minya about his time producing records for Kool Moe Dee, Doug E. Fresh and Big Daddy Kane. He also revealed the unique working relationship he had with the King of Pop, Michael Jackson, as well as going into detail about the Guy and New Edition tour that ended in tragedy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4PyIJAaEwIJg8qiKX9EESB</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2888</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 16: Sha Rock &amp; Grandmaster Caz</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5CpgxVh4EVEiwZe9GMFH8r?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Today, hip-hop is loved the world over. But that wasn’t always the case, as legends MC Sha-Rock (The Funky 4 + 1) and Grandmaster Caz (The Cold Crush Brothers) can attest. Travel back in time with these true believers who knew way back when that hip-hop was not a fad. Hear Sha-Rock speak about her triumphant rise as the first woman MC, while Caz details how hip-hop had to fight for respect during the disco era. And there were more battles to be waged, as Sha-Rock had to sue to get her financial dues and Caz had to finally come to grips with his lyrics being ripped off and used on Sugarhill Gang’s “Rapper’s Delight.” This is an episode rich in hip-hop history and a lesson in lost riches. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5CpgxVh4EVEiwZe9GMFH8r</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2631</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 15: Allen Hughes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1IrDHlFscGoqzArbBRAV7e?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>From an early age, Allen Hughes was bitten by the filmmaking bug. On this episode, we flashback to the accomplished auteur’s early days when he and his twin brother Albert would film local crack dealers and make home video recreations of gangster classics like Scarface. Making the jump to music videos, Hughes credits hip-hop with opening the door to make movies like Menace II Society and Dead Presidents possible. Not one to bite his tongue, Hughes also reveals how his family background inspired American Pimp, and shares with Nas and Miss Info the deep psychological aspect of his upcoming Tupac documentary. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1IrDHlFscGoqzArbBRAV7e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2517</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 14: Jadakiss</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6pHEOIvFfcIc24l82wbKFH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The respected MC (and New Yorker to the core) drops by to discuss how Mary J. Blige had a hand in getting The Lox signed, how the group was able to survive the Shiny Suit era, and why it’s vital to always stay true to the art of rhyming. All told, of course, in that instantly recognizable raspy voice. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6pHEOIvFfcIc24l82wbKFH</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1945</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 13:  Yara Shahidi</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1QZwEa82VeCmf1k06rBUUv?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>It’s a family reunion of sorts as Nas and Miss Info sit down with Yara Shahidi, who also happens to be Nas’ cousin. The accomplished actor (Black-ish) and activist talks about studying hip-hop at Harvard and being around Prince while growing up (her father was his personal photographer). She also speaks on why taking a time-out from social media was important for her. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1QZwEa82VeCmf1k06rBUUv</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2089</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 12: Doug E. Fresh</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1u6ARoIIa8CeEiegBxhEG3?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The World’s Greatest Entertainer takes us back to his formative years growing up in Harlem and how he developed his amazing beatboxing skills. Doug E. also recounts how he met and developed a creative dynamic with Slick Rick, tells a funny story about the time a promoter misspelled his name on a flyer, and for the real hip-hop heads, Nas, Minya and Doug go in depth on the Big Daddy Kane vs. KRS-One Verzuz battle, breaking down each of the legendary MCs' strengths. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1u6ARoIIa8CeEiegBxhEG3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2603</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 11: Bun-B</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1bfWI4pGmrsgoJ3PSO44fC?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Bun-B reminisces about the time he and Pimp C met Nas in the studio back in the '90s and the lasting impression it left on Pimp. Bun also shares memories of the early independent days of UGK, the group's first visit to Harlem, and the duo's collective mind state before they jumped on Jay-Z's "Big Pimpin'," one of the biggest records of the 2000s and beyond. And for anybody who has ever wanted to get some inside game on the ins-and-outs of the music biz, Bun drops some jewels you won't want to miss. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bfWI4pGmrsgoJ3PSO44fC</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2506</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 10: Rev Run</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6y37SzWfFvK22HkodjtN2F?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Legendary MC and TV personality Rev Run has stories for days. In this jam-packed episode, Run recreates in vivid detail the creation of some of Run-DMC’s greatest hits like “Rock Box” and how the group secured an Adidas sneaker deal during a sold-out show at Madison Square Garden. Run also breaks down how Jam Master Jay (RIP) is responsible for the group’s iconic look and addresses the current status of his relationship with rhyme partner and fellow legend DMC. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6y37SzWfFvK22HkodjtN2F</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2921</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 9: MC Lyte</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/43ESysRADTyMwATRTpH9Ao?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Lyte breaks down various parts of her storied career, from making rap classics like “I Cram to Understand U” and “Poor Georgie” to the aftermath of her memorable battle with rival Antoinette. She also gives a lowdown on studio arguments, becoming fast friends with Queen Latifah, and her continued success in the entertainment industry as a voice talent and now film director. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43ESysRADTyMwATRTpH9Ao</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2901</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 8: Fabolous</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5MCHsJthVyAsUkxk8w5Xhk?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In one of his most revealing interviews, Fab opens up about his days growing up in Brooklyn with his booster friends, the influence that Big Daddy Kane had on his style and the importance of the mixtape movement. He also tells Nas and Minya his plans to preserve his most stylish outfits for posterity's sake. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5MCHsJthVyAsUkxk8w5Xhk</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2774</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 7: Jeezy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/53IYpjDWS0GVsPzvnOqcx4?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The Snowman gives a detailed look at how he left the street life behind and became a major force in the rap game. Nas and Miss Info also talk to Jeezy about his initial resistance to Nas’ claim that “Hip-Hop is Dead” before the two collaborated on the anthem “My President.” Jeezy also reveals his feelings about getting uninvited to the White House. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53IYpjDWS0GVsPzvnOqcx4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2468</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 6: DJ Jazzy Jeff</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5KEl0BYgpST0S1rOEutPuu?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jeff paints a picture of the early hip-hop scene in Philly and gives a thrilling recap of how he won the New Music Seminar DJ Battle for World Supremacy. He also talks about how his family influenced his music, why the creative chemistry between him and Will Smith was (and is) so strong, and explains that even though the DJ Jazzy Jeff and Fresh Prince image may have been squeaky clean and embraced by the mainstream, he and Will Smith’s hip-hop upbringing was realer than you think.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5KEl0BYgpST0S1rOEutPuu</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2770</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 5: Juicy-J</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6zVrBxJBMANQvZxDHoR6Ov?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In a very candid conversation, Juicy J recalls the deadly realities of coming up in his Memphis ‘hood, the forces that drove Three 6 Mafia apart, and the turning point that allowed him to avoid self destruction in post-Oscar Los Angeles and return to being creative and clear minded about his future.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6zVrBxJBMANQvZxDHoR6Ov</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2325</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 4: Mary J. Blige</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0keJxyneNVvvTdtaW6NWd8?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Longtime friends Nas and Mary have an intimate conversation that goes deep, touching on everything from dealing with fame to their long-lasting friendship. Mary openly talks about her past relationship struggles and her growth both as an artist and a person. Miss Info also gets Mary to talk about her influential fashion style and what it was like behind the scenes when she and Nas went on tour together. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0keJxyneNVvvTdtaW6NWd8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2758</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 3: Ice Cube</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/65s3ZIucPFzoLLrXE4E1WI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In a conversation filled with mutual respect, Ice Cube is forthcoming about past rap beefs he's been involved in and his struggles getting the next Friday sequel made. But it’s not all serious. Nas, Miss Info and Cube share a laugh over outdated hairstyles and Cube reveals his little known connections to New York. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65s3ZIucPFzoLLrXE4E1WI</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2535</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 2: Cordae</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/78U3oabgGtnFm7sb3RmE9a?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>One can feel the admiration in the room as Cordae gets to speak with one of his childhood rap heroes. (The North Carolina MC even raps lyrics to “I Can” back to Nas.) Cordae also tells Nas and Miss Info the reason he wanted to travel to Africa and explains the competitive mind state he’s in as he completes his next album. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78U3oabgGtnFm7sb3RmE9a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1787</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 1: Jungle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5LKaJAYMAWOsMYXlpi3Clp?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Nas and Miss Info chat with Nas's younger brother, Jungle, about the trio's favorite hip hop groups, Nas's early career and childhood memories of growing up in Queensbridge surrounded by hip-hop stars like Roxanne Shante and MC Shan. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5LKaJAYMAWOsMYXlpi3Clp</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2504</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to The Bridge</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6zyunCpTKzMXmxq70yToRP?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Check out The Bridge: 50 Years of Hip Hop, a new show from Spotify Studios in association with Mass Appeal. Nas and Minya "Miss Info" Oh link with hip-hop's legendary figures and the new generation carrying it forward. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6zyunCpTKzMXmxq70yToRP</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>90</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

