<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>The Two Princes</title>
    <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/70QlYnLX3izDdFhlKfOaeF</link>
    <description>Rupert and Amir are finally getting married and this time nothing is going to stop them. Not the handsome new prince who’s rolled into town and only has eyes for Rupert. Not the mysterious disappearance of half the kingdom’s population. Not even the End of the World. Yes, this time the princes are definitely, absolutely, 100% getting married – even if it’s the last thing they do. Season 3 is out now!The Two Princes stars Noah Galvin, Ari'el Stachel, Jonah Fields, Gideon Glick, Michelle Gomez, Mandi Masden, Wesley Taylor, Samira Wiley, and CJ Wilson. The Two Princes was written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed by Mimi O’Donnell. Music and lyrics by Matt Schatz.Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, associate producer Julie Balefsky. Recorded and mixed by Jonathon Roberts, engineered by Armando Serrano, sound design by Daniel Brunelle. Music direction by Jonathon Roberts. Score by Greg Laswell.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8a078fe01b72f22189840beb73</url>
      <title>The Two Princes</title>
      <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/70QlYnLX3izDdFhlKfOaeF</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:29:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>S3 Ep1: Happily Ever After</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3e9DZJVjbF4uFHds95fDXT?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rupert and Amir are finally getting married. What could go wrong?The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed by Mimi O'Donnell. Music and lyrics by Matt Schatz. With performances by Noah Galvin, Ari’el Stachel, Alfredo Narciso, Gideon Glick, Mandi Masden, Samira Wiley, Wesley Taylor, and Jonah Fields. Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, associate producer Julie Balefsky. Recorded and mixed by Jonathon Roberts, engineered by Armando Serrano, sound design by Daniel Brunelle. Music direction by Jonathon Roberts. Score by Greg Laswell. Theme music and additional scoring by Bobby Lord. The Two Princes is a Spotify original podcast and Gimlet Production.Musicians: Enoch Kim (violin), Greg Laswell (guitar, drums), Peter Leonard (bass), Kevin Sparks (trumpet), Marcus Bagala (drum programming), Matt Schatz (synth)Special thanks to Squadcast. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e9DZJVjbF4uFHds95fDXT</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1494</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S3 Ep2: Something's Coming</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6ymAsRebDNE8WmD6Ynmeam?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Darling flirts. Amir snoops. Percy perseveres.The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed by Mimi O'Donnell. Music and lyrics by Matt Schatz. With performances by Wesley Taylor, Ari’el Stachel, Noah Galvin, Samira Wiley, Jonah Fields, Alfredo Narciso, Gideon Glick, CJ Wilson, and Mandi Masden. Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, associate producer Julie Balefsky. Recorded and mixed by Jonathon Roberts, engineered by Armando Serrano, sound design by Daniel Brunelle. Music direction by Jonathon Roberts. Score by Greg Laswell. Theme music by Bobby Lord. The Two Princes is a Spotify original podcast and Gimlet Production.Musicians: Enoch Kim (violin), Greg Laswell (guitar), Peter Leonard (bass), Matt Schatz (guitar), Kevin Sparks (trumpet)Special thanks to Squadcast. Additional voices: Matthew Nelson, Jonathon Roberts Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ymAsRebDNE8WmD6Ynmeam</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1270</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S3 Ep3: Adventures in Babysitting </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7uPl9vBfJBgja0aZkGDGfX?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>There’s a goat in the tub and doom on the horizon.The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed by Mimi O'Donnell. Music and lyrics by Matt Schatz. With performances by Ari’el Stachel, Jonah Fields, Noah Galvin, Alfredo Narciso, Wesley Taylor, CJ Wilson, Mandi Masden, Gideon Glick, and Samira WileyExecutive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, associate producer Julie Balefsky. Recorded and mixed by Jonathon Roberts, engineered by Armando Serrano, sound design by Daniel Brunelle. Music direction by Jonathon Roberts. Score by Greg Laswell. Theme music by Bobby Lord. The Two Princes is a Spotify original podcast and Gimlet Production.Musicians: Marcus Bagala (drum programming), Enoch Kim (violin), Greg Laswell (guitar, drums), Peter Leonard (bass), Jonathon Roberts (piano), Matt Schatz (guitar, ukulele, synths), Kevin Sparks (trumpet)Additional voices: Jonathon Roberts, Armando SerranoSpecial thanks to Squadcast.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7uPl9vBfJBgja0aZkGDGfX</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1348</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S3 Ep4: The Enemy Within </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1sf1uZu1jvDtxXGFheGTp5?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Joan is two minutes too late.The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed by Mimi O'Donnell. Music and lyrics by Matt Schatz. With performances by Noah Galvin, Jonah Fields, Ari’el Stachel, Alfredo Narciso, Samira Wiley, Mandi Masden, and Wesley Taylor.Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, associate producer Julie Balefsky. Recorded and mixed by Jonathon Roberts, engineered by Armando Serrano, sound design and additional scoring by Daniel Brunelle. Music direction by Jonathon Roberts. Score by Greg Laswell. Theme music by Bobby Lord. The Two Princes is a Spotify original podcast and Gimlet Production.Musicians: Enoch Kim (violin), Greg Laswell (guitar, drums), Peter Leonard (bass), Matt Schatz (guitar, accordion), Kevin Sparks (trumpet)Special thanks to Squadcast.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1sf1uZu1jvDtxXGFheGTp5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1017</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S3 Ep5: Love is a Battlefield</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4xMBaYgv1vqBCyThcJDeKf?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The Heartland falls.The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed by Mimi O'Donnell. Music and lyrics by Matt Schatz. With performances by CJ Wilson, Ari’el Stachel, Noah Galvin, Samira Wiley, and Alfredo Narciso.Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, associate producer Julie Balefsky. Recorded and mixed by Jonathon Roberts, engineered by Armando Serrano, sound design by Daniel Brunelle. Music direction by Jonathon Roberts. Score by Greg Laswell. Theme music by Bobby Lord. The Two Princes is a Spotify original podcast and Gimlet Production.Musicians: Enoch Kim (violin), Greg Laswell (guitar, drums), Peter Leonard (bass), Jonathon Roberts (piano), Kevin Sparks (trumpet)Special thanks to Squadcast.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4xMBaYgv1vqBCyThcJDeKf</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>865</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S3 Ep6: The Three Princes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5NdwC5HoGLDQYgUKM5U1e1?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Amir has questions. Darling has answers. Rupert has an impossible choice.The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed by Mimi O'Donnell. Music and lyrics by Matt Schatz. With performances by Wesley Taylor, Ari’el Stachel, Noah Galvin, and CJ Wilson. Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, associate producer Julie Balefsky. Recorded and mixed by Jonathon Roberts, engineered by Armando Serrano, sound design by Daniel Brunelle. Music direction by Jonathon Roberts. Score by Greg Laswell. Theme music by Bobby Lord. The Two Princes is a Spotify original podcast and Gimlet Production.Musicians: Jonathon Roberts (piano), Matt Schatz (synth), Kevin Sparks (trumpet)Special thanks to Squadcast.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5NdwC5HoGLDQYgUKM5U1e1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1040</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S3 Ep7: The Song of the Heartland</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0YqP7WcCg7waF9FXYkdmtB?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Everything ends. Except love.The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed by Mimi O'Donnell. Music and lyrics by Matt Schatz. With performances by CJ Wilson, Noah Galvin, Ari’el Stachel, Samira Wiley, Gideon Glick, Mandi Masden, Alfredo Narciso, Jonah Fields, Wesley Taylor, and Michelle Gomez.Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, associate producer Julie Balefsky. Recorded and mixed by Jonathon Roberts, engineered by Armando Serrano, sound design by Daniel Brunelle. Music direction by Jonathon Roberts. Score by Greg Laswell. Theme music by Bobby Lord. The Two Princes is a Spotify original podcast and Gimlet Production.Musicians: Julie Balefsky (voice), Enoch Kim (violin), Greg Laswell (guitar, drums), Peter Leonard (bass), Jonathon Roberts (piano, additional vocals, vocal arranging), Kevin Sparks (trumpet)Special thanks to Squadcast.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0YqP7WcCg7waF9FXYkdmtB</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1399</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S2 Ep1: How to Ruin a Royal Wedding</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1g03t3b6AucAUSeilsRubJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rupert and Amir can’t wait to get married. So why is everything falling apart?The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed Mimi O'Donnell. With performances by Samira Wiley, Mandi Masden, Cynthia Erivo, Noah Galvin, Ari’el Stachel, Jonathon Roberts, Sue O’Donnell, Alfredo Narciso, and Gideon Glick. Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, associate producer MR Daniel. Recorded, engineered, sound designed, and mixed by Jonathon Roberts. Additional mixing by Dan Brunelle and Armando Serrano. Score by Greg Laswell. The Two Princes is a production of Gimlet Media.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1g03t3b6AucAUSeilsRubJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>981</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S2 Ep2: The Woman of the Wolves</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/17QLGi7gM9HrprH8Ypuhpc?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>How do you solve a problem like Chad?The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed Mimi O'Donnell. With performances by Noah Galvin, Cynthia Erivo, Ari’el Stachel, Mandi Masden, Samira Wiley, Alfredo Narciso, and Tonya Pinkins. Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, associate producer MR Daniel. Recorded, engineered, sound designed, and mixed by Jonathon Roberts. Additional mixing by Dan Brunelle and Armando Serrano. Score by Greg Laswell. Additional score by Bobby Lord and Jonathon Roberts. The Two Princes is a production of Gimlet Media.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17QLGi7gM9HrprH8Ypuhpc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>922</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S2 Ep3: The Play's the Thing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5stnANKxT4AMMOZcgviYOq?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rupert needs a unicorn. Amir needs a break. Barabbas needs the facilities.The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed Mimi O'Donnell. With performances by Ari’el Stachel, Noah Galvin, Kathryn Kates, Alfredo Narciso, Richard Kind, Mandi Masden, and Jonah Fields. Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, associate producer MR Daniel. Recorded, engineered, sound designed, and mixed by Jonathon Roberts. Additional mixing by Dan Brunelle and Armando Serrano. Score by Greg Laswell. Additional score by Bobby Lord and Jonathon Roberts. The Two Princes is a production of Gimlet Media.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5stnANKxT4AMMOZcgviYOq</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1134</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S2 Ep4: The Song of the Sirens</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/67mN5eFJWCIv8pXmpvt4F3?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Good news: Amir is smitten. Bad news: it’s not with Rupert.The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed Mimi O'Donnell. With performances by Ari’el Stachel, Noah Galvin, Ali Stroker, and Gideon Glick. Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, associate producer MR Daniel. Recorded, engineered, sound designed, and mixed by Jonathon Roberts. Additional mixing by Dan Brunelle and Armando Serrano. Score by Greg Laswell. Additional score by Bobby Lord and Jonathon Roberts. Original song “Siren Song” by Matthew Boll and Kevin Christopher Snipes. The Two Princes is a production of Gimlet Media.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67mN5eFJWCIv8pXmpvt4F3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>993</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S2 Ep5: The Seventh Riddle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/35LYTGzlmZfPpihj81W5CX?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Snakes! Why did it have to be snakes?The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed Mimi O'Donnell. With performances by Noah Galvin, Ari’el Stachel, Michael Braun, Jonathon Roberts, and Samira Wiley. Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, associate producer MR Daniel. Recorded, engineered, sound designed, and mixed by Jonathon Roberts. Additional mixing by Dan Brunelle and Armando Serrano. Score by Greg Laswell.  Additional score by Bobby Lord and Jonathon Roberts. The Two Princes is a production of Gimlet Media. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35LYTGzlmZfPpihj81W5CX</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>958</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S2 Ep6: Holding Out for a Hero</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/701C3MtXoISlSFfMbenJqF?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>A song. A spell. A subterfuge.The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed Mimi O'Donnell. With performances by Alfredo Narciso, Ari’el Stachel, Richard Kind, Mandi Masden, Noah Galvin, Cynthia Erivo, Gideon Glick, and Tonya Pinkins. Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, associate producer MR Daniel. Recorded, engineered, sound designed, and mixed by Jonathon Roberts. Additional mixing by Dan Brunelle and Armando Serrano. Score by Greg Laswell. Additional score by Bobby Lord and Jonathon Roberts. Original song “The Easy Life” by Bobby Lord and Kevin Christopher Snipes. The Two Princes is a production of Gimlet Media.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">701C3MtXoISlSFfMbenJqF</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1011</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S2 Ep7: Lost and Found</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3VSyl1MHah8OthIgygOYtz?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The fate of the Heartland hangs in the balance. The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed Mimi O'Donnell. With performances by Cynthia Erivo, Noah Galvin, Gideon Glick, Ari’el Stachel, Mandi Masden, Tonya Pinkins, and Samira Wiley. Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, associate producer MR Daniel. Recorded, engineered, and mixed by Jonathon Roberts. Sound design by Dan Brunelle. Additional engineering by Armando Serrano. Score by Greg Laswell. Additional score by Bobby Lord and Jonathon Roberts. The Two Princes is a production of Gimlet Media.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3VSyl1MHah8OthIgygOYtz</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>917</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S1 Ep1: Once Upon a Time</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5NirEt8j6ekIBxkteXio0v?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rupert wants answers. Lavinia wants a wedding. The Forest wants... something. The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed by Mimi O'Donnell. Kelly AuCoin- Knight, Alfredo Narciso- Lord Chamberlain , Matthew Rhys- Sir Percy, Christine Baranski- Queen Lavinia, Noah Galvin- Prince Rupert, Wigs Pastore- Fitzroy, Sean Pertwee- Mysterious Voice, and Mandi Masden- Cecily. Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, producer Annamaria Sofillas, associate producer MR Daniel. Edited and mixed by Matthew Boll, sound design by Daniel Brunelle, score by Greg Laswell and Bobby Lord. The Two Princes is a production of Gimlet Media. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5NirEt8j6ekIBxkteXio0v</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1504</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S1 Ep2: Prince and Thief</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5SVUuv151DEf3K1waAxCzb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rupert makes a friend. Or an enemy. He’s not quite sure. The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed by Mimi O'Donnell. Noah Galvin- Prince Rupert, Laura Benanti- Flora, and Ari'el Stachel- Prince Amir. Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, producer Annamaria Sofillas, associate producer MR Daniel. Edited and mixed by Matthew Boll, sound design by Daniel Brunelle, score by Greg Laswell and Bobby Lord. The Two Princes is a production of Gimlet Media.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5SVUuv151DEf3K1waAxCzb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1069</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S1 Ep3: Cracking Up and Crashing Down</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3QxMbyZRZSJx6uPyiNMCsJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rupert and Amir are in the dark. A guest drops in on Lavinia. Literally. The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed by Mimi O'Donnell. Ari'el Stachel- Prince Amir, Noah Galvin- Prince Rupert, Alfredo Narciso- Lord Chamberlain, Christine Baranski- Queen Lavinia, Matthew Rhys- Sir Percy, and Shohreh Aghdashloo- Queen Atossa. Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, producer Annamaria Sofillas, associate producer MR Daniel. Edited and mixed by Matthew Boll, sound design by Daniel Brunelle, score by Greg Laswell and Bobby Lord. The Two Princes is a production of Gimlet Media. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3QxMbyZRZSJx6uPyiNMCsJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1137</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S1 Ep4: Life Upon the Wicked Stage</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/01H2zsq0DPgqbLTgFmtbL4?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rupert and Amir are a captive audience. The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed by Mimi O'Donnell. Shohreh Aghdashloo- Queen Atossa, Christine Baranski- Queen Lavinia, Alfredo Narciso- Barabbas, Noah Galvin- Prince Rupert, Ari'el Stachel- Prince Amir, Richard Kind- Cedric, and Mandi Masden- Crazy Tooth. Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, producer Annamaria Sofillas, associate producer MR Daniel. Edited and mixed by Matthew Boll, sound design by Daniel Brunelle, score by Greg Laswell and Bobby Lord. The Two Princes is a production of Gimlet Media Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01H2zsq0DPgqbLTgFmtbL4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1287</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S1 Ep5: That Sinking Feeling</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2e9YHz7N1GynMIR34NYkXy?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rupert needs some air. Amir needs a bath. Lavinia needs for a few good men. The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed by Mimi O'Donnell. Christine Baranski- Queen Lavinia, Alfredo Narciso- Lord Chamberlain, Shohreh Aghdashloo- Queen Atossa, Matthew Rhys- Sir Percy, Samira Wiley- Joan, Ari'el Stachel- Prince Amir, Noah Galvin- Prince Rupert, CJ Wilson- Brutus, and Mandi Masden- Cecily. Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, producer Annamaria Sofillas, associate producer MR Daniel. Edited and mixed by Matthew Boll, sound design by Daniel Brunelle, score by Greg Laswell and Bobby Lord. The Two Princes is a production of Gimlet Media Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e9YHz7N1GynMIR34NYkXy</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1370</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S1 Ep6: The Battle of the Phoenix</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5pvtMgjwILjGB4YUe4rMBB?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Three tough ladies. Two brokenhearted princes. One giant spider. The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed by Mimi O'Donnell. Noah Galvin- Prince Rupert, Ari'el Stachel- Prince Amir, Christine Baranski- Queen Lavinia, Shohreh Aghdashloo- Queen Atossa, Samira Wiley- Joan, Daphne Rubin-Vega- Arachne, Mandi Masden- Cecily, Sean Pertwee- King of the West, and Omar Metwally- King of the East. Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, producer Annamaria Sofillas, associate producer MR Daniel. Edited and mixed by Matthew Boll, sound design by Daniel Brunelle, score by Greg Laswell and Bobby Lord. The Two Princes is a production of Gimlet Media Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5pvtMgjwILjGB4YUe4rMBB</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1339</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S1 Ep7: The Hollow of the Kings</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6CYFylDD6Wp4umpJGlIOj6?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Rupert and Amir learn the truth. They wish they hadn’t. The Two Princes was created and written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed by Mimi O'Donnell. Noah Galvin- Prince Rupert, Ari'el Stachel- Prince Amir, Sean Pertwee- King of the West, Omar Metwally- King of the East, Shohreh Aghdashloo- Queen Atossa, Christine Baranski- Queen Lavinia, and Samira Wiley- Joan. Executive producer Mimi O'Donnell, senior producer Katie Pastore, producer Annamaria Sofillas, associate producer MR Daniel. Edited and mixed by Matthew Boll, sound design by Daniel Brunelle, score by Greg Laswell and Bobby Lord. The Two Princes is a production of Gimlet Media Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6CYFylDD6Wp4umpJGlIOj6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1402</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing: The Two Princes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0oL0zEP27ED4eeq73DV3K3?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>When Prince Rupert sets out to break the mysterious curse that’s destroying his kingdom, he’s ready to face whatever dastardly villain or vile monster stands in his way. What he isn’t prepared for are the bewildering new emotions he feels when he meets the handsome Amir, a rival prince on a quest to save his own realm. Forced to team up, the two princes soon discover that the only thing more difficult than saving their kingdoms is following their hearts. The Two Princes stars Noah Galvin (Booksmart, Dear Evan Hansen), Ari’el Stachel (The Band’s Visit), Christine Baranski (The Good Wife, The Good Fight), Shohreh Aghdashloo (House of Sand and Fog, The Expanse), Matthew Rhys (The Americans), Samira Wiley (Orange Is the New Black, The Handmaid’s Tale). The Two Princes was written by Kevin Christopher Snipes and directed by Mimi O’Donnell. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0oL0zEP27ED4eeq73DV3K3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>126</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

