<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>TMI with Cam &amp; Chloe</title>
    <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/1DXRz61ALFZzxZuMNhVhdq</link>
    <description>No topic is off limits when it comes to Cam and Chloe — the Geordie couple weighing-in on all the conversations and questions you might share with your mates.. As well as all the ones you’re too embarrassed to address, too. From their own hot takes on sex and relationships to the burning questions boys and girls are afraid to ask each other, for Cam and Chloe nothing is Too Much Information.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8ac1fae01632c3b9ba614cea0c</url>
      <title>TMI with Cam &amp; Chloe</title>
      <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/1DXRz61ALFZzxZuMNhVhdq</link>
    </image>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:50:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>4 - Our Holiday From Hell..</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0WYJvN8uSQeIOMPVq920X0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Welcome to the worst 24 hours of our lives.. but also the best? Get comfortable as we're taking you on the journey of our holiday from hell. From what started as a cute idea for our first holiday quickly turned into 24 hours we will never forget... for all the wrong reasons.  Follow our Instagram @tmicamchloe to give your opinions on what is our most insane episode yet :) This content contains adult subject matter and is intended for adult consumption only.  It may not be suitable for all audiences so your discretion is advised</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0WYJvN8uSQeIOMPVq920X0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2208</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 - Do Girls Fake Orgasms?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/68qTMJfleXdlCUnTfEyct6?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Chloe makes Cam squirm as we talk reveal the true answer; Do all girls fake orgasms? Cam takes Chloe by surprise as we reveal the answer to 'Do boys fake orgasms'. Furthermore, we dive deep into why girls may choose to fake an orgasms, how boys can tell if girls are faking it and taking the mick out of our own experiences when it comes to finishing. With us two.. nothing it TMI.  This content contains adult subject matter and is intended for adult consumption only.  It may not be suitable for all audiences so your discretion is advised</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68qTMJfleXdlCUnTfEyct6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1680</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 - Rocket Ship Dick</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0LYkNM41MPEI9X2IfImQBx?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>It's here. ROCKET SHIP DICK has landed. It's time for us talk about why guys can't last long in the bedroom. Do girls take it as a compliment if guys finish quickly? Do boys feel embarrassed when we finish to quick and so many other questions regarding ROCKET SHIP DICK. We also go into the secret tactics guys use to last longer in the bedroom and the reason why most girls can't finish. Watch now as we unpack this topic, unfiltered and where nothing is TMI.. Follow our Instagram @camkirkham @chloe_vardy to give your takes on the questions in this episode. This content contains adult subject matter and is intended for adult consumption only.  It may not be suitable for all audiences so your discretion is advised</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0LYkNM41MPEI9X2IfImQBx</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1455</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 - The first time we 'Did It'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1UnGwHmxZXG4nXRcJxrTp5?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>EPISODE 1 IS HERE!! It's time for us to expose too much of our personal lives... How Chloe slid into Cam's DMs; why Cam unfollowed Chloe; what did we do on our first date? Was it a disaster? And most importantly.. did we do it on the first date? Plus, Cam exposes a story that should've been kept a secret. We also dive into the Do's and Don'ts of first dates: should you go for a poo on a first date or should you hold it in? Should you sleep together on the first date? Does sleeping together effect what you think of the other person? With Cam and Chloe NOTHING is TMI. Follow us on Instagram @camkirkham @chloe_vardy to give us your thoughts on the questions! This content contains adult subject matter and is intended for adult consumption only.  It may not be suitable for all audiences so your discretion is advised. </p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1UnGwHmxZXG4nXRcJxrTp5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2356</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to TMI babyyyy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1jntBlenATMAs6DFZS6EVn?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>It's finally here!! Welcome to TMI with Cam and Chloe — an open and raw conversation where we address the questions you’re too embarrassed to talk about. From our own hot takes on sex and relationships to the burning questions boys and girls are afraid to ask each other, we've got you covered!! Got a question for us? Send them to @camkirkham @chloe_vardy on instagram. New episodes every Tuesday starting March 29th.</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1jntBlenATMAs6DFZS6EVn</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>62</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

