<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Unlocking Us with Brené Brown</title>
    <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/4P86ZzHf7EOlRG7do9LkKZ</link>
    <description>I’ve spent over 20 years studying the emotions and experiences that bring meaning and purpose to our lives, and if there’s one thing I’ve learned it’s this: We are hardwired for connection, and connecting requires courage, vulnerability, and conversation. I want this to be a podcast that’s real, unpolished, honest, and reflects both the magic and the messiness of what it means to be human. Episodes will include conversations with the people who are teaching me, challenging me, confusing me, or maybe even ticking me off a little. I'll also have direct conversations with you about what I’m learning from new research, and we'll do some episodes dedicated to answering your questions. We don’t have to do life alone. We were never meant to. Unlocking Us is a Spotify Original from Parcast.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8af234909e69a68d92ca0af6ca</url>
      <title>Unlocking Us with Brené Brown</title>
      <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/4P86ZzHf7EOlRG7do9LkKZ</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:18:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Father Richard Rohr on Spirituality, Certitude, and Infinite Love, Part 1 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/60j9urMuyE7CB6pSw76mOs?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Anyone who knows me or my work knows the immeasurable influence Father Richard Rohr has had on my life. Rohr is a Franciscan friar and ecumenical teacher, and his words live on Post-it notes all around my house; his numerous books are tattered and torn, as I’ve returned to them time and again, especially in the past couple years. In this magical two-part conversation, Father Richard graciously expands on just a few of the quotes that have turned my world upside down, sharing his thoughts on what it means to be humbled by the mysteries of faith; how we often misinterpret God as a dictator, not a lover; and how we’re ill-equipped to grasp the infinite nature of God and his love. This truly unforgettable conversation left me speechless—and filled me to the brim with love and connection. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60j9urMuyE7CB6pSw76mOs</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1894</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Scott Sonenshein on Why We’ll Never Be the Same Again (and Why It’s Time to Talk About It)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7pijX0aVjxpLqcEG4RKIyH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This is one of the most important conversations that we’ve ever had on the Dare to Lead podcast, so we also wanted to have it on Unlocking Us. I’m talking with Scott Sonenshein, a researcher, organizational psychologist, and New York Times best-selling author, about the pandemic, the racial reckoning, and work—specifically, what it means for people going to the office for the first time, or staying hybrid, or working from home. We will never be the same again after what we’ve experienced over the past couple of years, and it’s time we talk about how we’re going to rebuild moving forward. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7pijX0aVjxpLqcEG4RKIyH</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3271</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Emmanuel Acho on Being Illogical</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0d1P8b7i5VoP5fBDnBtmFR?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>I’m talking again with my friend Emmanuel Acho about his new book, Illogical: Saying Yes to a Life Without Limits. True to form, Emmanuel shows up with pure energy and thought-provoking opinions—which may seem illogical, but actually make so much sense. He also shares some real wisdom around how to handle naysayers and critics while also staying open, being receptive, and taking care of ourselves in the process. It’s a really meaningful conversation, we have a ton of fun, and I‘m really glad you’re here for it. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d1P8b7i5VoP5fBDnBtmFR</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3759</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Susan Cain on How Sorrow and Longing Make Us Whole, Part 2 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2le8r7Vexy3hu5RMFQa8Mw?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Welcome to part two of my conversation with Susan Cain, the best-selling author of Quiet, about her new revolutionary book, Bittersweet: How Sorrow and Longing Make Us Whole, which comes out on April 5. This book is giving me life right now. I feel deeply seen in this needed counterbalance to our society’s push for constant positivity. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2le8r7Vexy3hu5RMFQa8Mw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2307</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Susan Cain on How Sorrow and Longing Make Us Whole, Part 1 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2y2vlxXQpE7pQcNl12nxId?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This conversation is a bittersweet breath of fresh air for me. It’s the first of two episodes with Susan Cain, the best-selling author of Quiet, about her new revolutionary book, Bittersweet: How Sorrow and Longing Make Us Whole. This is such an important book and a needed counterbalance to our society’s toxic push for constant positivity. It gives a high five to those of us who know that melancholy is our secret strength, and it gives the rest of us permission to lean into our bittersweet feelings, which actually make us more hopeful and more whole. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2y2vlxXQpE7pQcNl12nxId</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2876</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Karen Walrond on Accessing Joy and Finding Connection in the Midst of Struggle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0UtfB3KfyySJneMV1onqcU?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I’m sitting across from my friend Karen Walrond and she’s helping me access joy. You may remember Karen from a two-part podcast we did last year on her book The Lightmaker's Manifesto, which is all about working for change without losing your joy. And I literally just called her and said, “Will you be on the podcast this week, because I’m in such deep struggle and I can’t access any joy? I feel guilty if I’m happy about something because the world is such a shit show right now and people are in so much pain.” This conversation was incredibly healing for me. If you’re struggling with how to be fully connected in your life and feel joy and acknowledge beauty and also fight for the things that we need to fight for right now, this will be a great podcast for you. It was a game changer for me. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0UtfB3KfyySJneMV1onqcU</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2140</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Kara Swisher and Scott Galloway on Pivot, Reverence, and What’s Behind Big Tech</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/59l0CtD9yEQVnyIWCoeLe0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>I’m talking with tech journalist Kara Swisher and NYU professor Scott Galloway, co-hosts of the podcast Pivot, a weekly discussion on the latest news as it relates to the worlds of business and tech. I start to do some word association with them, but we quickly go deep and take a hard, illuminating look at Big Tech. This is a great conversation for those of us who regularly engage with tech platforms but maybe who don’t understand their motivations, what they’re up to next, and the myriad ways they shape our lives and democracies. Let’s dig in. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59l0CtD9yEQVnyIWCoeLe0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4254</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Dr. Shawn Ginwright on The Four Pivots: Reimagining Justice, Reimagining Ourselves</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/27qUt2DfcLROhzFZaO2gqG?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In his brave new book, The Four Pivots: Reimagining Justice, Reimagining Ourselves, Shawn Ginwright asks a simple but profound question, “Can we heal the world without healing ourselves?” I’ve always believed the answer is no, but I’ve never seen anyone propose a more daring solution than what’s in this book and conversation. There is so much wisdom in these four pivots. This conversation opened my heart and my mind. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27qUt2DfcLROhzFZaO2gqG</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3948</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Jason Reynolds on Masterpieces and Messes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4mXjiV83xJzAePd5CP2f5k?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I’m talking with Jason Reynolds, #1 New York Times best-selling author of more than a dozen books for young people, about where he draws inspiration for his characters, his role as the National Ambassador for Young People’s Literature, and his latest book, Ain’t Burned All the Bright. I’m deeply inspired by Jason’s art and craft—I loved every minute of this conversation. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4mXjiV83xJzAePd5CP2f5k</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4697</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené on Places We Go When the Heart Is Open from Atlas of the Heart</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0eiwHq9JQcifBt88FYSBGt?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We're celebrating the audiobook release of Atlas of the Heart with a bonus Unlocking Us episode! The excerpt in this episode is from chapter 10, titled "Places We Go When the Heart Is Open." We're talking about love, lovelessness, and heartbreak. I'm excited to give you a first listen here, and I'm grateful that we're learning and working to reconnect with ourselves and with each other, together.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0eiwHq9JQcifBt88FYSBGt</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2311</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Ben Wizner on Free Speech, Misinformation, and the Case for Nuance</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2Aum4I0vVWLlnKpE0VWdzW?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>I was looking for some certainty around the tough issues of censorship and misinformation - legal definitions, rules, and clear lines - so I called Ben Wizner, ACLU lawyer and the director of its Speech, Privacy, and Technology Project. I hoped we’d have a Free Speech 101 conversation with tidy resolutions and a clear path forward. But what I suspected, and Ben confirmed, is that the law gives us very few answers to the hardest questions that we have. So, in this episode, the two of us grapple with issues of balance and boundaries, unpacking the harms that speech can cause, and the harms that censorship can cause. I'm glad that we had over an hour to talk, because as tempting as it is to approach issues like this with firm certainty or with 140 characters, it’s much more important to unpack the nuances and unlock the opportunity for growth and learning. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2Aum4I0vVWLlnKpE0VWdzW</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4371</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené and Barrett on Living Into Our Values</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4NahW06ohMyybdVDx9WFkA?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We’re back, and we are starting the year with a deep dive into values. I’m not a fan of resolutions, but I absolutely believe in the power of resetting. I can’t think of a more powerful way to double down on ourselves than getting clear on our values and the behaviors that support them—and the shit that gets in the way. Join us as Barrett and I talk through a values exercise PDF that we made for you to do your own values work. Of all the work we do with leaders and teams, this is probably the biggest game changer. Let’s go! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4NahW06ohMyybdVDx9WFkA</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2907</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with James Clear on Atomic Habits, Part 2 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7toucYjIgxIePLEVE9oDhO?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>It’s Part 2 of our two-episode crossover from our other podcast, Dare to Lead, featuring James Clear author of Atomic Habits, which has sold more than 5 million copies worldwide and has been translated into more than 50 languages. In part 1, we talked about building systems to create habits, and in this episode, we talk about how and why habits are atomic and how to build a habit or break a habit. We also look at our environments and how we can tweak them to support the habits we want to have, and then dive in and talk about organization habits and how we create habits in a team and in organizations. I took multiple pages of notes on this memorable conversation on forming habits that last. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7toucYjIgxIePLEVE9oDhO</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3046</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with James Clear on Atomic Habits, Part 1 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4FtUEweiSDXfHZCAPQhWEA?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Unlocking Us is going to Dare to Lead! We are kicking off 2022 with a two-episode crossover from our other podcast, Dare to Lead, featuring James Clear author of Atomic Habits, which has sold more than 5 million copies worldwide and has been translated into more than 50 languages. We are surrounded with resolutions and change right now, and James has some very helpful advice—and some really interesting research—on what works and what doesn't as we try to make new habits and break old ones. In part 1 of our series, we talk specifically about developing identity-based habits and how we can become the architects of those habits, not the victims of them. We also talk about the intersection of his work and mine, the collective stories we make up, and how our mindsets and our systems can set us up for success. It was so meaningful to finally meet James, to hear his story, and to take in his insights into how he developed such a deep understanding of the importance of consistency over intensity when it comes to forming habits that last. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4FtUEweiSDXfHZCAPQhWEA</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2768</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené, Ashley, and Barrett on Atlas of the Heart: A Sisters Book Club, Part 3 of 3</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7B6xreJFmRKeH3TCKmUXMb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We asked for your Atlas of the Heart questions and, man, did you deliver. More than 1,500 questions poured in. So in this final episode of our Sisters Book Club, Brené, Ashley, and Barrett answered as many questions as they could, tackling; how emotional literacy affects self-awareness, how family patterns affect emotions, and how emotionally intense moments affect our decision making. They also discuss the powerful connections between art and emotions, as well as how parents can bring this work to their teenagers. Thank you so much for reading. And for listening. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7B6xreJFmRKeH3TCKmUXMb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2440</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené, Ashley, and Barrett on Atlas of the Heart: A Sisters Book Club, Part 2 of 3</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3sOxnPtArSDjiEwHGevEKJ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>It's Part 2 of the three-part Sisters Book Club series, where Ashley and Barrett turn the tables on Brené and interview her about her new book Atlas of the Heart: Mapping Meaningful Connection and the Language of the Human Experience. In this episode, the sisters dive into more specific findings on some of the 87 emotions covered in the book. They also ask Brené the podcast Rapid-Fire questions—including her top 5 songs—plus, they included some brand-new Rapid-Fire questions she doesn't expect. Join us as they talk about how powerful it is to have vocabulary that's as expansive as our experiences. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3sOxnPtArSDjiEwHGevEKJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3389</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené, Ashley, and Barrett on Atlas of the Heart: A Sisters Book Club, Part 1 of 3</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3eyj6AUWzB1YgON2QVLMY5?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this first episode of a three-part Sisters Book Club series, Ashley and Barrett turn the tables on Brené and interview her about her new book, Atlas of the Heart: Mapping Meaningful Connection and the Language of the Human Experience. They ask all the questions we want to know, and they pull no punches—starting with stories about childhood superpowers, to matters of biology, biography, behavior, and backstory in the context of emotions and the book itself. They also talk about how Atlas is broken up into three sections, how the data was collected and analyzed to present the 87 emotions covered, and how powerful it is to have vocabulary that's as expansive as our experiences. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3eyj6AUWzB1YgON2QVLMY5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3455</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené on the Anatomy of Trust</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5huJRBajjwvJKHnlgokU3s?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I wanted to share with you a talk that I did at UCLA’s Royce Hall for Oprah’s SuperSoul sessions where I uncovered the fundamentals of trust. What is trust? The data says there are seven parts of trust, and we organize these into the acronym BRAVING trust. We talk about these seven elements and how they are reliable for exploring the integrity of our interactions with others as well as for engaging with our own self-trust. Breaking down the anatomy of trust into specific behaviors allows us to more clearly identify and address breaches of trust. I love the BRAVING checklist because it reminds me that trusting myself or other people is a vulnerable and courageous process. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5huJRBajjwvJKHnlgokU3s</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2042</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Lukas and Willie Nelson on Family, Love, and Music</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6OzTzCzwMdvBfLAbT0UHZu?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I’m talking with Lukas and Willie Nelson about their new album The Willie Nelson Family, a collection of country gospel-flavored songs performed by the Nelson Family Band and recorded at Willie’s Pedernales Studios—where we recorded this podcast—just outside of Austin. We talk about faith and family, music as church, and love—and how it’s really all tied together. We also talk about what brings us together, what keeps us apart, and what holds us back. We get some Nelson family advice—including their three family rules. And we end the episode with a surprise treat you’ll be singing all week. It was a special day and a treasured conversation. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6OzTzCzwMdvBfLAbT0UHZu</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2403</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Karen Walrond on The Lightmaker’s Manifesto, Part 2 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/164UzwJJPpFiG2BG9PMBZj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>It’s part 2 of our two-part series with Karen Walrond, writer, activist, and longtime friend. We are talking about her new book, The Lightmaker’s Manifesto: How to Work for Change without Losing Your Joy. In part 1, we talked about activism and how it shows up in our daily lives. And in this episode, we talk about the connection between activism and spirituality. We talk about listening to the whispers that are calling us and the self-inquiry strategies that help us know what we’re supposed to be doing. We also dig in on performative activism and outrage, as well as the realities of burnout and how joy helps curb some of that. It’s an important conversation—and one we need to be having right now. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">164UzwJJPpFiG2BG9PMBZj</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2513</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Karen Walrond on The Lightmaker’s Manifesto, Part 1 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6uhVKTZPyPD0fOMv9qvHtx?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week I’m talking to Karen Walrond, writer, activist, and longtime friend of mine about her new book, The Lightmaker’s Manifesto: How to Work for Change without Losing Your Joy. This is the right book for the right time. Activism is such a big and often intimidating concept, and Karen breaks it down into small, intentional, and integrated acts that create a joyful life. We talk about how we met and how we define activism, and we share some really personal experiences we each had after Hurricane Harvey that shaped how we see the intersection of activism and joy. So enjoy this first of two episodes on life, light, and activism and how those three things are completely interconnected. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6uhVKTZPyPD0fOMv9qvHtx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3463</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Jake Wesley Rogers on Songwriting, Storytelling, and Dropping Keys</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3J6Z97RuSOhGGwgoU0onR2?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this deeply special episode, I’m talking with singer-songwriter, activist, and artist Jake Wesley Rogers, whom I discovered on TikTok. It was love at first listen—and I mean, I fell madly, truly, deeply in love with him and his art, as well as how it made me feel, how it made me dance, and how it made me sing. He takes me to church. His songs are relatable and universal, he is pure light and love, and I cannot wait for you to hear this conversation. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3J6Z97RuSOhGGwgoU0onR2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3778</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Brett Goldstein Live at ACL Fest on Comedy, Creativity, and Roy Kent</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6zuvvBFj02eTVvcfJsEeBT?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>OY! It's our first LIVE Unlocking Us, recorded at ACL Fest in Austin, Texas. I asked Brett Goldstein—writer, comedian, producer, and Emmy Award-winning actor—to join me onstage for a conversation. We talked about the vulnerability and humanity behind comedy, we talked about the band we’d create, we talked about the Muppets—and we talked about why everyone loves his character Roy Kent and all his friends on the beloved comedy series Ted Lasso. This will definitely not be our last live recording. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6zuvvBFj02eTVvcfJsEeBT</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2988</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené, Ashley, and Barrett on Perfectionism, Numbing, Boundaries, Polling, and Authenticity: A Summer Sister Series Follow-Up</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4yll80UxbgVB1efyPumvq1?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I am back with my sisters Ashley and Barrett to do a follow-up on the Summer Sister Series on The Gifts of Imperfection. We received a lot of questions in the comments after the six-episode series, so I’ve pulled my sisters back in to seek some answers. We are also knee-deep in life stuff right now, so we open up about our own struggles with some of the topics in question, including running away, setting and managing boundaries, polling others over listening to ourselves, and living in authenticity. Join us as we seek As to all the Qs from social media. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4yll80UxbgVB1efyPumvq1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2691</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Aminatou Sow and Ann Friedman on Big Friendship</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2bmgfkVEXoUgnSmIESto9f?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I’m talking with first-time authors and longtime podcasters—and even longer-time friends—Aminatou Sow and Ann Friedman. We’re talking about their book, Big Friendship: How We Keep Each Other Close, and why the lack of meaningful, intimate, vulnerable friendships is almost a crisis right now. One key learning for me is how many of us believe that friendships should be easy and require little effort, when, in reality, we can’t have any meaningful relationships without putting in meaningful work. And that’s not always easy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2bmgfkVEXoUgnSmIESto9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4331</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Sarah Niles on Life, Truth, and Ted Lasso</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4uKAJf07kruF7sfDAvaorE?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I am talking with Sarah Niles, who plays Dr. Sharon Fieldstone, the respected sports psychologist on Ted Lasso---and I just want to let you know that we have worked very hard for no show spoilers at all. It’s just a great conversation about where she came from, what she believes in, and the story of how she ended up as this central and pivotal character on one of our favorite shows. This is one of those podcasts where if you're walking, just take a deep breath. If you're driving, maybe crack the window. If you're at home, grab some hot tea or a cup of coffee. To know Sarah is to love her and appreciate her talent, her gifts, and her commitment to truth, love, and kindness. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4uKAJf07kruF7sfDAvaorE</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2781</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Esther Perel on Partnerships, Patterns, and Paradoxical Relationships</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4yYdCMNKI83j0fhtHCOfCp?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>I’m talking to Esther Perel, psychotherapist, New York Times best-selling author, and podcaster, about relationships in the pandemic and beyond. She blew my mind around some patterns that Steve and I have discovered over the past months in lockdown. We also talk a lot about paradox and straddling the tension of two competing ideas that can both be true. It’s maddening and inspiring. And you’ll hear in real time how I’m wowed, impressed, and completely Esther Perel-ed before it’s all over. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4yYdCMNKI83j0fhtHCOfCp</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4443</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Tarana Burke on Unbound, Liberation, and the Birth of the Me Too Movement</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4Dt49YUTuwS8pYTfnQtsmg?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>I’m talking to my dear friend Tarana Burke about her new memoir, Unbound: My Story of Liberation and the Birth of the Me Too Movement. Her book is beautiful, hard, and breathtaking. Tarana is unflinching in her storytelling. As she takes us on the journey that transformed her life and the world, we can feel our own transformation happening. The person who starts this book is not the person who finishes this book. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4Dt49YUTuwS8pYTfnQtsmg</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3661</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Priya Parker on How We Return and Why It Matters, Part 1 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6TmP7EnoNuiafpctzgX8tz?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>From the vault: Join me for Part 1 of a two-part series with Priya Parker on gathering together again that originally ran on my other podcast Dare to Lead. Priya is a master facilitator, strategic advisor, and the author of The Art of Gathering: How We Meet and Why It Matters. We talked late last spring about the real, big and small challenges we’ll see when we return to workspaces, the need we’ll have to use our creativity and ingenuity to figure out how to be together, and the opportunity we’ll get to ask how we can be together better. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6TmP7EnoNuiafpctzgX8tz</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3865</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Jason Sudeikis &amp; Brendan Hunt on Ted Lasso</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1OuaJxT69t6fOnxxCtUi70?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>From the vault: As the self-appointed president of the TLFC (Ted Lasso Fan Club), Brené interviewed Jason Sudeikis, the co-creator, writer and executive producer who plays Ted Lasso, and Brendan Hunt, the co-creator and writer who plays Coach Beard on the Apple TV+ hit series, as they were writing season two of the beloved show that received 20 Emmy nominations. The show follows the adventures of a small-time college football coach from Kansas hired to coach a professional soccer team in England, despite having no experience coaching soccer. We talk about the show’s interesting origin story, writers’ room inspirations, and why intention is critical to the creative process. It’s a fun conversation about a show that is unapologetically awkward, brave, and kind. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1OuaJxT69t6fOnxxCtUi70</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3075</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Us Programming Note</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1TksDkQgbbIiLkluhYCu9q?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Barrett is here today with a note to let you know that Brené is still heads down under a book deadline, so we’re going to take a few weeks off from Unlocking Us. We hope this a good opportunity for you to catch up on episodes from Brené’s two podcasts-- Dare to Lead and Unlocking Us -- because we have some really excellent new episodes coming this Fall that you’ll want to be ready for. We will be back with new Unlocking Us episodes on September 15. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1TksDkQgbbIiLkluhYCu9q</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>102</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part 6 of 6: Brené with Ashley and Barrett for the Summer Sister Series on The Gifts of Imperfection</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6DQRlCO5iwW8y4GgaOkSSb?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>It’s the final episode of our six-part Summer Sister Series on The Gifts of Imperfection with my sisters, Ashley and Barrett, and we finish strong with the last of the Guideposts: #9: Cultivating Meaningful Work: Letting Go of Self-Doubt and “Supposed To” and #10: Cultivating Laughter, Song, and Dance: Letting Go of Being Cool and “Always in Control.” We talk about how doing meaningful work connects us and how being cool is honestly, very lonely. And we finally reach the moment Ashley and Barrett have been waiting for all along—and possibly the only reason they agreed to do this series—they finally get to share their top five songs. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6DQRlCO5iwW8y4GgaOkSSb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2076</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part 5 of 6: Brené with Ashley and Barrett for the Summer Sister Series on The Gifts of Imperfection</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1FMBgRDdlV2YAP2UkRRhxD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this second-to-last episode of the Summer Sister Series on The Gifts of Imperfection, I have a couple of in-real-time revelations: namely that I suck at cultivating quality rest and play (a.k.a. Guidepost #7). Thankfully, on the flip side, I’ve gotten pretty good over the years at cultivating calm and stillness (thank you, five-mile-long daily walks) and letting go of anxiety as a lifestyle (Guidepost #8). We dig in and ask the existential question: What does your ideal restful vacation look like? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1FMBgRDdlV2YAP2UkRRhxD</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1683</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part 4 of 6: Brené with Ashley and Barrett for the Summer Sister Series on The Gifts of Imperfection</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6sm20oADcc5O8qcL2BZ70p?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This might just be the toughest, most personal episode yet in the Summer Sister Series on The Gifts of Imperfection. As Ashley, Barrett, and I tackle Guideposts #5 — Cultivating Intuition and Trusting Faith: Letting Go of the Need for Certainty — and #6 — Cultivating Creativity: Letting Go of Comparison, we reflect on our upbringing, which was marked with uncertainty, unpredictability, and plenty of eggshell living. It’s no surprise then, that letting go of certainty is one of my greatest challenges. We talk about that and how we to try to show up differently in the families we are raising now. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6sm20oADcc5O8qcL2BZ70p</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1341</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part 3 of 6: Brené with Ashley and Barrett for the Summer Sister Series on The Gifts of Imperfection</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6WwScZEpyU3YrsLFI9cq7m?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We’re at the halfway mark of our six-episode Summer Sister Series on The Gifts of Imperfection, and this week we dig into Guideposts #3 — Cultivating a Resilient Spirit: Letting Go of Numbing and Powerlessness — and #4 — Cultivating Gratitude and Joy: Letting Go of Scarcity and Fear of the Dark. Ashley, Barrett, and I look at our lives post-COVID and talk candidly about the ways we’ve numbed over the past year—and how we’ve lost some of our gratitude practices. These two things may be related. Moving forward, we (re)commit to making wholeheartedness a family affair. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6WwScZEpyU3YrsLFI9cq7m</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1932</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part 2 of 6: Brené with Ashley and Barrett for the Summer Sister Series on The Gifts of Imperfection</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2cZSnElaA0B8K2lV5RS47b?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>It's Part 2 of our six-part Summer Sister Series on The Gifts of Imperfection, with my sisters, Ashley and Barrett. In this episode, we start with Guidepost #1: Cultivating Authenticity and Letting Go of What People Think and move into Guidepost #2: Cultivating Self-Compassion and Letting Go of Perfectionism. Practicing authenticity--and yes, it is a daily practice--is really connected to boundary work, so we admit the individual fears we each experience when setting boundaries. We also talk about perfectionism as a process addiction, and how our imperfections are not inadequacies, but instead, they're reminders that we're all in this together.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cZSnElaA0B8K2lV5RS47b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2559</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part 1 of 6: Brené with Ashley and Barrett for the Summer Sister Series on The Gifts of Imperfection</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3UrjBdrskRKfjh2UCK7UHu?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Join me and my sisters, Ashley and Barrett, for Part 1 of our six-part Summer Sister Series on The Gifts of Imperfection. In this episode, we start with the Introduction, go over the 10 Guideposts, and talk about our personal Wholehearted Inventory scores. Surgeon General’s Warning: This is about as real as it gets. Equal amounts laughing, hard conversations, surprising revelations, and cussing. And some singing. But I file that under painful and/or laughing. If this sounds like your kind of conversation, join us for the rest of the series. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3UrjBdrskRKfjh2UCK7UHu</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3391</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Dr. Clint Smith on How the Word Is Passed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7zxyMWfMSJXeCCMMFPkDKw?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>I’m talking to writer, teacher, and scholar Dr. Clint Smith about his new book, How the Word Is Passed: A Reckoning with the History of Slavery Across America. We talk about the history of slavery in this country and how we approach, excavate, recognize, and react to that history—and how we have a responsibility and accountability to get the story and the history right. Because when we can be honest about the history, we can begin to acknowledge it, reckon with it, and heal from it. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7zxyMWfMSJXeCCMMFPkDKw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5778</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Ashley C. Ford on Storytelling, Truth-Telling, and Liberation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2Vvt2zaigSZ7db6WHV2Qd6?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I’m talking to writer Ashley C. Ford about her new memoir, Somebody’s Daughter, and how it is written for everyone who walks into a bookstore and feels like they can't find a book about themselves—and there are a lot of us looking for that. We talk about the writing process, the truth-telling process, and how connecting the two can be liberating not only to us, but also to others. Our conversation is not just a story about her life, it is a story about life and what connects us to show us that we are not alone--and that we are braver than we know. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2Vvt2zaigSZ7db6WHV2Qd6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3881</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Justina Blakeney on Creating Space to Reflect Our Stories</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6qxl9jkMMoscid7GeeZIC2?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I talk with Justina Blakeney, designer, artist, and New York Times best-selling author about how we can create spaces to tell our stories. We talk about how color, pattern, plants, and windy paths can be personalized to help express our individuality, and how connecting with both our unique roots and adventures allows us to not only look at objects and space differently, but also to see ourselves and our worlds in new ways. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6qxl9jkMMoscid7GeeZIC2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3758</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Oprah Winfrey and Dr. Bruce D. Perry on Trauma, Resilience, and Healing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7GgvaJ3DUL4oQyxtyr86H3?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week I’m talking to Oprah Winfrey and Dr. Bruce Perry about their new book, What Happened to You? Conversations on Trauma, Resilience, and Healing. We define trauma and talk about why big and small traumas activate our stress response systems and create emotional, physical, and social consequences, and how we can find the path to healing. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7GgvaJ3DUL4oQyxtyr86H3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4314</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Tarana Burke and Jason Reynolds on "You Are Your Best Thing"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/06QDH5SNTwSHmFYN434X2S?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week's episode features two audio essays from “You Are Your Best Thing,” an anthology on the Black lived experience of vulnerability and shame resilience, led by my friend Tarana Burke, an organizer, writer, activist, and the founder of the 'me too.' movement. It starts with an introduction from Tarana and me, followed by an essay from Jason Reynolds, award-winning and #1 New York Times bestselling author. All of the essays in the book are urgent, compelling, heartbreaking, and heart affirming. I'm proud and grateful to share this work with you. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06QDH5SNTwSHmFYN434X2S</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2604</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Jason Karlawish, M.D. on The Problem of Alzheimer’s</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7DDza4W6k9KeyPTdU7qRFC?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week I have a tough, loving conversation about dementia and Alzheimer's with Jason Karlawish, physician, researcher, professor, clinician, and author of The Problem of Alzheimer’s: How Science, Culture, and Politics Turned a Rare Disease Into a Crisis and What We Can Do About It. This heartbreakingly common diagnosis creates multiple patients—both the diagnosed and the caregivers. We talk about the difference between Alzheimer's and dementia, how we respond to a disease that diminishes our autonomy, and what we can do to take care of ourselves and each other. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7DDza4W6k9KeyPTdU7qRFC</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3817</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Samin Nosrat on Grief, Gratitude, and Connection</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7jFyKtDjKPaF50xeCZEBuo?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Get ready for a delicious conversation. I am talking to Samin Nosrat, author, cook, teacher, podcaster, and the force of nature behind the revolutionary cookbook Salt, Fat, Acid, Heat and its Netflix documentary. We connect on her work and the struggles and realities of creating connections in a period of great disconnection. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7jFyKtDjKPaF50xeCZEBuo</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3376</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Brandi Carlile on Music, Mysticism, and Broken Horses</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5Lzryk7lOVEPN3II6gHKXH?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week I’m talking to Brandi Carlile, singer, songwriter, performer, producer, activist, and author of a new memoir, Broken Horses. We talk about everything from the politics of middle school lunch tables, to the pursuit of complicated faith, to the tyranny of fitted sheets. This is a conversation between two people, meeting for the first time, and yet, somehow, it feels like we've been friends forever. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5Lzryk7lOVEPN3II6gHKXH</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3201</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Hanif Abdurraqib on Art, Culture, and Black Performance</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/63lTWMybkw5CQWzxRF9cda?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Hanif Abdurraqib is a beautiful person and an incredible writer, poet, essayist, and cultural critic. His new book, A Little Devil in America: Notes in Praise of Black Performance, took my breath away.  Hanif’s ability to straddle the tension of grief and gratitude, beauty and horror, mourning and jubilation is where the miracle and the genius happen. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63lTWMybkw5CQWzxRF9cda</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4341</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Aiko Bethea on Inclusivity at Work: The Heart of Hard Conversations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/385S52KYhZ44Is6Xyyrtxg?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Unlocking Us is here to Dare to Lead on inclusivity. In this episode, I talk to friend, colleague and Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion expert, Aiko Bethea. We discuss empathy, accountability, and the power of listening and believing (including a very real role play). We also dissect the differences between transactional leadership and transformational leadership, and why courage is a prerequisite to lasting, meaningful change. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">385S52KYhZ44Is6Xyyrtxg</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2856</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Abby Wambach on the New Rules of Leadership</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0zRdwoqoMMYqb0ZsEEJRON?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week, Unlocking Us is going to Dare to Lead! In this episode, I connect with Olympian, activist and author Abby Wambach on the new rules of leadership. Her book WOLFPACK, I kid you not, is on my top five must-read leadership books. I buy this book for everyone. It’s leadership gold. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0zRdwoqoMMYqb0ZsEEJRON</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4068</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Dr. Angus Fletcher on Life-Changing Inventions in Literature</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4bUHpeTSSKZY2ZsxLINyP7?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week I’m talking to Dr. Angus Fletcher, professor and author of Wonderworks: The 25 Most Powerful Inventions in the History of Literature, about the science behind the great writings of authors across time--from Greek tragedies, to Maya Angelou, to Tina Fey. We look at how the technology of literature can nurture democracy, power personal growth, and improve our mental health and well-being. Weaving together library and laboratory research, we discuss how literature actually changes who we are, helps us understand who we are, and teaches us how to think. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4bUHpeTSSKZY2ZsxLINyP7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4553</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Dr. Yaba Blay on One Drop: Shifting the Lens on Race</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0rP3gQOMESgPwU0MU23nfw?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I talk to Dr. Yaba Blay about her new book, One Drop: Shifting the Lens on Race. It's an honest and raw conversation about identity, grief, transformation, history, colorism, and taking responsibility for change. I continue to reflect on this quote from Dr. Blay: "Identity is nuanced. It's complicated. I think it's hard to define. Sometimes I think it's dangerous to define, depending upon who's doing the defining." Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0rP3gQOMESgPwU0MU23nfw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4822</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Dr. Edith Eger on Recognizing the Choices and Gifts in Our Lives</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4rT0TLIumjIWC0x3P6E5TX?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This week I’m talking to clinical psychologist and author Dr. Edith Eger about her books, The Choice and The Gift. Dr. Eger is a Holocaust survivor who has dedicated her career to helping us understand trauma, anger, resilience, and the power of choosing how we see ourselves and how we resist the labels that people put on us. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4rT0TLIumjIWC0x3P6E5TX</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2604</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Jennifer Rudolph Walsh and Ashley C. Ford on Hungry Hearts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3GhwF816473UEUWR5tkY6a?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I’m talking with Jennifer Rudolph Walsh and Ashley C. Ford about their work, their lives, and the new anthology Hungry Hearts, a collection of intimate stories and essays on courage, desire, and belonging. I just love talking to the storytellers and magic-makers! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3GhwF816473UEUWR5tkY6a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4452</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Roxane Gay and Debbie Millman on Love, Life, and the Pursuit of Creative Space</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6IPw6CDp14xaRqmPieFGsi?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>A conversation with two unforgettable creators: Debbie Millman and Roxane Gay. Debbie is a designer, author, educator, and the host of the award-winning podcast Design Matters; and Roxane is a writer, editor, cultural critic, and co-host of the podcast Hear to Slay. Roxane and Debbie are newlyweds, and we talk about their love story, creativity, and the power of a dinner party. Their words and art have been very influential in my life - talking to them about the ins-and-outs of ordinary life is, in itself, extraordinary. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6IPw6CDp14xaRqmPieFGsi</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5362</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Drs. John and Julie Gottman on What Makes Love Last</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6nNnUm8dhdHm4DD6QwzqSo?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Drs. Julie and John Gottman have taken more than 40 years of breakthrough research and written or co-written more than 40 books on marital stability, divorce prediction, and how science can help people have successful, loving relationships. We talk about the toll the pandemic has taken on couples, their work in the context of current events, and practical shifts that can help us take care of each other. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6nNnUm8dhdHm4DD6QwzqSo</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4928</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Emmanuel Acho on Uncomfortable Conversations with a Black Man</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7942OGiMeHjuIqpcVpzuVV?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I talk with Emmanuel Acho, creator, host, and producer of Uncomfortable Conversations with a Black Man, a web series about racism to drive open and uncomfortable dialogue. His book with the same name is a thoughtful manifesto, a mandate and a playbook that’s both generous and full of love. We get personal, and we talk about what these important questions mean in context of history and for culture today. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7942OGiMeHjuIqpcVpzuVV</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3547</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Melinda Gates on The Moment of Lift</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/29gnRftqNHRTtnC8jqIVLM?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I talk with philanthropist and global advocate for women and girls, Melinda Gates. We talk about empathy, the power of story, and about her book, The Moment of Lift - a clear and powerful call to action for gender equity. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29gnRftqNHRTtnC8jqIVLM</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4578</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené on Words, Actions, Dehumanization, and Accountability</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3VeEuyFibDfesoCOx5jUA7?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this "On My Mind" episode, we talk about shame and accountability. We discussed this a bit last summer, but I’m going deeper today in light of the insurrection at the US Capitol building and the resulting calls to unity without accountability. Dehumanization is the most significant driver of insurrection and it always starts with language. We are all responsible for recognizing it, stopping it, and holding people accountable for dehumanizing language and actions. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3VeEuyFibDfesoCOx5jUA7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2124</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Tim Ferriss and Dax Shepard on Podcasting, Daily Practices, and the Long and Winding Path to Healing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3gRCgIyUFcuaciQLUkVqgh?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>It’s a podcasters’ roundtable! In this episode, Tim Ferriss, Dax Shepard, and I talk about everything from preparing for podcasts, parenting, and ping pong, to addiction, trauma, and the long, winding road to healing and wholeness. It’s fun and hard and messy. Everything you’d expect from three people who consider curiosity a way of life. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3gRCgIyUFcuaciQLUkVqgh</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6003</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with President Barack Obama on Leadership, Family and Service</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7webPHEy75rgM8hpb3LXfZ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I talk with President Barack Obama about his life, his work, and his new book A Promised Land. We dive into the power of leaning into uncertainty, and why the rare skill of holding the tension of opposites makes us better leaders, partners, and parents. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7webPHEy75rgM8hpb3LXfZ</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3714</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené on The Queen's Gambit, Revisiting FFTs, and Resting Our Tired Brains</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6y9JKcGz34ZekA0jqugnf0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this "On My Mind" episode, we revisit FFTs and talk about tired brains and new strategies for recovering from too many hard first times. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6y9JKcGz34ZekA0jqugnf0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1883</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with David Eagleman on The Inside Story of the Ever-Changing Brain</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3zWZuSHMooOnPv5oIvDXCM?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I talk with David Eagleman, a neuroscientist, New York Times bestselling author, TED speaker, and Guggenheim Fellow, all about the brain and how it works. It’s mysterious, malleable, constantly changing and up for new challenges. We dig deeper into the research in his book Livewired: The Inside Story of the Ever-Changing Brain on the power of being uncomfortable and trying new things and how important new experiences are for continued brain development and health. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3zWZuSHMooOnPv5oIvDXCM</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3496</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Priya Parker on The Art of Gathering</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/62J7pAGnjo9VVtM35DTBdS?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I talk with Priya Parker - a master facilitator, strategic advisor, and the author of The Art of Gathering: How We Meet and Why it Matters. We dig into what it means to come together, why connection requires intention, and the often-invisible structures inside our most meaningful gatherings. Priya even helps me deconstruct my wedding and why, decades later, people still tell me how different and fun it was! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62J7pAGnjo9VVtM35DTBdS</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3676</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Dolly Parton on Songtelling, Empathy, and Shining Our Lights</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4Hl8VxJh7NUTjQ27NE4gWI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This episode is proof that dreams do come true! I get to talk to Dolly Parton about love, empathy, and the power of truth-telling. We talk about everything from her new book, Dolly Parton, Songteller: My Life in Lyrics and songwriting, to the challenges of leading organizations and Burt Reynolds. It's amazing to me how Dolly's songwriting and storytelling seems to be driven by a deep calling to turn toward pain and heartbreak so she can shine a light for all of us to find our way. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4Hl8VxJh7NUTjQ27NE4gWI</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2803</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Gabby Rivera on Superheroes, Storytelling and Joy as Resistance</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2kpy3UFwArGDIa4jklvWcv?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I talk with writer, storyteller, and joy advocate Gabby Rivera, the first Latina to write for Marvel Comics. Gabby penned the solo series America about America Chavez, a portal-punching queer Latina powerhouse. We also talk about her debut novel Juliet Takes a Breath, how important it is to see ourselves in stories about the hero’s journey, and how joy is a form of resistance. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2kpy3UFwArGDIa4jklvWcv</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3949</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené on Strong Backs, Soft Fronts, and Wild Hearts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4bzdPR8mZr8ohiJhzkFmWt?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this solo episode recorded on Election Day 2020, I talk directly to our wholehearted community about the practice that helps me when I'm feeling fearful, worried, or wobbly, and why this work is the foundation for true belonging. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4bzdPR8mZr8ohiJhzkFmWt</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1257</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Elizabeth Lesser on the Power of Women’s Stories</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/55atWP0vLw6lQGXUyhDe2Y?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I speak with Elizabeth Lesser, bestselling author and cofounder of Omega Institute, about her newest book Cassandra Speaks: When Women are the Storytellers, the Human Story Changes. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55atWP0vLw6lQGXUyhDe2Y</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3368</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing My New Podcast: Dare to Lead</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/30W4kVSx7RziKpRLSLVSZL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>What does it take to be a leader at any level? Join me every Monday on the Dare to Lead podcast as I unpack the skill-sets of courage-building, and talk to as many change-makers, culture-shifters, and troublemakers as possible. Together, we’ll have conversations that help us show up, step up, and dare to lead. In this first solo episode, I talk about my passion for this work, what we’ve been learning about courageous leadership and skill building, and the differences between armored and daring leadership. Listen now and follow Dare to Lead for free, only on Spotify!  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30W4kVSx7RziKpRLSLVSZL</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2517</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Joe Biden on Empathy, Unity and Courage</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2APKx5PPXL9Vls0tOjdLIe?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>My thoughts on power and leadership, and a conversation on empathy, unity, and courage with Vice President Joe Biden, the 2020 Democratic Presidential Nominee. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2APKx5PPXL9Vls0tOjdLIe</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2974</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Emily and Amelia Nagoski on Burnout and How to Complete the Stress Cycle   </title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6L48OhNvYeIlv7Tir3yij0?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Burnout. We're all experiencing it and we're all desperate for a way through it. In this episode, I talk to Drs. Emily and Amelia Nagoski about what causes burnout, what it does to our bodies, and how we can move through the emotional exhaustion. This has been a game-changer for me and for my family! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6L48OhNvYeIlv7Tir3yij0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3778</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Jason Sudeikis &amp; Brendan Hunt on Ted Lasso</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1ccFfMewrjJaKOvruJsIPY?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>As the self-appointed president of the TLFC (Ted Lasso Fan Club), it was a blast to talk to Jason Sudeikis, the co-creator, writer, and executive producer who plays Ted Lasso, and Brendan Hunt, the co-creator and writer who plays Coach Beard on the Apple TV+ hit series. The show follows the adventures of a small-time college football coach from Kansas hired to coach a professional soccer team in England, despite having no experience coaching soccer. We talk about the show's interesting origin story, writers' room inspirations, and why intention is critical to the creative process. It's a fun conversation about a show that is unapologetically awkward, brave, and kind. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ccFfMewrjJaKOvruJsIPY</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2977</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Bishop Michael Curry on Love &amp; Hope in Troubling Times</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0YLi9221ng9ewoA9NNZecS?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The Most Rev. Michael Curry is Presiding Bishop of The Episcopal Church, and on this episode, we talk about love. Messy, hard, complicated love. I ask him how we can transcend fear in a scarcity-based culture and what we can learn from those who came before us. We also talk about the church, how to develop beloved community, and the scrappy, gritty, work of love that is my definition of faith. Plus, Bishop Curry shares his playlist with one song that I really didn’t expect. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0YLi9221ng9ewoA9NNZecS</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4948</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On My Mind: RBG, Surge Capacity, and Play as an Energy Source</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6MXs4hnUIn0PzrMY110pQR?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I share my thoughts on the power of dissent, what happens when we max out our surge capacity during a crisis, and how time spent without purpose can refuel and reconnect us. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6MXs4hnUIn0PzrMY110pQR</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1798</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Sonya Renee Taylor on "The Body is Not an Apology"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6K5ytRMH1tMPldejD5TbKK?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode Sonya Renee Taylor and I talk about body shame, radical self-love, and social justice. This conversation was a big unlocking for me - especially when it comes to understanding the connection between how we think about our bodies and oppression. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6K5ytRMH1tMPldejD5TbKK</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4639</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Scott Sonenshein on Stretching and Chasing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0ieajR88ywXyV2ges2Fll2?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, researcher and professor Dr. Scott Sonenshein and I talk about the art and science of being scrappy, why outsiders are sometimes better than experts, and why comparison is truly the thief of joy. This book turned things upside down for me - in the best way. I hope the conversation does the same for you. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ieajR88ywXyV2ges2Fll2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3683</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené on Day 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3b9yib2wFZfZoETTpq7COq?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>So glad to be back! Launching our second season with a conversation on one of my favorite subjects (and least favorite experiences): Day 2! It sounds easy enough, but Day 2 is no joke. It’s the messy middle - the point of no return. Join us as we talk about navigating what's next and why it's always best to stumble through the darkness together. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b9yib2wFZfZoETTpq7COq</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1740</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing: It Was Said (w Jon Meacham)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3Lab19ynGFJAhQnCSxyYBn?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Welcome to It Was Said, a 10-episode limited documentary series looking back on some of the most powerful, impactful and timeless speeches in American history. Join Pulitzer Prize winning and best-selling author-historian, Jon Meacham, Peabody-nominated C13Originals Studios and HISTORY, as we take you through 10 speeches. Season One of It Was Said draws on a selection of speeches from powerful figures in history where Meacham will offer expert insight and analysis into their origins, the orator, the context of the times they were given, why they are still relevant today, and the importance of never forgetting them. Each episode of this documentary podcast series will also bring together some of the top historians, authors and journalists relevant to each respective speech and figure. Subscribe and listen to It Was Said for free now, wherever you listen to podcasts. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3Lab19ynGFJAhQnCSxyYBn</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>316</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené on Ask Me Anything, Part 2 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0A71ziMwkAF9jO6k1kBzDR?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We received so many thoughtful and tough AMA questions from listeners that it took us two episodes to cover the most popular topics. In Part 2, I unpack one of the most asked questions: How do parents build shame resilience in our children? I'm also answering another popular question: Are there TV series and/or films that I think do a great job of accurately capturing emotions and the human experience? While there are SO many that do that well, I share a few of my current favorites. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0A71ziMwkAF9jO6k1kBzDR</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1812</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené on Ask Me Anything, Part 1 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5f4bgRWkDHBLopdOshelQv?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>I said, “Ask Me Anything,” and the Unlocking Us community came through with the tough questions. To be honest, I thought I’d get some easy, fun ones—but no, all deep-end questions. In fact, we had hundreds and hundreds of tough, smart, thoughtful questions submitted, and in today’s episode I answer five of them. We cover ‘fake news,’ disappointment vs self-pity, religion and shame, when something is shame-worthy, and we’re just getting started. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f4bgRWkDHBLopdOshelQv</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2918</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené on Shame and Accountability</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4ypjS5u16CzxusNkLzugmQ?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In today’s solo episode, I share my thoughts about why accountability is a prerequisite for change, and why we need to get our heads and hearts around the difference between being held accountable for racism and feeling shame, and being shamed. I share my personal stories of being held accountable and holding myself accountable, as well as my strategies for pulling my “thinking brain” back online when I’m experiencing the flight and fight energy fueled by shame. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ypjS5u16CzxusNkLzugmQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2714</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Judd Apatow on Vulnerability and Laughter</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7qYoFH7SlmfYLBrYqlJf4U?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>I'm talking with Judd Apatow, who has directed, produced, and written many of the biggest comedy films and hit TV shows of the last two decades. We look at what's funny, why it's funny, and why laughter creates connection. We also uncover that thin line between humor and grief and what it means to tell the stories of our lives in a way that we recognize ourselves and our shared humanity. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7qYoFH7SlmfYLBrYqlJf4U</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3815</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Gina Chavez and Carrie Rodriguez on the Heart and Soul of Music</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4cjnHxETT2GeJh1tmjhfHa?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Meet Carrie Rodriguez and Gina Chavez, the musicians who created and perform the music you hear every week on Unlocking Us. Artists and activists, Gina and Carrie integrate stories, culture, and the heart of past generations into their music to create artful and hopeful futures. You can hear it in their music, and you can see it in their lives. I’m so grateful that our weekly Unlocking Us conversations begin and end with their soulful sounds. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cjnHxETT2GeJh1tmjhfHa</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4740</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Laverne Cox on Transgender Representation, Advocacy + the Power of Love</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7CwLfxxxpM8hfekGqvGf8J?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I talk to artist, advocate, executive producer, and all-around amazing woman and friend Laverne Cox about her new, groundbreaking documentary, Disclosure: Trans Lives on Screen, the importance of policy protection for the trans community, and the seismic shifts in the world today. We also discuss the complexities of intersectionality and accountability, the difference between discomfort and safety, and the ultimate power of seeking love and living in the light. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7CwLfxxxpM8hfekGqvGf8J</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3686</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Austin Channing Brown on I’m Still Here: Black Dignity in a World Made for Whiteness</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5fCZPAJgoSlrCU7Gj5IFYE?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Austin Channing Brown’s anti-racism work is critical to changing our world, and her ability to talk about what is good and true about love, about our faith, and about loving each other is transformative. She is a writer, a speaker, and a media producer providing inspired leadership on racial justice in America. In this episode, we connect on her book I’m Still Here: Black Dignity in a World Made for Whiteness, and talk about her online television show, The Next Question. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5fCZPAJgoSlrCU7Gj5IFYE</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3838</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Ibram X. Kendi on How to Be an Antiracist</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/53R0DZptFINuwJLjNqo32D?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>I'm talking with professor Ibram Kendi, New York Times bestselling author of How to Be an Antiracist and the Director of the Antiracist Research and Policy Center at American University. We talk about racial disparities, policy, and equality, but we really focus on How to Be an Antiracist, which is a groundbreaking approach to understanding uprooting racism and inequality in our society and in ourselves. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53R0DZptFINuwJLjNqo32D</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3696</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Reese Witherspoon &amp; Kerry Washington on Little Fires Everywhere</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6nSKGwZTOnD9L9GhdHv9ZD?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Reese Witherspoon and Kerry Washington are true creatives and storytellers, working to make timely art that is honest and vulnerable and truth-telling. Here’s part two of my conversation on Little Fires Everywhere. This episode covers how Reese and Kerry worked with a team of other creatives to bring Celeste’s words to life. We talked about the challenges and responsibilities of creating authentic, living, breathing characters with complex internal thoughts. We talked about motherhood and how it connects us, changes us, and changes as it goes. And we talked about creating art that honors ordinary, complicated people from completely different backgrounds, while connecting us all together. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6nSKGwZTOnD9L9GhdHv9ZD</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3939</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené and Celeste Ng on Little Fires Everywhere</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4IAy4fS9X0m0LLTwJsvjvN?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>My conversation with Celeste Ng is the first of two episodes on Little Fires Everywhere, where I'll cover the book and the series. We talked about the writing process, the stories that we tell, and the stories that define us. We also covered how our hometowns shape us, how parenting is a shame minefield, and how we all have the power to mourn moments even while we’re in them. Celeste also filled us in on what she thinks about the series and what it felt like watching Reese Witherspoon and Kerry Washington create a show from her novel. I loved this episode as a reader, as a writer, and as an observer of what it means to be human. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4IAy4fS9X0m0LLTwJsvjvN</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3759</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Jay Duplass and Mark Duplass on The Power of Paradox</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/7LFXOXvzngotIIVAyUPKxE?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Jay and Mark Duplass are two of my favorite humans. They are film-makers, writers, directors, producers, actors, and activists. They’re also partners, fathers, and brothers who believe in connection, love, and the importance of small moments. In this episode we talk about their memoir, Like Brothers, and how so much of what we crave in life comes from straddling the paradoxes inherent in love, creativity, and relationships. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7LFXOXvzngotIIVAyUPKxE</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5161</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harriet Lerner and Brené - I’m Sorry: How To Apologize &amp; Why It Matters, Part 2 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2pkVKCdRVgeQ00PyszmMLP?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This two-episode special is based on a course that Dr. Harriet Lerner and I did together on her groundbreaking book, “Why Won’t You Apologize?: Healing Big Betrayals and Everyday Hurts.” You can expect authentic, hard conversations (and one helluva role play) about making mistakes, healing hurts, and being brave. Harriet is a friend, mentor, and teacher. Her work has shaped my career and made my life better. During a time of deep uncertainty and anxiety - when many of us have struggled to be our best selves all of the time - apologizing has never been more important. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2pkVKCdRVgeQ00PyszmMLP</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4512</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harriet Lerner and Brené - I’m Sorry: How To Apologize &amp; Why It Matters, Part 1 of 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2jxcLXMB672u5dpc9YqDu9?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>This two-episode special is based on a course that Dr. Harriet Lerner and I did together on her groundbreaking book, “Why Won’t You Apologize?: Healing Big Betrayals and Everyday Hurts.” You can expect authentic, hard conversations (and one helluva role play) about making mistakes, healing hurts, and being brave. Harriet is a friend, mentor, and teacher. Her work has shaped my career and made my life better. During a time of deep uncertainty and anxiety - when many of us have struggled to be our best selves all of the time - apologizing has never been more important. ( Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2jxcLXMB672u5dpc9YqDu9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4315</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené with Sue Monk Kidd and Jen Hatmaker on Longing, Belonging and Faith</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4n9fCBnNLeAFmM7iODDGBo?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In this episode, I talk to two women who provide wise counsel for those of us who have struggled with belonging and faith (and still do on occasion). Sue Monk Kidd and Jen Hatmaker are dissident daughters, brave leaders, and the very best companions for a contemplative journey. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4n9fCBnNLeAFmM7iODDGBo</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>4933</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Vivek Murthy and Brené on loneliness and connection</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5k83Zo3xagECvKANgmcRTl?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Have you ever struggled with feeling lonely - even when you’re surrounded by people you love? I have. It’s painful and confusing. In this episode, I talk to Dr. Vivek Murthy, a physician and the 19th Surgeon General of the United States, about loneliness and the physical and emotional toll that social disconnection takes on us. We talk about his new book, TOGETHER, and what it takes for each of us to tilt the world toward love and connection. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5k83Zo3xagECvKANgmcRTl</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3234</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Marc Brackett and Brené on “Permission to Feel”</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6fL2uT9nJRUsWcRqlKgXuS?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Dr. Marc Brackett has dedicated his life to studying emotions and to teaching us what he’s learning. In this episode, we talk about how emotional literacy - being able to recognize, name, and understand our feelings - affects everything from learning, decision making, and creativity, to relationships, health, and performance. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6fL2uT9nJRUsWcRqlKgXuS</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3173</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alicia Keys and Brené on More Myself</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/10sxcptFGlrGGBTzx3VeAR?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Alicia’s book, More Myself: A Journey, is a masterclass in authenticity and vulnerability. In this episode, Alicia and I talk about the quiet, subtle experiences that fuel our need to armor up and self-protect, and the courage behind owning our worth, listening to our own voice, and living with our own “girl on fire” energy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10sxcptFGlrGGBTzx3VeAR</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3725</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené on Anxiety, Calm + Over/Under-Functioning</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/3TBa32kXLjT1sPJ44RDH4l?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We all have patterned ways of managing our day-to-day anxiety, and these patterns often reflect the roles and expectations of our first families. In this episode, we’ll talk about over and under-functioning in anxious times, why anxiety is contagious, and how we can cultivate a calm practice.   Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3TBa32kXLjT1sPJ44RDH4l</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1773</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Kessler and Brené on Grief and Finding Meaning</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/02NfXb67kxDN55vNIURgPV?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Grief expert David Kessler takes us by the hand and walks us into what he's learned about love, loss, and finding meaning. As someone who has a lot of fear about grief and grieving, this conversation is not what I expected. The only word I can use to describe what I learned from David is "beautiful." Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02NfXb67kxDN55vNIURgPV</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2764</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené on Comparative Suffering, the 50/50 Myth, and Settling the Ball</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5gJS0eDh1lQDCLRmxCDLKj?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>We have collectively hit weary. This is especially true for the brave folks on the front lines of this pandemic and for the people who love and support them. And, it’s also true for all of us. In this episode, I talk about strategies for falling apart, staying connected + kind, and giving ourselves permission to feel hard things. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5gJS0eDh1lQDCLRmxCDLKj</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1496</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glennon Doyle and Brené on Untamed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5zGCm7riA1pjlBGwvxFIC7?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Strap yourselves in! In this episode, I talk to my dear friend and sister Cheetah, Glennon – author of the New York Times #1 bestseller, Untamed. This is an honest conversation about walking away from the lifelong training that keeps us small, quiet, and afraid, and embracing our wild, brave hearts. Glennon is the author of two #1 New York times bestsellers – Untamed and Love Warrior. She’s the author of the New York Times bestseller, Carry On, Warrior, an activist, and the founder of Together Rising, an all-women led nonprofit organization that has revolutionized grassroots philanthropy – raising over $25 Million for women, families and children in crisis. She lives in Florida with her wife and three children. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5zGCm7riA1pjlBGwvxFIC7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>3930</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarana Burke and Brené on Being Heard and Seen</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1zLUgXuBxyJJW6s87oZuKt?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Tarana is a good friend and one of my favorite people on earth. She has been working at the intersection of racial justice and gender equity for nearly three decades, and she started the “Me Too” Movement in 2006.  In 2017, when the #metoo hashtag went viral, Tarana emerged as a global leader in the evolving conversation around sexual violence. In this episode we talk about how her theory of “empowerment through empathy” is changing the way the world thinks and talks about sexual violence, consent, and social justice. AND, we also talk/cry/laugh about falling in love, running as fast as we can from love, and the perils of sharing a bathroom with the guys we love. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1zLUgXuBxyJJW6s87oZuKt</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5226</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brené on FFTs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6UAoHu3VQJNrZcBubo4ABF?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The first Unlocking Us podcast is here! Along with the excitement of sending this into the world, I’m feeling equal doses of fear, Awkwardness, And Vulnerability. In this episode I talk about my strategy for staying in tough first times versus tapping out and shutting down. When we get to the point that we only do things that we’re already good at doing, we stop growing. And truly living. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6UAoHu3VQJNrZcBubo4ABF</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2272</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing: Unlocking Us</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/14iBaBeFNMvHcoZKdJsPRi?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Join researcher and #1 New York Times best-selling author Brené Brown as she unpacks and explores the ideas, stories, experiences, books, films, and music that reflect the universal experiences of being human, from the bravest moments to the most brokenhearted.  Subscribe now for updates. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14iBaBeFNMvHcoZKdJsPRi</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>115</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

