<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Whistleblowers</title>
    <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/4bsB2xF1giPoZqPFD3xX13</link>
    <description>Would you risk it all - your career, your life, even the lives of your family - for what you believe in? In Whistleblowers, we explore the biggest, most bizarre lies in history, through the eyes of those who risked absolutely everything to expose them. Every Tuesday, we delve into captivating stories of corruption. There are respected spiritual leaders who ask way too much of their followers. Doctors with sinister motives. Governments that value profit over all else. And at the heart of every tale is a whistleblower who put everything on the line to tell the truth, and paid the price. Whistleblowers is a Spotify Original from Parcast, hosted by Pat Rodriguez.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8a7cb80abbbddaca85acc4f044</url>
      <title>Whistleblowers</title>
      <link>https://api.spotify.com/v1/shows/4bsB2xF1giPoZqPFD3xX13</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:41:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Big Tobacco Whistleblower</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/74Te5C9mZLV6ZAt9Mry2wr?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>When biochemist Jeffrey Wigand took a job in the tobacco industry, he hoped he could improve it from the inside, and develop a ‘healthier’ cigarette. But before long, Jeff discovered deadly truths that Big Tobacco had tried to hide. He was faced with a dilemma: Should he stay quiet, and keep collecting his generous salary? Or blow the whistle, and make a life-changing sacrifice? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74Te5C9mZLV6ZAt9Mry2wr</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2385</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Walrus Whistleblower</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1EQph0KvWzLmnu65TZ4TSL?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In 2013, animal trainer Phil Demers was accused of plotting to kidnap an 800lb walrus named Smooshi. The accuser was Phil’s former employer: an aquatic amusement park in Niagara Falls, Canada. The park’s management claims he’s a disgruntled ex-employee with a penchant for fame. While Phil insists he’s an industry whistleblower trying to expose malpractice. This is their still-unfolding story. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1EQph0KvWzLmnu65TZ4TSL</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2196</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The FBI 9/11 Whistleblowers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/4hl7mVs4TP6kovfEl75oHx?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In late August 2001, Minneapolis FBI agents predicted a major terrorist attack. They raced against the clock to try and stop it, but came up against a wall of bureaucracy. When their worst fears were realized on 9/11, the agents felt that something had to change. In the end, only the bravest would speak up and criticize the government of a grieving nation. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4hl7mVs4TP6kovfEl75oHx</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2826</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Nuclear Bomb Whistleblower</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/70faTrynX73N3SiBSNp17J?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Nuclear lab technician Frits Veerman first met officemate Abdul Qadeer Khan in 1971. The two quickly became fast friends. But then Frits began to suspect that Abdul had dark intentions. When he tried to blow the whistle, he was silenced and accused of being a spy. In the end, Frits’ suspicions turned out to be just the tip of the iceberg. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70faTrynX73N3SiBSNp17J</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2305</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Princess Diana Whistleblower</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/51JBgWO5gK95dw2MN21yEh?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Princess Diana shocked the world when, in 1995, she appeared on BBC TV and spoke about her failing marriage, her husband’s affair, and an alleged royal campaign against her. The public were mesmerized by the Princess's honesty. And the journalist who interviewed Diana, Martin Bashir, was praised for landing the scoop of the century. It wasn’t until twenty five years later that the world learned about the web of lies and deception behind the interview. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">51JBgWO5gK95dw2MN21yEh</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2751</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Kray Twins Whistleblower</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0RIeWKpOcKHz9FUqKAlorw?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>The Kray twins were the kings of East London in the early 1960s. With their string of glamorous bars and casinos, they attracted the attention of the rich and famous. Behind closed doors, they were violent gangsters who would do anything for power and money. They relied on a circle of close associates to help run their empire. But when they began to take those associates for granted, their crowns began to slip. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0RIeWKpOcKHz9FUqKAlorw</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2357</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Chelsea Manning Story</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/2165vpjlVfCLwXDdykK5Or?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In 2010, U.S. soldier Chelsea Manning leaked thousands of explosive military documents to WikiLeaks. At first, it seemed like she’d gotten away with her crime. So why did she confess to a complete stranger a few weeks later?  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2165vpjlVfCLwXDdykK5Or</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2339</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Russian Doping Whistleblower</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0YCwi8kmvkrDuCLMEZSGdi?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Just like Romeo and Juliet, Vitaly Stepanov and Yuliya Rusanova were never supposed to be together. He was an anti-doping officer and she was a drug-taking athlete. But their turbulent love story led them to expose one of the biggest scandals in Russia’s sporting history. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0YCwi8kmvkrDuCLMEZSGdi</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2450</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The UFO Whistleblower</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/5IZ5kzHxAQ3SkRUiEm2gMC?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In 2021, U.S. Intelligence Agent Lue Elizondo made headlines when he told the world about worrying UFO sightings. Sightings that he said the government had ignored. Lue claimed that he had been the director of a secret UFO department at the Pentagon, but when his colleagues denied that he’d ever worked there, Lue's credibility began to crumble. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5IZ5kzHxAQ3SkRUiEm2gMC</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2291</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Chinese HIV Whistleblower</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/6dAOQhhMjlWZfhtI0nspns?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In the 1990s, China’s poorest communities could make good money by selling their blood to government plasma stations. When Dr. Shuping Wang discovered these stations were the source of a Hepatitis C epidemic, she thought things couldn’t get any worse. But then she realized the blood banks were spreading an even deadlier virus to the country’s poorest people. When she spoke up, she paid dearly. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6dAOQhhMjlWZfhtI0nspns</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2044</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Facebook Whistleblower</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/0uq1pfeqoDaWRwdRoPKNX3?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In 2020, Facebook employee Frances Haugen came across shocking internal reports. Reports suggesting that Facebook’s platforms could be far more dangerous than the public realized. Reports that mentioned teen suicide, human trafficking, and even genocide. Reports that Frances would go on to share with the world. This is the story of one woman’s battle with one of the most powerful companies on the planet.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0uq1pfeqoDaWRwdRoPKNX3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2396</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Supersurgeon Whistleblower</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/74o8ed34Wut2SezJZXIX59?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Dr. Oscar Simonson had great hopes for his future when he started working under famous supersurgeon Paolo Macchiarini. But by the end of their working relationship, Oscar’s career was in ruins, hearts were broken and several lives had been lost forever. Oscar was left asking himself: Was Paolo more con man than genius? This is a story that even the Pope, Elton John, and the Obamas were unwittingly dragged into. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74o8ed34Wut2SezJZXIX59</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2409</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hot Yoga Whistleblowers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1TP3LTwlKxUvlk6TJi69lG?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Bikram Choudhury was once Hollywood’s favorite yoga guru. His life-changing hot yoga classes attracted celebrities like Madonna, Lady Gaga, and David Beckham. But when his closest assistant started to suspect that Bikram wasn’t as holy as he claimed, she started digging. That’s when his true colors started to show…  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1TP3LTwlKxUvlk6TJi69lG</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2294</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Tuskegee Experiment Whistleblower</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/1OjZjV6s2392xdtLOPZhiI?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>In the fall of 1966, public health worker Peter Buxtun overheard a conversation in the work canteen that changed his life forever. He found out that for the last 30 years, the U.S. government had funded a racist and unethical experiment that had left hundreds of black, Southern men ill or dying. And his colleagues in public health had no plans to shut it down. When Peter set out to discover why, he uncovered the most shocking health scandal in America’s history. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1OjZjV6s2392xdtLOPZhiI</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2515</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Whistleblowers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ <iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/episode/60pqccCRZht8alc3usrEeA?utm_source=generator" width="100%" height="232" frameBorder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe><p>Have you ever discovered something you wished you hadn’t? A secret… a lie… a crime, even? What if that discovery opened up a Pandora's box of corruption… corruption that was harming hundreds, even thousands of people? And what if sharing that discovery would put you and your family in danger? Would you keep your mouth shut? Or take the risk, and blow the whistle? Whistleblowers is a new Spotify Original from Parcast where we explore some of the most bizarre lies in history, through the eyes of the people who risked everything to expose them. Starting January 18th. New episodes weekly. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</p> ]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60pqccCRZht8alc3usrEeA</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>82</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

